All right, all right, all
right, what's it going to be?
A triple cream cup for Christopher...
A Squelchy Snorter for Otis...
A Sizzler for June Marie...
- And listen! Wonka's got a new one today.
- What is it?
This is called a Scrumdidilyumptious Bar.
Scrumbibilyunctions Bar?
How does he do it?
- My dear boy, do you ask a fish how it swims?
- No.
- Or a bird how it flies?
No sirree, you don't!
They do it because they were
born to do it.
Just like Willy Wonka was
born to be a candy man,
you look like you were
born to be a Wonkerer.
♪ Who can take a sunrise ♪
♪ Sprinkle it with dew ♪
♪ Cover it in chocolate
And a miracle or two ♪
♪ The Candy Man ♪
♪ The Candy Man can ♪
♪ The Candy Man can
'Cause he mixes it with love ♪
♪ And makes the world taste good ♪
♪ Who can take a rainbow ♪
♪ Wrap it in a sigh ♪
♪ Soak it in the sun
And make a strawberry lemon pie ♪
♪ The Candy Man? ♪
♪ The Candy Man! ♪
♪ The Candy Man can ♪
♪ The Candy Man can
'Cause he mixes it with love ♪
- ♪ And makes the world taste good ♪
- Me! Me!
♪ Willy Wonka makes ♪
♪ Everything he bakes ♪
♪ Satisfying and delicious ♪
♪ Talk about your childhood wishes ♪
♪ You can even eat the dishes ♪
♪ Who can take tomorrow ♪
♪ Dip it in a dream ♪
♪ Separate the sorrow
And collect up all the cream ♪
- ♪ The Candy Man ♪
- ♪ Willy Wonka can ♪
♪ The Candy Man can ♪
♪ The Candy Man can
'Cause he mixes it with love ♪
♪ And makes the world taste good ♪
♪ And the world tastes good ♪
♪ 'Cause the Candy Man thinks it should ♪
Hi, Mr. Jopeck.
Ah, come along, Charlie.
You're late.
It's payday, Mr. Jopeck.
You're right.
- There you are.
- Thanks.
- Say hello to your Grandpa Joe.
- Okay.
Up the airy mountain
Down the rushing glen
We dare not go a-hunting
For fear of little men
You see...
Nobody ever goes in...
and nobody ever comes out!
Charlie's late.
He works too hard for a little boy.
He should have some time to play.
Not enough hours in the day.
With the four of you bedridden
for the past twenty years,
it takes a lot of work
to keep this family going.
If only his father were alive.
Soon as I get my strength back, I'm
gonna get out of this bed and help him.
Dad, in all the years you've been saying
you're going to get out of that bed,
I've yet to see you set foot
on the floor.
Well... maybe if the floor wasn't so cold.
Hi, everybody!
Wake up. Charlie's home!
Grandpa George.
Grandma Georgina.
Grandma Josephine.
Grandpa Joe.
Is this your supper, Grandpa?
Well, it's yours too, Charlie.
I'm fed up with cabbage water.
It's not enough!
- Charlie!
- It's all we have.
What are you saying?
- How about this?
- Charlie, where'd you get that?
What difference does it make where
he got it? Point is: he got it.
It's my first pay day.
Good for you, Charlie.
We'll have a real banquet.
Mom...?
Here's what's left. You keep it.
Except for this.
From now on, I'm going to
pay for your tobacco.
No one's going to pay for it, Charlie.
I'm giving it up.
Come on, Dad, it's only one pipe a day.
When a loaf of bread looks like a
banquet, I've no right buying tobacco.
Go on, Grandpa.
Please take it.
After I finished my paper route,
I was in front of Wonka's.
There was this strange man there.
I think he was a tinker.
He was standing right behind me,
looking up at the factory.
Just before he left he said,
"Nobody ever goes in,
and nobody ever comes out."
And right he was, Charlie.
Not since the tragic day
that Willy Wonka locked it.
Why'd he lock it?
Because all the other chocolate makers
in the world were sending in spies,
dressed as workers, to steal
Mr. Wonka's secret recipes.
Especially Slugworth... Oh,
that Slugworth, he was the worst!
Finally Mr. Wonka shouted
"I shall be ruined!"
"Close the factory!"
And that's just what he did.
He locked the gates and
vanished completely.
And then suddenly, about three years later,
the most amazing thing happened.
The factory started working
again, full blast!
And more delicious candies were
coming out than ever before.
But the gates stayed
locked so that no one,
not even Mr. Slugworth, could steal them.
But Grandpa, someone must be
helping Mr. Wonka work the factory.
Thousands must be helping him.
But who?
Who are they?
That is the biggest mystery of them all.
- Charlie Bucket?
- Yes, Mr. Turkentine?
I shall need an assistant.
Come and give me a hand.
We have here nitric acid, glycerine...
and a special mixture of
my own.
Together it's horrible, dangerous stuff.
Blows you up.
But mixed together in the right way, as only
I know how, what do you think it makes?
- I don't know, sir.
- Of course you don't know.
You don't know
because only I know.
If you knew and I didn't know, then you'd
be teaching me instead of me teaching you.
And for a student to teach his teacher is
presumptuous and rude. Do I make myself clear?
- Yes, sir.
- Good.
Now, mixed together in the right way
these three highly dangerous ingredients
make the finest wart remover in the world.
The trick is to pour them in in
equal amount.
Now, Charlie, you take the
nitric acid and the glycerine,
and I'll take my own special
mixture. You ready?
Good lad. Pour.
Did we do it wrong?
No, certainly not. This
is for very big warts.
Now what's going on out there?
You, Winkelmann, come here.
What's happening?
Willy Wonka's opening his factory.
He's gonna let people in.
Are you sure?
It's on the radio. And he's giving
truckloads of chocolate away.
- Class dismissed!
- No, no, it's only for five people.
Class un-dismissed.
He's hidden five Golden Tickets, and the
people who find them will win the big prize.
Where's he hidden the tickets?
Inside five Wonka Bars! You
gotta buy Wonka Bars to find 'em!
Class re-dismissed!
And now, details on the sudden announcement
that has captured the
attention of entire world.
Hidden among the countless
billions of Wonka Bars
are five gold tickets,
and to the five people who find them will
come the most fabulous prize one could wish for:
a lifetime supply of chocolate.
And as if this were not enough,
each winner before he receives his prize
will be personally escorted through
the top secret chocolate factory.
They're all crazy!
Sssshhh! The man's a genius!
He'll sell a million bars.
Grandpa, do you think I've got a
chance to find one?
One? I'm counting on you to find all five!
One's enough for me.
Already we have reports coming in
that the response is phenomenal.
Wonka Bars are beginning to disappear
from candy store shelves at
a rate to boggle the mind.
Truly it is incredible,
the way that Wonkamania
has descended upon the globe.
While the world searches, we
watch and wait,
wondering where the pursuit will lead and
how long the spirit of man will hold up
under the strain.
I'm still having these dreams, Doctor, and I
still can't stop myself from believing them.
I've told you, Mr. Hofstedder,
to believe in one's dreams
is a manifestation of insanity.
And the sooner you accept this,
the sooner you will get well.
But I dreamed the Archangel appeared and whispered
into my ear and told me where to find a Golden Wonka Ticket.
And what exactly did he say?
Well what difference does that
make? This was a dream, a fantasy.
- I mean, you said just now...
- Shut up, Hofstedder, and tell me where the ticket is!
We began with five Golden Tickets,
like five lucky bolts of lightning ready to
strike without notice at any point on the map.
No one knew where, no one knew when the
first one would hit.
But as you all know, last
night we got our answer.
While we in America slept, the
first golden ticket was found
in the small town of
Duselheim, Germany.
We've been waiting several hours for the follow-up
story and we're finally ready with a live report.
Proud we are, for the attention
of the entire world
focuses today right here in Duselheim.
A community suddenly thrust into prominence
by the unexpected discovery of
the first Wonka Golden Ticket.
Its lucky finder is the son of our
most prominent parve butcher.
The boy's name?
Augustus Gloop.
Augustus Gloop, the pride of Duselheim,
the fame of Western Germany,
an example for the whole world.
Augustus, how does it make you feel
to be the first Golden Ticket finder?
- Hungry.
- Any other feelings?
Feel sorry for Wonka.
It's gonna cost him a fortune in fudge.
Mr. Gloop, would you mind saying...
Mrs. Gloop, would you care to say a few
words to the television audience?
I just knew Augustus would find a Golden Ticket.
Eating is his hobby, you know.
We encourage him...
Happy Birthday, Charlie!
Here you are, Charlie.
Thank you.
It's terrific.
We each knitted a bit: Grandma
Georgina, Grandma Josephine, and me.
I did the end pieces with the little tassels.
And here's a little gift from
Grandpa George and me.
I think I know what this is.
- It is! A Wonka!
- Open it, Charlie.
Let's see that Golden Ticket.
- Wouldn't that be fantastic?
- It's not fair to raise his hopes.
Never mind. Go on, open it, Charlie.
I want to see that gold.
Stop it, Dad.
- I've got the same chance as anybody else, haven't I?
- You've got more, Charlie, because you want it more.
Go on, open it.
Here goes.
- I got it!
- Where? Where?
Let's see!
Fooled you, didn't I?
You thought I really had it.
Never mind, Charlie.
You'll find one.
- Here, everybody have a bite.
- No no no, you eat it.
I wanted to be the first to find
a Golden Ticket, Daddy.
I know, Angel.
We're doing the best we can.
I've got every girl on the
bleeding staff hunting for you.
All right, where is it?
Why haven't they found it?
Veruca, sweetheart, I'm not a magician!
Give me time!
I want it now! What's the matter
with those twerps down there?
For five days now the entire
flipping factory's been on the job.
They haven't shelled a peanut
in there since Monday.
They've been shelling flaming
chocolate bars from dawn to dusk.
Make 'em work nights.
Come along, come along,
you girls,
put a jack in it or you'll be out
on your ears, every one of you!
And listen to this.
The first girl that finds a Golden Ticket
gets a one pound bonus in her pay bucket!
What do you think of that?
They're not even trying.
They don't want to find it.
They're jealous of me.
Sweetheart, I can't push 'em no harder.
Nineteen thousand bars
an hour they're shelling.
Seven hundred and sixty
thousand they've done so far.
You promised, Daddy!
You promised I'd have
it the very first day!
You're going to very unpopular around here,
Henry, if you don't deliver soon.
It breaks my heart, Henrietta.
I hate to see her unhappy.
I won't talk to you ever again.
You're a rotten, mean father.
You never give me anything I want.
And I won't go to school 'til I have it.
Veruca, sweetheart, angel...
Now. There are only four
tickets left in the whole world,
and the whole ruddy
world's hunting for them.
What can I do?
I got it! I got it, Mr. Salt, here it is!
It's about time too! I want it!
Give me that ticket! It's mine!
I've found a Golden Ticket!
Thank God for that.
Aye. Happiness is what
counts with children.
Happiness and harmony.
This, ladies and gentlemen, is the sign of
our times, the symbol of the havoc,
the mad craze that's
sweeping the world today.
Whatever corner of the globe we are in,
whichever of the five continents we're on,
the great search for
Wonka Bars continues.
We're now nearing the end of our forty-third
day in the hunt for Golden Tickets,
and everywhere we're beginning
to see signs of anxiety.
Every hour on the hour,
new shipments are being sent to
different points around the globe,
but they're just not moving fast enough.
And as time passes, the men who seek
them become more and more desperate.
Gentlemen, I know how anxious you've
all been during these last few days,
but now I think I can safely say
that your time and money
have been well spent.
We're about to witness the greatest
miracle of the machine age.
Based on the revolutionary Computonian
Law of Probability this machine
will tell us the precise location
of the three remaining
Golden Tickets.
It says:
"I won't tell. That
would be cheating."
I am now telling the computer that,
if it will tell me the correct answer,
I will gladly share with it
the grand prize.
He says:
"What would a computer do with
a lifetime supply of chocolate?"
I am now telling the computer exactly what he
can do with a lifetime supply of chocolate.
And it can happen right here too,
unbelievable as it sounds
right here in America.
Where even in the smallest town,
the happiest of dreams can come true.
Because folks, here she is.
Miss Violet Beauregarde, finder of
Wonka's Golden Ticket Number Three,
from Miles City, Montana.
And with her, the proud parents:
Mr. Beauregarde, a prominent local
politician, a great civic leader, a philosopher...
Hi, folks, Sam Beauregarde here,
Square Deal Sam to you,
with all of today's great give-away bargains.
The finest values you'll get
anywhere in the entire country.
- Now this little number right here's a four door sedan...
- Come on, Dad, they don't want you!
- Violet, would you care to say a few words to the nation?
- Sure I will.
Here it is, Golden Ticket Number
Three, and it's all mine.
Tell us how it happened, Violet.
Well I'm a gum-chewer, normally, but when
I heard about these ticket things of Wonka's,
I laid off the gum and
switched to candy bars instead.
Now, of course, I'm right back on gum.
I chew it all day except at meal
times when I stick it behind my ear.
- Violet...
- Cool it, Mother.
Now this piece of gum here is one that I've been chewing
on for three months solid, and that's a world record.
It's beaten the record held by my best
friend Miss Cornelia Prinzmetel,
and was she mad!
Hi, Cornelia, how are you sweetie?
Let me just butt in here for a moment to say that if
any of you folks watching are dissatisfied with your...
- Charlie, what are you doing here?
- I thought if you were ready, I'd walk you home.
I wish I were, but it looks like I'm
gonna be here late tonight.
Oh, well, then I guess I'll be going.
Well why don't you stay a minute?
Here, pull up a pile of clothes and sit down.
Everything all right at school?
Yep.
Good.
Go on your newspaper route today?
Just finished.
Good.
I wanted to tell you something.
They found the third ticket today.
Did they?
Yeah.
Well...
Guess I'll be going now.
Is that all?
Well I thought you'd like to know.
Most people are pretty interested.
I know I'm interested.
There are only two tickets
left, you know. Just two.
Pretty soon just one.
I wonder who the lucky ones will be.
Well in case you're wondering
if it'll be me, it won't be.
Just in case you're wondering,
you can count me out.
Charlie, there are a hundred
billion people in this world,
and only five of them
will find Golden Tickets.
Even if you had a sackful of money
you probably wouldn't find one.
And after this contest is over, you'll be no different
from the billions of others who didn't find one.
But I am different. I want it
more than any of them.
Charlie, you'll get your chance.
One day things will change.
When? When will they change?
Probably when you least expect it.
See you later.
♪ You get blue
Like everyone ♪
♪ But me and Grandpa Joe ♪
♪ Can make your troubles go away ♪
♪ Blow away ♪
♪ There they go ♪
♪ Cheer up, Charlie ♪
♪ Give me a smile ♪
♪ What happened to that smile
I used to know ♪
♪ Don't you know your grin ♪
♪ Has always been
My sunshine ♪
♪ Let that sunshine show ♪
♪ Come on, Charlie ♪
♪ No need to frown ♪
♪ Deep down you know ♪
♪ The world is still your toy ♪
♪ When the world gets heavy ♪
♪ Never pit-a-pat 'em ♪
♪ Up and at 'em, boy ♪
♪ Someday ♪
♪ Sweet as a song ♪
♪ Charlie's lucky day will come along ♪
♪ 'Til that day
You've gotta stay in strong, Charlie ♪
♪ Up on top
Is right where you belong ♪
♪ Look up, Charlie ♪
♪ You'll see a star ♪
♪ Just follow it ♪
♪ And keep your dream in view ♪
♪ Pretty soon the sky
Is gonna clear up, Charlie ♪
♪ Cheer up, Charlie, do ♪
♪ Cheer up, Charlie ♪
♪ Just be glad you're you ♪
While the rest of the world
goes on searching,
here in the Southwest
it has actually happened.
That's what I said, friends. There's only
one Golden Ticket left in the entire world,
because right here in our own
community of Marble Falls, Arizona,
is lucky winner number four.
Now, the name soon to be heard around
the universe is Mr. Mike Teevee.
Hey, Mike, do you think we
might shut that thing off?
- No, are you crazy?
- He won't answer 'til the station break.
Mike, the country wants to hear
from you. The world is waiting...
Can't you shut up? I'm busy.
Boy, what a great show.
I serve all his TV dinners right here.
He's never even been to the table.
- You love to watch TV, Mike?
- You bet.
What about that Golden Ticket, Mike?
Hold it! I wanna catch this.
- You like the killings, huh?
- What do you think life's all about?
Mike, would you tell us...
Wait 'til I get a real one.
Colt 45.
Pop won't let me have
one yet, will you, Pop?
Not 'til you're twelve, son.
Four down, and one to go.
And somewhere out there, another lucky
person is moving closer and closer
to finding the last of the most
sought after prizes in history.
Though we cannot help but
envy him, whoever he is,
and we might be tempted
to be bitter in our losing,
we must remember there are
many more important things,
many more important things.
Offhand I can't think of what they are,
but I'm sure there must be something.
And now for tomorrow's weather and...
Why'd you wake me up, Grandpa?
Is something wrong?
Grandpa, that money was for tobacco.
I told you, Charlie, I've given it up.
Go on, open it.
One ticket left. Now
let's see some of that gold.
No, you do it. I can't.
Something tells me we're
gonna be lucky this time.
I've got a funny feeling inside.
Which end shall I open first?
That end. Just a tiny bit.
- Like this?
- Now a bit more.
- You finish it. I can't.
- No, Grandpa, you do it.
All right,
here goes.
You know...
I bet those Golden Tickets make
the chocolate taste terrible.
Lot 403.
I can personally guarantee,
ladies and gentlemen,
that this is the one and only, the
absolutely last case of Wonka Bars
left in the United Kingdom.
Shall we start the bidding at one thousand
pounds? Do I hear one thousand pounds?
Fifteen hundred pounds?
Two thousand?
I have two thousand five hundred here.
Four thousand pounds?
Forty-five hundred pounds!
Five thousand pou...
Your Majesty!
I'm sorry, Mrs. Curtis.
Doesn't seem to be anything
in his papers to give us a clue.
They kidnapped my husband twelve hours ago.
When are we going to hear from them?
What do they want?
Try to stay calm. They did it for ransom.
All we can do is wait to hear their demands.
I'll give them anything, anything they want!
All I want is to have Harold back!
Go ahead, we're listening.
What did they ask for?
Whatever it is, they can have it.
They want your case of Wonka Bars.
Mrs. Curtis, did you hear me?
It's your husband's life or
your case of Wonka Bars.
How long will they give me to think it over?
That's it, that's it!
It's all over!
The Wonka Contest is all over!
The fifth and final ticket has been found,
and we've got a live report coming in
directly now from Paraguay, South America.
Ladies and Gentlemen, it is finished.
The end has come.
The fifth and last Golden
Ticket has just been found,
right here in Paraguay.
The finder is lucky Alberto Minoleta,
the multimillionaire owner of gambling
casinos throughout South America.
Here is the most recent picture
of Alberto the happy finder.
Turn it off.
Well, that's that.
No more Golden Tickets.
A lot of rubbish, the whole thing.
Not to Charlie it wasn't.
A little boy's got to have something in this
world to hope for. What's he got to hope for now?
Who's going to tell him?
Let's not wake him.
He'll find out soon enough.
Yeah, let him sleep.
Let him have one last dream.
I've just decided to switch our
Friday schedule to Monday,
which means that the test we take each
Friday on what we learned during the week
will now take place on Monday
before we've learned it.
But since today is Tuesday,
it doesn't matter in the slightest.
Pencils ready.
Today we are going to learn about...
percentages.
And for an example, let's take
the recent unpleasantness.
Supposing that there were a thousand
Wonka Bars in the world,
and during the contest you each
opened a certain number of them.
That number is...
a percent. Everyone understand?
You, Madeline Durkin, how many
Wonka Bars did you open?
About a hundred.
There are ten hundreds in a thousand.
Therefore you opened ten percent.
You, Peter Goff, how many did you open?
A hundred and fifty.
That's ten percent half over again, which
makes fifteen percent. Charlie Bucket.
- How many did you open?
- Two.
That's easy. Two hundred
is twice one hundred...
Not two hundred.
Just two.
Two? What do you mean
you only opened two?
I don't care very much for chocolate.
Well I can't figure out just two,
so let's pretend you opened two hundred.
Now, if you opened two hundred Wonka Bars,
apart from being dreadfully sick,
you'd have used up twenty
percent of one thousand,
which is fifteen percent half
over again, ten percent...
Hi.
I'd like a bar of chocolate please.
Yeah, sure.
What kind?
A Slugworth Sizzler?
A Wonka Scrumdidilyumptious?
- Whichever's the biggest.
- Try a Wonka Scrumdidilyumptious.
Now that all the tickets have been found,
I don't have to hide them anymore.
Hey, hey, hey, take it easy.
You'll get a stomach ache
if you swallow it like that.
- Bye.
- Bye now.
I think I'll buy just one more,
for my Grandpa Joe.
Sure.
Why not try a regular Wonka Bar this time?
Fine.
- All right, all right, take it easy. One at a time.
- Did you hear the news?
That gambler from Paraguay
made up a phony ticket.
That means there's one Golden Ticket
still floating around somewhere.
Can you imagine the nerve of that guy,
trying to fool the whole world?
Aw, he really was a crook!
Well this means the contest goes on forever.
Hey, you've got it!
You've got the last Golden Ticket!
The kid's found the last Golden Ticket!
Stand back there.
Leave the boy alone!
Break it up.
Come on, Charlie! Hold on to that ticket!
Run for it, Charlie!
Run straight home,
and don't stop 'til you get there!
I congratulate you, little boy.
Well done.
You found the fifth Golden Ticket.
May I introduce myself?
Arthur Slugworth.
President of Slugworth
Chocolates, Incorporated.
Now listen carefully because I'm
going to make you very rich indeed.
Mr. Wonka is at this moment
working on a fantastic invention:
The Everlasting Gobstopper.
If he succeeds, he'll ruin me.
So all I want you to do is to get hold
of just one Everlasting Gobstopper,
and bring it to me so that I
can find the secret formula.
Your reward will be ten
thousand of these.
Think it over, will you?
A new house for your family,
and good food and comfort
for the rest of their lives.
And don't forget the name:
Everlasting Gobstopper.
Look, everyone, look, I've got it!
The fifth Golden Ticket is mine!
You're pulling our legs, Charlie!
There aren't any more Golden Tickets.
No, Grandpa, the last one was a fake.
It said so in the papers.
I found some money in the street, and I
bought a Wonka Bar, and the ticket was in it.
Look at it, Grandpa, see for yourself!
Read it, Joe, for heaven's sake!
"Greetings to you, the lucky
finder of this Golden Ticket,"
"from Mr. Willy Wonka. Present
this ticket at the factory gates"
"at ten o'clock in the morning of the first
day of October, and do not be late."
"You may bring with you one member
of your own family, but no one else."
"In your wildest dreams
you could not imagine"
"the marvellous surprises that await you!"
- Charlie, you've done it!
- I can't believe it.
Grandpa? It says I can take
somebody with me.
I wish you could go.
Charlie.
Ah, that's good, Charlie.
Now help me up.
Are you okay?
Oh yeah, I'm fine, Charlie.
Joe!
Watch it, Joe!
Look at me!
Up and about...
I haven't done this in twenty years.
Grandpa!
♪ I never thought my life could be ♪
♪ Anything but catastrophe ♪
♪ But suddenly I begin to see ♪
♪ A bit of good luck for me ♪
♪ 'Cause I've got a golden ticket ♪
♪ I've got a golden twinkle ♪
♪ In my eye ♪
♪ I never had a chance to shine ♪
♪ Never a happy song to sing ♪
♪ But suddenly half the world is mine ♪
♪ What an amazing thing ♪
♪ 'Cause I've got a golden ticket ♪
It's ours, Charlie!
♪ I've got a golden sun up in the sky ♪
Slippers, Charlie!
♪ I never thought I'd see the day
When I would face the world and say ♪
♪ "Good morning, and look at the sun" ♪
♪ I never thought that I would be
Slap in the lap of luxury ♪
♪ 'Cause I'd have said ♪
♪ "It couldn't be done" ♪
♪ But it can be done ♪
The cane, Charlie!
Here I go!
Watch my speed!
♪ I never dreamed that I would climb
Over the moon in ecstasy ♪
♪ But nevertheless it's that that I'm
Shortly about to be ♪
♪ 'Cause I've got a golden ticket ♪
♪ I've got a golden chance to make my way ♪
♪ And with a golden ticket it's a golden day ♪
Good morning! Look at the sun!
♪ 'Cause I'd have said
"It couldn't be done" ♪
♪ But it can be done ♪
♪ I never dreamed that I would climb
Over the moon in ecstasy ♪
♪ But nevertheless it's there that I'm
Shortly about to be ♪
♪ 'Cause I've got a golden ticket ♪
♪ I've got a golden ticket ♪
♪ I've got a golden chance to make my way ♪
♪ And with a golden ticket it's a golden day ♪
Stop! It says the first of
October. That's tomorrow!
Jumping Crocodiles, Charlie! We've got a lot to do.
Comb your hair, wash your face, polish your shoes...
- I'll take care of everything, Dad.
- We don't have too much time.
Grandpa... On the way home today,
I ran into Mr. Slugworth.
Hey, Mom, we're on TV!
Hi, everybody in Marble Falls!
Hi, Billy! Hi, Maggie! Hi, Fishface!
How do I look?
- You guys ready?
- Yeah, you're on.
Well, this is it folks. This is the big day,
the historic day on which Willy Wonka has promised to
open his gates and shower gifts on the five lucky winners.
From all over the globe, people have
gathered here waiting for the hour to strike,
waiting to catch a glimpse of that
legendary magician Mr. Willy Wonka.
Hi, friends. Sam Beauregarde here. The next time
you're in Miles City, Montana, don't forget to visit...
Cut it out, Dad. For heaven's
sake, this is my show!
Hi, Cornelia sweetie, I've still got it.
And how's this for a stretch?
I want to go in first before anybody else.
Anything you say, sweetheart.
Save some room for later,
Augustus liebling.
Grandpa? I don't believe it. We did it.
We're actually going in.
We're going to see the greatest of them all:
Mr. Willy Wonka!
Thank you. Thank you.
Welcome, my friends.
Welcome to my chocolate factory.
Would you come forward please?
Veruca first! Get back, you!
Come on, Veruca sweetheart!
That's Slugworth! That's the
one I've told you about!
Welcome. It's nice to have you here.
I'm so glad you could come.
This is going to be such an
exciting day. I hope you enjoy it.
I think you will.
And now would you please
show me your Golden Tickets?
I'm Veruca Salt.
My dear Veruca, what a pleasure.
And how pretty you look
in that lovely mink coat.
I've got three others at home.
And Mr. Salt, overjoyed to see you, sir.
Would you just step over there for a minute?
Augustus Gloop.
Augustus, my dear boy,
how good to see you,
and in such fine shape.
And this must be the radiant Mrs.
Gloop. Just over there, dear lady.
- Violet Beauregarde.
- Darling child, welcome to Wonka's.
What kind of gum you got here?
Charming, charming!
Sam Beauregarde here, Mr. Wonka.
My dear sir, what a genuine pleasure.
If ever you need anything in the automotive line,
just call on Sam B, phone number's on the card.
With Sam B, it's a guarantee.
- I'm Mike Teevee.
- Mike.
Wham! You're dead!
Wonderful to meet you, Mike.
And Mrs. Teevee, how do you do?
- What an adorable little boy you have.
- Thank you.
Charlie Bucket.
Well, well, Charlie Bucket, I read all about you in the papers.
I'm so happy for you. And who is this gentleman?
My grandfather, Grandpa Joe.
Delighted to meet you, sir.
Overjoyed, enraptured, entranced.
Are we ready? Yes! Good!
In we go!
Now. Hats, coats, galoshes, over here.
But hurry please, we have so
much time and so little to see.
Wait a minute! Strike that.
Reverse it. Thank you.
- When do I get my chocolate?
- First take off your coat, Violet.
Boy, what weird looking coat hangers.
Little surprises around every corner but
nothing dangerous. Don't be alarmed.
And as soon as your outer
vestments are in hand,
we'll begin.
Now.
Will the children kindly step up here?
Accidents? What kind of accidents?
I didn't know we had to
sign anything for this tour.
I can't see what it says in the bottom.
Violet? You first.
Sign here.
Hold it!
Lemme through here, you kids.
Violet, baby, don't you sign anything there.
What's this all about?
Standard form of contract.
Don't talk to me about contracts, Wonka.
I use 'em myself. They're strictly for suckers.
Yes, but you wouldn't begrudge
me a little protection. A drop.
I don't sign anything without my lawyer.
- My Veruca don't sign anything either.
- Then she don't go in.
I'm sorry, rules of the house.
- I want to go in. Don't you dare stop me.
- I'm only trying to help you, sweetheart.
Gimme that pen. You're
always making things difficult.
Nicely handled, Veruca. She's a
girl who knows where she's going.
Violet.
Wait a minute, what's all that
small print there at the bottom?
Oh, if you have any problems,
dial information, thank you for calling.
- Mike, Augustus.
- Violet.
Violet!
I assume there's an accident
indemnity clause.
Never between friends.
Saw this in a movie once. Guy
signed his wife's insurance policy.
- Then he bumped her off.
- Clever.
What about me, Grandpa?
Sign away, Charlie.
We got nothing to lose.
Let's go in. Come on!
Patience, patience, little dear.
Everything has to be in order.
Everyone's signed? Yes?
Good. On we go!
Ninety-nine...
forty-four...
one hundred percent pure.
Just through the other door please.
Uh, Wonka, there's some mistake here...
There is no other door.
There's no way out!
Well I know there's a door here someplace.
I don't like this, Wonka.
I don't like it at all!
Is this a trick or something, Wonka?
Help! Mr. Wonka, help!
I'm getting squashed! Save me!
Is it my soul that calls upon my name?
Let me out or I'll scream!
- Somebody's touching me.
- Now look here, Wonka...
Excuse me, question time will come at the end of
the session. We must press on. Come along...
Come along.
- Ah, here we are.
- Oh, don't be a darn fool, Wonka.
That's the way we came in.
It is? Are you sure?
We've just come through there.
Huh. How do you like that?
- There we are...
- What is this, Wonka?
Some kind of fun house?
Why, having fun?
I've had enough. I'm not going in there.
Come on, Violet, we're getting out of here.
Oh, you can't get out backwards.
You've gotta go forwards to go back.
Better press on.
- Hey, the room is getting smaller!
- No, it's not.
- He's getting bigger.
- He's at it again.
- Where's the chocolate?
- I doubt if there is any.
I doubt if any of us
will get out of here alive.
Oh, you should never, never doubt
what nobody is sure about.
You're not squeezing me
through that tiny door.
You're off your bleeding nut, Wonka.
No one can get through there.
My dear friends,
you are now about to enter the nerve centre
to the entire Wonka Factory.
Inside this room, all of my
dreams become realities.
And some of my realities
become dreams.
And almost everything you
will see is eatible. Edible.
I mean, you can eat almost everything.
Let me in, I'm starving!
Now, don't get overexcited!
Don't lose your head Augustus.
We wouldn't want anyone to lose that!
Yet.
Now, the combination...
This is a musical lock.
Rachmaninoff.
Ladies and gentlemen,
boys and girls...
The chocolate room.
Hold your breath.
Make a wish.
Count to three.
♪ Come with me ♪
♪ And you'll be ♪
♪ In a world of pure imagination ♪
♪ Take a look ♪
♪ And you'll see
Into your imagination ♪
♪ We'll begin ♪
♪ With a spin ♪
♪ Travelling in the world of my creation ♪
♪ What we'll see
Will defy ♪
♪ Explanation ♪
♪ If you want to view paradise ♪
♪ Simply look around and view it ♪
♪ Anything you want to, do it ♪
♪ Want to change the world ♪
♪ There's nothing to it ♪
Hurry up, Violet.
This way, Grandpa.
♪ There is no life I know ♪
♪ To compare with pure imagination ♪
♪ Living there
You'll be free ♪
♪ If you truly wish to be ♪
♪ If you want to view paradise ♪
♪ Simply look around and view it ♪
♪ Anything you want to, do it ♪
♪ Want to change the world ♪
♪ There's nothing ♪
♪ To it ♪
♪ There is no
Life I know ♪
♪ To compare with pure imagination ♪
♪ Living there ♪
♪ You'll be free ♪
♪ If you truly ♪
♪ Wish to be ♪
What a disgusting, dirty river.
It's industrial waste, that.
You've ruined your
watershed, Wonka. It's polluted.
It's chocolate.
That's chocolate?!?
That's chocolate.
A chocolate river.
That's the most fantastic
thing I've ever seen.
Ten thousand gallons an hour.
And look at my waterfall.
That's the most important thing.
It's mixing my chocolate.
It's actually churning my chocolate.
You know, no other factory in the
world mixes its chocolate by waterfall.
But it's the only way if
you want it just right...
Grandpa, look over there across the river!
They're little men!
Jumping crocodiles, Charlie!
Now we know who makes the chocolate.
I never saw anybody with
an orange face before.
Funny-looking people, aren't they, Wonka?
What are they doing there?
It must be creaming and sugaring time.
- Well they can't be real people.
- Well of course they're real people.
Stuff and nonsense.
No, Oompa Loompas.
From Loompaland.
Loompaland? There's no such place.
Excuse me, dear lady...
Mr. Wonka, I am a teacher of geography.
Oh, well then you know all about it
and what a terrible country it is.
Nothing but desolate wastes
and fierce beasts.
And the poor little Oompa Loompas
were so small and helpless,
they would get gobbled up right and left.
A Wangdoodle would eat ten of them
for breakfast and think nothing of it.
And so, I said:
"Come and live with me
in peace and safety,"
"away from all the Wangdoodles
and Hornswogglers"
"and Snozzwangers and
rotten Vermicious Knids."
Snozzwangers? Vermicious Knids?
What kind of rubbish is that?
I'm sorry, but all questions
must be submitted in writing.
And so, in the greatest of secrecy,
I transported the entire population of
Oompa Loompas to my factory here.
Hey, Daddy, I want an Oompa Loompa. I want
you to get me an Oompa Loompa right away.
All right, Veruca, all right. I'll get
you one before the day is out.
I want an Oompa Loompa now!
Can it, you nit!
Mmmmm... this stuff is terrific.
- Grandpa, look at Augustus.
- Don't worry, he can't drink it all.
Augustus, sweetheart,
save some room for later.
Oh, uh, Augustus, please, don't do that. My
chocolate must never be touched by human hands.
Please don't do that! Don't do that.
You're contaminating my entire river.
Please, I beg you, Augustus!
My chocolate!
Help!
My chocolate! My beautiful chocolate.
Don't just stand there. Do something!
Help. Police. Murder.
- Quick, Charlie. Here.
- Quick, Augustus, grab this!
What-what's happening to him?
- It looks like he's drowning.
- Dive in!
- Save him!
- Oh, it's too late.
- Too late?
- Oh, he's had it now,
- the suction's got him.
- Augustus, come back.
Where is he?
Watch the pipe.
How long is he going to stay down, Daddy?
- He can't swim.
- There's no better time to learn.
There's his coat going up the pipe.
Call a plumber.
He's stuck in the pipe
there, isn't he, Wonka?
It's his stomach that's done that.
- He's blocking all the chocolate.
- Well, what happens now?
Oh, the pressure'll get him out. Terrific
pressure is building up behind the blockage.
I wonder how long it's gonna
take him to push through.
The suspense is terrible.
I hope it'll last.
He'll never get out!
Yes, he will, Charlie. Watch.
Remember you once asked me
how a bullet comes out of a gun?
He's gone! He'll be made into
marshmallows in five seconds!
- Impossible, my dear lady, that's absurd! Unthinkable!
- Why?
Because that pipe doesn't go to the
marshmallow room. It goes to the fudge room.
You terrible man.
Take Mrs. Gloop straight to the
fudge room, but look sharp!
Or her little boy is liable to
get poured into the boiler.
You've boiled him up, I know it!
Nil desperandum, dear lady.
Across the desert lies the promised land.
Goodbye, Mrs. Gloop.
Adieu! Auf wiedersehen.
Gesundheit. Farewell.
♪ Oompa, Loompa, doompadee doo ♪
♪ I've got a perfect puzzle for you ♪
♪ Oompa, Loompa, doompadah dee ♪
♪ If you are wise you'll listen to me ♪
♪ What do you get
When you guzzle down sweets? ♪
♪ Eating as much as an elephant eats ♪
♪ What are you at getting terribly fat? ♪
♪ What do you think will come of that? ♪
♪ I don't like the look of it ♪
♪ Oompa, Loompa, doompadee dah ♪
♪ If you're not greedy
You will go far ♪
♪ You will live in happiness too ♪
♪ Like the Oompa Loompa doompadee do ♪
♪ Doompadee doo ♪
Hey, what kind of place you
running here anyhow, Wonka?
Madames et monsieurs, maintenant nous
allons faire un petit voyage par bateau.
What's he talking about?
Voulez-vous entrer le Wonkatania?
Wow, what a boat!
Ohhhh, looks good enough to eat.
That's quite a nice little canoe
you've got there, Wonka.
All I ask is a tall ship
and a star to sail her by.
All aboard, everybody.
Uh, ladies first, and that means Veruca.
If she's a lady, I'm a Vermicious Knid.
- You sure this thing'll float, eh, Wonka?
- With your buoyancy, sir, rest assured.
She's very pretty, but is she seaworthy?
Nothing to worry about, my dear lady.
I take good care of my guests.
Yeah, you took real good care of that
August kid over there, that's for sure.
Everybody aboard?
You're going to love this.
Just love it.
Hey, Daddy, I want a boat like this.
A beautiful paddle boat, that's what I want.
What she wants is a good kick in the pants.
I think I'm gonna be seasick.
- Here, try one of these.
- What are they?
Rainbow drops. Suck 'em and you
can spit in seven different colours.
Spitting's a dirty habit.
I know a worse one.
- What business you in, Salt?
- Nuts.
Hang on, where are we going?
I don't know, but I don't like the
looks of that tunnel up there.
Hey, Wonka, I want off!
Round the world and home again,
that's the sailor's way!
I don't like this ride, Daddy.
We're going too fast!
We're gonna sink, I know it!
- Why doesn't he stop the boat?
- Faster!
Hang on, darling! Just close
your eyes and hang on tight!
- What is this, a freak-out?
- Hey, this isn't funny, Wonka!
You can't possibly see
where you're going, Wonka!
You're right. I can't.
Boy, what a great series this would make.
- This is kind of strange...
- Yeah, strange, Charlie, but it's fun! Ha ha!
How much to get off the boat, Wonka?
I think I'm gonna be sick.
I can take a joke, but this has gone too far.
Tell that little guy to
turn us around, Wonka!
Now I am gonna be sick!
♪ There's no earthly way of knowing ♪
- He's singing.
- ♪ Which direction we are going ♪
♪ There's no knowing where we're rowing ♪
♪ Or which way the river's flowing ♪
♪ Is it raining? ♪
♪ Is it snowing? ♪
♪ Is a hurricane a-blowing? ♪
Not a speck of light is showing,
so the danger must be growing.
Are the fires of hell a-glowing?
Is the grisly reaper mowing?
Yes!
The danger must be growing,
for the rowers keep on rowing.
And they're certainly not showing
any signs that they are slowing!
Oh, make him stop, Daddy!
- Wonka, this has gone far enough!
- Quite right, sir!
Stop the boat!
- We're there
- Where?
Here.
A small step for mankind,
but a giant step for us.
All ashore!
Let me off this crate!
- Now why don't they show stuff like that on TV?
- I don't know.
What a nightmare.
Daddy, I do not want a boat like this.
Dairy cream.
Whipped cream.
- Coffee cream.
- Vanilla cream.
Hair cream?
Meine Herrschaften, schenken
Sie mir ihre Aufmerksamkeit.
That's not French.
Sie kommen jetzt in den interessantesten
und gleichzeitig geheimsten
raum meiner fabrik.
I can't take much more of this.
Meine Dammen und Herren,
Der Inventing Room.
Now remember, no messing about.
No touching, no tasting, no telling.
No telling what?
You see, all of my most secret inventions
are cooking and simmering in here.
Old Slugworth would give his false
teeth to get inside for just five minutes,
so don't touch a thing!
Inventing room?
It looks more like a Turkish bath to me.
Even if Slugworth did get in here,
he couldn't find anything.
- You got a garbage strike going on here, Wonka?
- Who does your cleaning up?
Shouldn't you be wearing rubber gloves?
You'll have the health inspectors
after you, you know that, don't you?
Invention, my dear friends,
is ninety-three percent perspiration,
six percent electricity,
four percent evaporation,
and two percent butterscotch ripple.
That's a hundred and five percent!
Any good?
Yes!
Excuse me...
Time is a precious thing. Never waste it.
- He's absolutely bonkers.
- And that's not bad.
♪ In springtime
The only pretty ring time ♪
♪ Birds sing, hey ding
A-ding a-ding ♪
♪ Sweet lovers love the spring ♪
♪ The spring ♪
I told you not to, silly boy.
Your teeth!
Boy, that's great stuff.
That's exploding candy for your enemies.
Great idea, isn't it?
Not ready yet, though, still too weak.
Needs more gelignite.
What's that for?
Gives it a little kick.
Wonka?
Butterscotch... butter gin...
you've got something going on
inside of here?
Candy is dandy, but liquor is quicker.
What's the matter?
Too hot, Mr. Wonka?
Too cold. Far too cold.
That's gourmet cooking for you.
No! Don't. Please.
Forgive me, but no one
must look under there.
This is the most secret machine
in my entire factory.
- This is the one that's really going to sizzle old Slugworth.
- What's it do?
- Would you like to see?
- Yeah.
But what's it do?
Can't you see?
It makes Everlasting Gobstoppers.
Did you say "Everlasting Gobstoppers"?
That's right. For children with very little
pocket money. You can suck 'em forever.
I want an Everlasting Gobstopper.
- Me too!
- And me!
Fantastic invention.
Revolutionize the industry.
You can suck 'em and suck 'em and suck 'em,
and they'll never get any smaller. Never.
At least I don't think they do.
- A few more tests.
- How do you make 'em?
I'm a trifle deaf in this ear.
Speak a little louder next time.
- Who wants an Everlasting Gobstopper?
- Me! I do!
I can only give them to you if you solemnly
swear to keep them for yourselves
and never show them to another living
soul as long as you all shall live.
Agreed?
Agreed.
Good. One for you, and one
for you, and one for you.
Eh, what about Charlie?
And one for Charlie.
Hey, she's got two. I want another one!
- Stop squawking, you twit!
- Everybody has had one,
and one is enough for anybody.
Now come along.
Now over here, if you'll follow me,
I have something rather
special to show you.
Well, it's special, all right.
I only hope my Veruca doesn't want one.
What a contraption.
Isn't she scrumptious?
She's my revolutionary,
non-pollutionary mechanical wonder.
Now. Button, button, who's
got the button?
It's over there.
- Here?
- Yeah.
What you are witnessing, dear friends,
is the most enormous
miracle of the machine age:
the creation of a confectionery giant!
- Finito!
- That's all?
That's all!? Don't you know what this is?
- By gum, it's gum!
- Wrong!
It's the most amazing, fabulous,
sensational gum in the whole world.
What's so fab about it?
- This little piece of gum is a three course dinner.
- Bull.
- No, roast beef, but I haven't got it quite right yet.
- I don't care
Oh, I wouldn't do that.
I really wouldn't.
So long as it's gum, then that's for me.
Violet, now don't you do anything stupid.
What's it taste like?
Madness! It's tomato soup!
It's hot and creamy I can actually feel it
running down my throat!
- It's delicious!
- Stop, don't...
Why doesn't she listen to Mr. Wonka?
Because, Charlie, she's a nitwit.
This sure is great soup.
Hey, second course is coming up!
Roast beef and a baked potato! Mmmm.
With sour cream?
- What's for dessert, baby?
- Dessert? Here it comes.
Blueberry pie and cream! It's the most
marvellous blueberry pie that I've ever tasted!
- Holy Toledo, what's happening to your face?
- Cool it, Dad!
Lemme finish.
Yeah, but your face is turning blue!
- Violet, you're turning violet, Violet!
- What are you talking about?
I told you I hadn't got it quite right yet.
You can say that again.
Look what it's done to my kid!
It always goes wrong when we
come to the dessert. Always.
Violet, what are you doing now?!?
- You're blowing up!
- I feel funny.
- I'm not surprised.
- What's happening?
- You're blowing up like a balloon!
- Like a blueberry.
- Somebody do something! Call a doctor!
- Stick her with a pin.
- She'll pop!
- It happens every time!
- They all become blueberries.
- You've really done it this time, haven't you, Wonka?
I'll break you for this.
Oh, well, I'll get it right in the end.
Help! Help!
We've got to let the air out of her, quick!
There's no air in there.
- That's juice.
- Juice?!
Would you roll the young lady down
to the juicing room at once, please?
- What for?
- For squeezing.
She has to be squeezed immediately
before she explodes.
- Explodes?!
- It's a fairly simple operation.
♪ Oompa Loompa doompadee doo ♪
♪ I've got another puzzle for you ♪
♪ Oompa Loompa doompadah dee ♪
♪ If you are wise you'll listen to me ♪
♪ Gum chewing's fine when it's once in a while ♪
♪ It stops you from smoking
And brightens your smile ♪
♪ But it's repulsive, revolting and wrong ♪
♪ Chewing and chewing ♪
♪ All day long ♪
♪ The way that a cow does ♪
♪ Oompa Loompa doompadee dah ♪
♪ Given good manners you will go far ♪
♪ You will live in happiness too ♪
♪ Like the Oompa Loompa doompadee do ♪
I'll get even with you for this,
Wonka, if it's the last thing I ever do!
I got a blueberry for a daughter...
Where is fancy bred?
In the heart, or in the head?
Shall we roll on?
Thank you.
Well, well, well... two naughty,
nasty little children gone.
Three good, sweet little children left.
Hurry, please, long way to go yet.
Wait a minute. Must show you this.
Lickable wallpaper for nursery walls.
Lick an orange, it tastes like an orange. Lick a
pineapple, it tastes like a pineapple. Go ahead, try it.
Mmm, I got a plum.
Grandpa, this banana's
fantastic! It tastes so real.
Try some more. The strawberries
taste like strawberries.
The snozzberries taste like snozzberries!
Snozzberries? Who ever
heard of a snozzberry?
We are the music-makers,
and we are the dreamers of dreams.
Come along, come along.
Something very unusual in here.
Bubbles, bubbles everywhere,
but not a drop to drink...
Yet.
What's it making, Mr. Wonka?
Fizzy Lifting Drinks. They fill you with gas,
and the gas is so terrifically lifting
that it lifts you right off the
ground like a balloon.
Oh, isn't it high! Gosh!
But I daren't sell it yet.
It's still too powerful.
Come on, let us try some! Please?
No, no, no. Absolutely not. There'd be
children floating around all over the place.
Come along now. Don't hang about.
You're going to be wild about this next room.
Let's take a drink,
Charlie. Nobody's watching.
A small one won't hurt us.
Mmmm, not bad.
Well?
Nothing's happening.
You're right, Charlie. I
can't understand why...
Oh, oh, oh, I feel terribly strange...
- What do we do now, Grandpa?
- I don't know, Charlie, but aaaah! Oh! Oh!
- We're in big trouble! Mr. Wonka isn't gonna like this.
- We can't stay up here all day!
- You're right, Charlie, but...
- I'm gonna try and get down.
All right, Charlie, but please...
be very careful.
Hey, it's fun, Grandpa! It works!
Come on in, the air's fine!
Oh, I don't know, Charlie.
- I haven't been swimming in twenty years, I...
- Come on, give me your hand.
I don't think I ought to...
Oh. Oh! This is great!
Hey, try this, Grandpa! Whee!
All right, Charlie, wait for me! Wheeeeee!
- I'm a shooting star!
- I'm a rocket!
Grandpa, this is really great.
Look, I'm a bird!
I feel light as a feather.
Look down, Charlie.
We're really high now.
Watch this, Grandpa.
Wonderful, Charlie.
- Try it, Grandpa.
- Oh, I don't know, I...
Come on, Grandpa.
All right.
Hey, you did it, Grandpa.
I think I hit an air pocket.
You can fly to the moon this way.
Let's just fly south for the winter.
Why not?
I'm a bird!
I'm a plane!
I'm...
going too high!
Hey, Grandpa, I can't get down!
Help!
Grandpa, the fan!
Stay away from it, Charlie.
It'll chop us to bits!
We're in trouble, Charlie. I can't stop!
It's pulling me in!
I can't stop! I can't stop!
- What do we do?
- Grab hold of something, quick!
There's nothing to grab on to! Help!
We're gonna get killed!
Help! Help!
Mr. Wonka, please! Turn off the fan!
I'm going down!
Quick, Charlie, burp, burp! If you don't
get down you'll be chopped into ribbons!
- I can't! Help!
- You've gotta burp, Charlie.
It's the only way.
'Atta boy, burp again.
'Atta boy, come on.
Ahhhh, that's wonderful, Charlie.
Grab onto me, Charlie.
We're gonna be all right now.
Good boy.
From now on, we keep
our feet on the ground.
Come on, let's catch up to the others!
I know what you're thinking.
They can't be doing what they're doing.
But they are. They have to.
I haven't met the Oompa Loompa
yet who could do it.
These are the geese that lay the golden eggs.
As you can see, they're larger than
ordinary geese. As a matter of fact,
they're quadruple size geese,
which produce octuple size eggs
They're laying overtime right now for Easter.
But Easter's over!
They don't know that.
I'm trying to get ahead for next year.
What happens if they drop
one of those eggs, Wonka?
An omelet fit for a king, sir.
Are they chocolate eggs?
Golden chocolate eggs.
That's a great delicacy.
But I wouldn't get too close.
The geese are very temperamental.
That's why we have the Eggdicator.
Eggdawhat?
The Eggdicator. The Eggdicator can
tell the difference between a good egg
and a bad egg.
If it's a good egg, it's shined up
and shipped out all over the world.
But if it's a bad egg...
down the chute.
It's an educated Eggdicator.
It's a lot of nonsense.
♪ A little nonsense now and then ♪
♪ Is relished by the wisest men ♪
Hey, Daddy, I want a golden goose.
Here we go again.
All right, sweetheart, all right.
Daddy'll get you a golden goose
as soon as we get home.
No, I want one of those!
Wonka, how much do you
want for the golden goose?
- They're not for sale.
- Name your price.
She can't have one.
Who says I can't?
- The man with the funny hat.
- I want one!
I want a golden goose!
Gooses.
Geeses.
I want my geese to lay gold eggs for Easter.
- It will, sweetheart.
- At least a hundred a day.
- Anything you say.
- And by the way...
I want a feast.
You ate before you came to the factory.
♪ I want a bean feast ♪
Huh, one of those.
♪ Cream buns and doughnuts
And fruitcake with no nuts ♪
- ♪ So good you could go nuts ♪
- You can have all those things when you get home.
No, now!
I want a ball.
♪ I want a party ♪
♪ Pink macaroons
And a billion balloons ♪
♪ And performing baboons
And... ♪
♪ Give it to me ♪
Now!
♪ I want the world ♪
♪ I want the whole world ♪
♪ I want to lock it all up in my pocket
It's my bar of chocolate ♪
♪ Give it to me now ♪
♪ I want today ♪
♪ I want tomorrow ♪
♪ I want to wear 'em like braids in my hair ♪
♪ And I don't want to share 'em ♪
♪ I want a party with roomfuls of laughter ♪
♪ Ten thousand tons of ice cream ♪
♪ And if I don't get the things I am after ♪
♪ I'm going to scream ♪
♪ I want the works ♪
♪ I want the whole works ♪
♪ Presents and prizes
And sweets and surprises ♪
♪ Of all shapes and sizes and now! ♪
♪ Don't care how
I want it now ♪
She was a bad egg.
Where's she gone?
Where all the other bad eggs go:
down the garbage chute.
The garbage chute.
Where does it lead to?
To the furnace.
The furnace.
- She'll be sizzled like a sausage.
- Well not necessarily.
- She could be stuck just inside the tube.
- Inside the...
Hold on!
Veruca, sweetheart.
Daddy's coming!
There's gonna be a lot of garbage today.
Well, Mr. Salt finally got what he wanted.
- What's that?
- Veruca went first.
Mr. Wonka, they won't really be
burned in the furnace, will they?
Well, I think that furnace
is lit only every other day,
so they have a good sporting
chance, haven't they?
♪ Oompa Loompa doompadee doo ♪
♪ I've got another puzzle for you ♪
♪ Oompa Loompa doompadee dee ♪
♪ If you are wise you'll listen to me ♪
♪ Who do you blame when your kid is a brat ♪
♪ Pampered and spoiled like a Siamese cat ♪
♪ Blaming the kids is a lie and a shame ♪
♪ You know exactly ♪
♪ Who's to blame ♪
♪ The mother and the father ♪
♪ Oompa Loompa doompadee dah ♪
♪ If you're not spoiled you will go far ♪
♪ You will live in happiness too ♪
♪ Like the Oompa Loompa doompadee do ♪
I don't understand it. The children
are disappearing like rabbits.
Well, we still have each other.
Shall we press on?
Mr. Wonka, can't we sit down for a minute?
- The pace is killing me.
- My dear lady, transportation has already been arranged.
Behold the Wonkamobile.
A thing of beauty is a joy forever.
Places, please, the dance is about to begin.
Better grab a seat, they're going fast.
Mr. Wonka, what's that
they're filling it up with?
Oh, ginger ale, ginger pop,
ginger beer, beer bubbles,
bubble-ade, bubble cola, double cola,
double bubble burp-a-cola,
and all the crazy carbonated
stuff that tickles your nose.
Few people realize what tremendous
power there is in one of those things
Sorry I asked.
You think Slugworth would
pay extra to know about this?
Just keep your eyes open and your mouth shut.
Everybody set?
Is this gonna go fast, Grandpa?
It should, Charlie. It's got more
gas in it than a politician.
Now hold on tight. I'm gonna really open
her up this time and see what she can do.
Swifter than eagles...
stronger than lions...
It's getting in my eye!
Oh, it's even in my shoes!
I'm soaked! It'll never come out!
It's sticking to my gun.
My dress, my hair, my face!
Ohhhhhh...
I'm sending you the cleaning bill,
Mr. Wonka!
I'm dry cleaned!
Hey, Grandpa,
what was that we just went through?
Hsawaknow.
- Is that Japanese?
- No, that's "Wonkawash" spelled backwards.
That's it, ladies and gentlemen.
The journey is over.
Finest bath I've had in twenty years.
Let's do it again, Mr. Wonka.
- You mean that's as far as it goes?
- Couldn't we have walked?
If the Good Lord had intended us to walk,
he wouldn't have invented roller skates.
Now would you all please put these on.
We have to be very careful.
There's dangerous stuff inside.
Wonkavision,
my very latest and greatest invention.
- It's television.
- Uh, it's Wonkavision.
Now I suppose you all know
how ordinary television works.
Sure, I do. You photograph something,
and then the photograph is split
up into millions of tiny pieces,
and they go whizzing through the air down to your TV set
where they're all put together again in the right order.
You should open your mouth
a little wider when you speak.
So I said to myself,
"If they can do it with a photograph,"
"why can't I do it with a bar of chocolate?"
I shall now send this chocolate bar from
one end of the room to the other.
It has to be big because whenever
you transmit something by television,
it always ends up smaller
on the other end.
Goggles on, please.
Lights, camera,
action!
You can remove your goggles.
Where's the chocolate?
It's flying over our
heads in a million pieces.
Now watch the screen.
Here it comes.
There it is.
Take it.
How can you take it? It's just a picture.
All right, you take it.
It's real.
Taste it. It's delicious.
It's just gotten smaller, that's all.
It's perfect.
It's unbelievable.
It's a miracle.
It's a TV dinner.
It's Wonkavision.
It could change the world.
Mr. Wonka, can you send other things?
- Not just chocolate, I mean.
- Anything you like.
What about... people?
People?
I don't really know.
I suppose I could.
Yes, I'm sure I could.
I'm pretty sure I could.
But it might have some messy results.
Look at me. I'm gonna be the first person
in the world to be sent by television!
Mike, get away from that thing!
Stop, don't, come back...
Lights, camera, action!
Mike! Where are you?
He's up there, in a million pieces!
- Mike! Are you there?
- No good shouting here. Watch the screen.
Mike? Why's he taking so long?
Million pieces take a
long time to put together.
- Oh, where are they?
- There's definitely something coming through.
- Is it Mike?
- Well it's hard to tell, but I...
Our little group is getting
smaller by the minute.
Look at me, everybody. I'm the first person
in the world to be sent by television.
Wow, what a wild trip that was.
It's the greatest thing
that's ever happened to me.
Am I coming in clear? Hey, Mom, I said,
"Am I coming in clear?"
Great. He's completely unharmed.
You call that unharmed?
Wow, that was something
Can I do it again?
No, there'll be nothing left.
Don't worry about a thing, Mom. I feel fine.
I'm famous. I'm a TV star.
Wait 'til the kids back home hear about this.
Nobody's gonna hear about this.
Where are you taking me?
I don't want to go in there!
Be quiet.
Well...
Well, fortunately small boys are
extremely springy and elastic,
so I think we'll put him in my special
taffy-pulling machine. That should do the trick.
To the taffy-pulling room.
You'll find the boy in his mother's purse.
But be extremely careful.
Oh, what's he saying?
No, no, I won't hold you responsible.
And now, my dearest lady,
it's time to say goodbye.
No, no, don't speak.
For some moments in life there
are no words. Run along now.
Adieu, adieu,
parting is such sweet sorrow.
♪ Oompa Loompa doompadee doo ♪
♪ I've got another puzzle for you ♪
♪ Oompa Loompa doompadah dee ♪
♪ If you are wise you'll listen to me ♪
♪ What do you get from a glut of TV ♪
♪ A pain in the neck and an IQ of three ♪
♪ Why don't you try simply reading a book ♪
♪ Or could you just not bear to look ♪
- ♪ You'll get no ♪
♪ You'll get no commercials ♪
♪ Oompa Loompa doompadee dah ♪
♪ If you're not greedy you will go far ♪
♪ You will live in happiness too ♪
♪ Like the ♪
♪ Oompa ♪
♪ Oompa Loompa doompadee do ♪
So much to do, so much to do,
invoices and bills, letters...
I must answer that note from the queen.
Mr. Wonka, what's gonna
happen to the other kids?
Augustus, Veruca?
My dear boy,
I promise you they'll be quite all right.
When they leave here, they'll be completely
restored to their normal, terrible old selves.
But maybe they'll be a
little bit wiser for the wear.
Anyway, don't worry about them.
Eh, what do we do now, Mr. Wonka?
Oh, yes, well, I hope you enjoyed yourselves.
Excuse me for not showing you out.
Straight up the stairs.
You'll find the way.
I'm terribly busy. Whole day wasted.
Goodbye to you both. Goodbye.
What happened?
Did we do something wrong?
I don't know, Charlie.
But I'm gonna find out.
- Mr. Wonka?
- I am extraordinarily busy, sir.
I just wanted to ask about the chocolate.
The lifetime supply of
chocolate, for Charlie.
When does he get it?
- He doesn't.
- Why not?
Because he broke the rules.
What rules? We didn't see any rules,
did we, Charlie?
Wrong, sir, wrong!
Under Section Thirty-Seven B
of the contract signed by him,
it states quite clearly that all offers
shall become null and void if,
and you can read it for yourself
in this photostatic copy:
"I, the undersigned,
shall forfeit all rights,
privileges, and licenses
herein and herein contained,
etcetera, etcetera...
fax mentis,
incendium gloria culpam,
etcetera, etcetera...
memobis quelitor della cassum!"
It's all there, black and white,
clear as crystal!
You stole Fizzy Lifting Drinks.
You bumped into the ceiling which
now has to be washed and sterilized,
so you get nothing!
You lose!
Good day, sir!
You're a crook!
You're a cheat and a swindler!
That's what you are.
How can you do a thing like this?
Build up a little boy's hopes and then
smash all his dreams to pieces.
You're an inhuman monster!
I said "good day"!
Come on, Charlie, let's get out of here.
I'll get even with him if it's
the last thing I ever do.
If Slugworth wants a
Gobstopper, he'll get one.
Mr. Wonka?
So shines a good deed
in a weary world.
Charlie,
my boy...
You won!
You did it! You did it!
I knew you would. I just knew you would.
Oh, Charlie, forgive me for putting
you through this. Please, forgive me.
Come in, Mr. Wilkinson
Charlie, meet Mr. Wilkinson.
- Pleasure.
- Slugworth!
No, no, that's not Slugworth.
He works for me.
- For you?
- I had to test you, Charlie.
And you passed the test.
You won!
- Won what?
- The jackpot, my dear sir,
- the grand and glorious jackpot.
- The chocolate?
The chocolate, yes, the chocolate,
but that's just the beginning.
We have to get on, we have to get on.
We have so much time, and so little to do.
Strike that. Reverse it.
This way please.
We'll take the Wonkavator.
Step in, Charlie. Grandpa Joe, sir.
- This is the Great Glass Wonkavator.
- It's an elevator.
It's a Wonkavator. An elevator
can only go up and down,
but the Wonkavator can go sideways and
slantways and longways and backways...
And frontways?
And squareways and frontways and
any other ways that you can think of.
It can take you to any room in the whole factory, just
by pressing one of these buttons. Any of these buttons.
Just press a button and zing!
You're off.
And up until now I've pressed them all...
except one.
This one.
Go ahead, Charlie.
Me?
There it goes.
Hold on tight.
I'm not exactly sure what's going to happen.
Faster, faster... If we don't pick up
enough speed, we'll never get through.
Get through what?
- You mean we're going...?
- Up and out!
But this roof is made of glass
It'll shatter into a thousand pieces.
- We'll be cut to ribbons!
- Probably.
Hold on, everybody.
Here it comes.
- You did it, Mr. Wonka, congratulations!
- Get up. Take a look.
Grandpa, our town looks
so pretty from up here.
Yeah, look over here, Charlie.
I think I see our house.
Wow!
It really looks beautiful.
There is my school, Grandpa.
How did you like the
chocolate factory, Charlie?
I think it's the most wonderful
place in the whole world.
I'm very pleased to hear you say that,
because I'm giving it to you.
That's all right, isn't it?
- You're giving Charlie the...?
- I can't go on forever,
and I don't really want to try.
So, who can I trust to run the factory when I leave
and take care of the Oompa Loompas for me?
Not a grown-up.
A grown-up would want to do everything
his own way, not mine.
That's why I decided a long time ago
I had to find a child.
A very honest,
loving child,
to whom I can tell all my most
precious candy making secrets.
- And that's why you sent out the Golden Tickets.
- That's right.
So the factory's yours, Charlie.
You can move in immediately.
- And me?
- Absolutely.
- What happens to the rest of...
- The whole family.
I want you to bring them all.
But Charlie...
don't forget what happened to the man who
suddenly got everything he always wanted.
What happened?
He lived happily ever after.