??[Group Singing Hymn ]
?? [ Continues ]
?? [ Singing Fades ]
We must see
this beautiful train.
That's it. Okay.
Oh, yeah. That's really great.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, now as I said before,
you're under no obligation to me.
You can, ifyou want to,
give me a tiny, little twinkle.
Yeah.
That is... Iovely.
Right. A bit closer.
Now, don'tyou worry.
You'll be all right.
[ Chuckles ]
Hair's just a little bit--
That's it.
And you've got an eyelash
on your nose.
We don't want it. Supposed to be
on your eye, not on your snitch.
[ Chuckles ] Ah. See? You have a lovely smile
when you smile, haven'tyou?
Right. Okay. Nowyou keep
that lovely, gorgeous smile.
That's lovely.
[ Sniffs ]
I think that'll do for the time being.
Well done, Sara.
That's the easy bit.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Shouting, Indistinct ]
[Shouting Fades Away]
They make a noise,
don't they?
Least they can play
out around here.
Suppose so.
- What is it?
- Is that a suit?
It came as a combination.
They go together?
Well, ifyou think they do, they do,
and ifyou think they don't, they don't.
It's nice.
Twenty-one in August.
- She is.
- I used to worrymeselfsick when she playedout.
- She survived it, though, didn't she?
- All things considering.
- She's back on the streets now.
- I beg your pardon?
- Well, she is, isn't she?
- I don't half miss her.
I know.
How long is it
since we've seen her?
Two and a halfyears.
[ Sighs ]
- We could always ask her over.
- I'd like to.
For her birthday?
It's only a couple of months away.
- [ Chuckles ]
- What now?
"Hey, Roxanne,
whatyou doing foryour 2 1st?"
"I'm going over to my auntie
and uncle's house for my birthday treat."
- [ Chuckling]
- It was only a suggestion.
She's probably
doing her own thing.
I suppose we'd have to
invite Cynthia as well.
There's no show without Punch.
- I'm sure she'd like to see the place.
- Oh, I'm sure she would.
- She can't help it.
- Can't she?
It's about time
you showed it off.
- I mean, you've done a lovelyjob.
- I think so.
[ Exhales Deeply]
I really must get down
to see her.
- Youspeak to her on the phone, don'tyou?
- It's not the same though, is it?
She's your sister.
I'm reallyproud
ofthat portrait.
Bet that's the last time
she ever smiled.
[ Clacking ]
[Tennis Game On TV]
I don't know
what's got into you lately.
- You complaining?
- No.
Well, shut up then.
Sit here on me own foryears on end.
Can't getyou to stop in at all.
- Nowyou never go out.
- Leave it out.
You've been sitting there for a month
with a face like a slapped horse.
Well, what's there
to smile about?
Thought he might have phoned
at the weekend.
- Who?
- Who doyou think?
- Ain't heardfrom him forages.
- He's busy, ain't he?
-We're all busy.
-He's got his weddings and that. It's the summer.
Out of sight, out of mind.
Well, ifyou're that bothered, why don'tyou
ring him yourself? He's your brother.
I'm not running up
me phone bill.
He knows where I am
ifhewants me.
He'd have had us up there to see it by now,
I expect, ifit weren't for her.
Toffy-nosed cow.
What's he want
with six bedrooms anyway?
[Tennis Game On TV Continues ]
What's all your mates
doing tonight then?
I don't know.
I ain't asked 'em.
You wanna get yourself a bloke.
That's what you wanna do.
I told you
I don't wanna get anything.
I'm quite happy here,
thankyou very much.
When I was your age, I could've
had the pick ofthe crop.
Well, whydidn'tyou?
Because I lost my poor mother,
that's why.
- Oh, here we go.
- I was stuck at home...
from the age of 1 0 looking after Maurice
and your granddad.
Yeah, we know.
Then I got saddled with you.
That was my downfall, darling.
- I didn't ask to be born.
- No, and I never asked to haveyou neither.
Well, you should have thought about that
beforeyou dropped your knickers!
- With... orwithout?
- I thinkwithout.
- Without? Okay.
- Yeah.
[Sniffs ]
What about this one?
Betterwith orwithout?
- I think this time it's with.
- With? All right.
We'll pop this one in then.
- I hearyou're a really good runner.
- Yeah. Cross-country.
- Haveyou won anything?
- Not yet.
- I've onlyjust started.
- Okay. Now look up again.
Now, this is gonna blur a bit, but just
tell me what you can read, okay?
"H, L, A...
- C, T."
- Right.
And I can't read anymore.
Okay. That's good.
Very good.
I'm gonna do your other eye now.
- You offthen?
- Yeah.
- Got any plans for the weekend?
- I've got to go to my mum's house
and sort through her things.
- Oh, okay. Hope it goes all right.
- Yeah.
- Well, it's gotta be done.
- Okay then.
- I'll seeyou on Monday.
- Yeah. Have a nice weekend.
- Cheers.
- Ooh. Enjoy the christening.
- I'll try.
- Okay. Bye.
- Bye.
[ Chattering In OtherRoom ]
- What areyou talking about?
- I got 1 0 minutes.
Listen. We've got to
sort this out while we're here.
Face it, Leroy.
I t's you one here i n this massive house.
Thank you. We have got two children.
You understand?
- And we could have more. We wanna have more.
- What?
Listen, right? You can't stay here
on your own. It's not fair, is it?
I mean, we can sell the house, can't we?
Sell the house and split the money.
- You could split this whole house in two.
- We could sell the house.
[Woman ] We couldsplit it into two flats
andit'dstill be biggerthan--
We couldsplit it into two, possiblyinto three.
Well, there you are then.
Sort your tie out for you,
if I m ight.
- Looks just a little bit skewered there.
- Oh, skewered again.
There. That's lovely.
Can I have the paper?
- Yep. Okay.
- Oh, right.
You two ladies look gorgeous.
That's splendid.
Put your hands together.
Thereyou are. Really nice.
Okay. Here we go.
Right down there.
Right. Andhere we go.
Okayand--
- Do we say, "Cheese," Maurice?
- Well,you can ifyou like.
Butyou can.
You can say, "Cheese. "
You can say whateveryou like,
butjust give me a little bit-- Perfect!
- Aaah!
- Ah, yeah. Very sweet.
- [ Grunti ng ]
- Okay. That's lovely.
- So it tookyou 1 5 years, eh?
- Yes.
- Did they give you a prize?
- No.
- Not even a stethoscope? Lovely.
- [ Chuckles ]
- [ Cooing ]
- Ooh. The baby.
- Yeah. That's really lovely.
- I 'm so glad he's got his eyes open.
Yeah. That's it. Yeah. That's it.
And give him a look down. Lovely!
Are you gonna
see that flea collar?
- You gonna see that?
- Don't worry about that.
You come out then. Come out.
- Hang on. That's it.
- Youjust come out the way.
Uh, pop out now.
Come out. And here we go.
I think I got the comb in there
that time.
- Lovely. Very good.
- Ohhh.
- Does he look good?
- He does look good.
- Oh, good. Yeah, yeah.
- So do you. Thankyou very much,Jane.
That's lovely.
- I t's for my auntie.
- Oh, what, fond ofyou, is she?
- No. She's in I ndia.
- Oh, right.
- Time I got married, isn't it?
- Oh, I see.
"Pick a bride" time,
is it?
I told you,
I don't want flashy.
- And... Iovely!
- [ Giggling ]
I never thought
I'd have any.
- Fertility treatment.
- [ Giggles ]
It's a miracle.
Don't do that with your nose.
Now stop it. Put it there.
Hello. Look at that lovelycat.
Look overthere.
- Look. It's lovely!
- Look at that cat.
- Oh, I see. Then scratch it first.
- No!
Go on. That's it.
That's it. Lovely!
[ Giggling ]
I feel so silly.
Aha! Lovely! That's it!
Ah! Thankyou very much.
[ Whirring ]
- What do you thinkyou're doing?
- Sorry.
Didn't you hear me?
- Well, hi.
- What? Mind, out ofthe way.
- Want a drink?
- What?
Ifl want a drink,
I'll get it myself, thankyou.
[Huffs ]
Sincewhen was Hoovering
a spectator sport?
- Can I have a glass too, please?
- Sorry. I thoughtyou didn't want one.
I've changed my mind.
I'm having milk. Not in a wine glass.
Give me a highball.
You don't put milk in a wine glass.
- Thereyou go.
- Thankyou.
- That'll doyou good.
- Meaning?
Nothing.
- [ Sighs ]
- Hada goodday?
Scintillating.
Supposeyou'll be
starving as usual.
I'm a little bit peckish, yeah.
- Doyou want me to do something?
- Likewhat?
- Anything you like.
- No, I bloodywell wouldn't.
- Fair enough.
- Well, all right then.
There's the fridge.
There's the freezer.
There's the hop.
There's the recipe books.
Helpyourself.
And don't make a mess.
[ Sighs ]
Unless you fancy a take-away.
[ Sighs, Crying ]
- You're not gonna smile, areyou?
- No.
Okay. It's a free world.
Now,you're under no obligation,
butyou can, ifyou want to...
give me a lovely big smile.
Thankyou.
Oh, go on! Come on!
Lovely.
[ Chuckling ] You're under no obligation to me,
butyou can smile ifyou like.
Yes! Thankyou.
- Did you sm i le, Mother?
- No.
That's it. To me.
Now look at each other.
- [ Giggl i ng ]
- That's lovely.
- Don't.
- Go on. Look up. Keep your face up.
- Wait, wait, wait. Wait, please.
- That's lovely.
- Yeah. You were closingyour eyes.
- Wait a minute.
[ Exhales Deeply ]
Don't forget to burp it properly.
Give it a drop of gripe water.
We used to pour it down Roxanne
by the gallon.
She farted like a trouper.
Runs in the family.
Would madame care to
test the temperature?
I'm sure it'll be fine.
Thanks.
- Been bad, has it?
- It eased offat lunchtime.
- Managed a couple of crackers.
- [ Chuckles ]
It's unpredictable, isn't it?
No, it's not unpredictable.
- You've drawn the short straw, mate.
- [ Sighs ] You're telling me.
I wish it was unpredictable.
- What areyou gonna have foryour tea?
- Tonight I'm eating fancy.
- What?
- A steak.
You're not having any steak
in this house.
- Don't worry about me.
- You'll be keeling overwith a heart attack.
Don't we still have
something a bit lighter?
There's a chicken Kiev
in the freezer.
- Be a bit cold, wouldn't it?
- [ Huffs ]
Anyway, I'm on a diet.
You're disgusting.
Okay. That's verygood.
And we can see the ring perfectly.
All right now.
Sir, ifyoujust bringyour chin up--
Yeah.Just like that.
That's brilliant.
- All right. Great.
- Wait. Sorry. Listen.
- U m, take your glasses off.
- I don't want to take my glasses off.
- [ Whispers ] Take them off!.
- [ Sighs ]
- Doesn't matter-- keep 'em on, take 'em off.
- No, it's all right.
- It looks betterwithout them.
- It's not what I look like, okay?
- Come on.Just-- here.
- Right. Okay. And to the--
Can you-- One moment, please.
Can you take the cross out, please?
- Mm?
- Take the cross out. The gift. Take it out.
- I just think it looks awful.
- It doesn't look awful.
It looks awful 'cause it's not gold.
I told you to buy gold.
- Okay. Right.
- [ Conversing In Foreign Language ]
Okay. And to me again.
Right. That's lovely.
Now, ifyou want to look happy
orsad, I don't mind.
That's it! [ Chuckles ]
Ah, look at me! And lovely!
[ Key Rattles In Lock ]
Hel lo. My name's
Hortense Cumberbatch.
I got your letter. Hi.
All right. Tuesday.
[ Voices Murmuring In Distance ]
- [Phone Rings ]
- [ Woman ] Hello.
- Hortense. Hello.Jenny Ford. Nice to meet you.
- Oh, hi.
- Come this way. How are you? All right?
- Fine. Thankyou.
Good. I'm sorry
about this prison cell.
We've been going on about it foryears,
but thereyou go.
Have a seat.
Makeyourselfat home.
[DoorShuts ]
Now, before we go any further, have you
got any I.D.-- passport, driving license?
- Oh, yeah.
- I have to get used to all this red tape.
- Would you like a Rollo?
- No, thankyou.
- Yousure?
- Yeah.
Thereyou go.
Hmm. Have a shufty.
- That's great, Hortense, then.
- Thankyou.
- You on your lunch break?
- Yeah, an extended one.
- Well, haveyou hadanylunch?
- No, not yet.
No? Me neither.
So what do you do?
- I'm an optometrist.
- Oh, really?
Oh, God. That's one ofthose things
you keep putting off and putting off, isn't it?
When I got to the station,
overthe Guardian crossword...
but I'm going like this,
so I think the time has come.
I'll have to pop in.
You can give me a test.
- Where doyou live?
- Kilburn.
- Right, right. In a flat?
- Yes.
- Youshare?
- No, I live on my own.
All right.
I lived on my own...
foraboutsixyears.
- Before I was married. It's all right.
- [ Chuckles ]
Right, Hortense. Let's talk a little bit
about you, shall we?
Now, obviously,you've been
giving a great deal ofthought to things...
and you've come to a decision,
which is good.
But for me,
the question is "why now?"
I just feel that it's
the right time, that's all.
- Right, right. You thinking
about getting married?
- No.
- Doyou have children?
- You thinking about having children?
- No.
That's fair enough.
Areyou sharing this with your parents?
Do they know thatyou're here today?
How do they feel about it?
They're both dead actually.
All right.
Uh, Mum died
two months ago now.
Oh, that is recent.
I'm-- I'm sorry to hear that.
- Was it sudden?
- Yeah.
Perhaps that's what has
madeyou start on this.
I don't know.
It's possible.
Well, I'm not trying to
replace her.
She's irreplaceable.
They both are.
No. Of course, of course.
- And whenyou were growing up,
was it a happy environment?
- Yes, very.
Oh, good, good.
And did you, um--
Were you able to discuss
the fact that you'd been--
No. It was never
really an issue.
Right, right.
So you've onlyjust found out?
Oh, no. They told me
when I was little.
Oh, good, good. And doyou remember
howyou felt about that?
Well, it's not exactly
something you forget, is it?
No. No. [ Chuckles ]
I'm sure it isn't.
So how did you feel?
Well, we all just got on with it as a family,
doyou know what I mean?
Yeah. Perhaps you
should have discussed it.
My parents loved me,
and that was all that matters.
Isn't it?
Yeah. Yeah.
So, now that we've gotyou here,
what areyour expectations?
Basically,
I just want to know.
Yeah, yeah.
Of courseyou do.
Let me share something
with you, Hortense.
Somewhere out there,
and we don't know where...
is your birth mother.
Now, she's probably married--
perhaps not.
She mayhave other children.
She might be dead.
She may even be in Australia
orsomewhere. Wejust don't know.
But what we do know is that
at the time she gave you up for adoption...
she was under the impression that she
would probably never see you again.
Now, as I know
you're verywell aware...
the law has changed since then
and you are now legally entitled
to seekyour birth mother out.
But the snag is,
she may not want to seeyou.
So I don't wantyou to
raiseyour hopes too high at this stage.
- Sure.
- Okay.
Have a look at this.
What is it?
It's allaboutyou.
I tell you what.
- I'll leave it withyou
and I'll be back in a few minutes.
- Yeah.
- Can I get you anything?
- No. Uh, thankyou.
[Door Opens, Closes ]
[ Creaking ]
How you doing?
All right?
Thankyou.
[ Sniffles ]
"Cynthia Rose Purley."
That's her.
Cynthia Rose.
It's a nice name,
isn't it?
- That's her signature.
- Mm-hmm.
Does it feel strange?
"Elizabeth."
That's my middle name.
They must've kept it.
Well, that would be
your birth name, you see?
"Elizabeth Purley."
[ Exhales Deeply]
[ Sniffles ] Listen, is there anyway
I could get a copy ofthese?
No. Those are the originals
and they'reyours to keep.
That's your right
under the 1975Act.
I've made copies upstairs.
Can I pop those in here foryou?
So...
what we need to do now is...
- [ Exhales Deeply]
-you go away and have a think.
And when the time's right,
and not before--
you know, it's very much
in your own time--
come back to me,
ifthat's whatyou want...
and we'll
get the ball rolling.
Now, it can be
a very long-winded process.
And there's no two ways
about it...
it's a very traumatic journey
we're embarking on.
And there may be other people's
feelings to consider too.
So I'll wait
to hear from you, okay?
Now, y-you could decide to trace your
birth mother byyourself ifyou want to...
but I-- I wouldn't advise it.
We're a professional service
and we know how to handle these things.
So I thinkyou should
take advantage of us.
- Hello.
- Oh, you're back. Hello.
- I think I found a mistake.
- I'm sorry, Hortense. I can't stop. I'm late now.
- Look. It says she's white.
- Sorry?
"Mother: White."
Well, it's perfectly feasible
thatyour motherwas white, isn't it?
Look, I'm sorry, Hortense. Really,
I've got to go. I'm on an emergency case.
Yes, but could this
be a mistake?
I very much doubt it.
Look. Give me a ring in the morning
and we'll have a talk then.
- Okay. I'm sorry.
- [Hurried Footsteps Departing]
Look at that.
- Legs like a teenager.
- Do you have to?
- You'd like a pair like that.
- What for?
I'm known for my legs.
Ifyou've got it, flaunt it.
- You going out?
- Of course I ain't.
[DoorKnockerKnocking]
- Who's that?
- Well, I don't know.
Ifit's what's-her-name,
you could ask her to come in.
I don't even know
who it is yet.
- [ Breathing Heavily]
- Whatyou doing here?
Just come to seeya.
Well, you can't come in.
My mum's here.
- Who is it?
- I'm going out.
Hello.
- You all right, sweetheart?
- Would you get inside?
Nothing's changed much.
- No.
- Ain'tyour mum been around, looking afteryou?
She came around Sunday,
after mass.
Didn't take long
to mess it up again.
She laying off of me
a bit now though.
- Well, Ishould thinkso too, atyourage.
- Yeah.
She should have a word
with my mum.
I bet she misses you though.
Fuckin'... better off
without it altogether, I'll tell ya.
Yeah, I know whatyou mean.
You and me, mate.
We're better offwithout 'em.
Look. I'm sorry about--
You know.
Soyou should be.
Don't get all serious
on me, Paul.
- No, no. I ain't.
- Yes, you are, you fool.
I just missed you.
How much?
- A lot.
-Just a lot?
No. Y-Yeah.
Well, I might have
missed you a bit.
Ya know, I've been
going out of me head.
So was I.
[ Breathing Heavily]
Just so's you know, I ain't staying the night,
not every time I come round.
And I wantyou to stop before.
I was just speaking my mind, all right?
- [ Softly] Yeah.
- Now give us a snog.
[ Breathing Heavily]
[ Sniffles ]
- Hello. Good afternoon.
What can I do foryou today?
- Hello.
Right. That's fine.
Is that, uh, to post or collect?
- Collect, please.
- Collect. Thanks very much.
That's ?6, please, madam.
Okay.
- I saw her, you know.
- Did ya?
Yeah.
8:00 in the morning--
[ Indistinct ]
She's just, like,
"You got a boyfriend yet, Dionne?"
Nearly everyone
who went to the funeral...
reckoned they'd seen her and she'd
given them some kind of sign.
[Jamaican Accent ] "Me seeyour mother
twoyears before she dead.
And she hold onto me arm
and look in me eye as ifshe did know."
[Laughing]
I mean, ifshe knew,
I wish she'd told us.
You're gettin' better though.
It's a nice day.
Yeah.
I don't know...
why I can't contain it all.
It's too soon.
[ Sighs ]
There's nothing rational
about grief.
Maybeyou cry foryourself.
Been out much?
Nah. I can't.
Some days
I'm completelyvulnerable.
I can feel everything.
Other days I'm numb.
- Ifyou wanna come out with me--
- No.
- I've got stuffto sort out.
- What?
Life.
- Look. Ifthere's anything I can do--
- No. Thanks.
I'll be all right.
- Haveyou heard from Bernard?
- Nah.
Yes! He sent a sympathy card.
- Mm?
- Which I thought was a very nice thing to do.
[Laughing]
I did something really bad.
Oh, no. I don't think
I can deal with no confession.
- Cleanse my soul.
- Mm-mmm!
- I didthe do.
- Do it.
- Did the deed with a complete stranger.
- Didit.
- No! Who?
- [ Giggles ] I don't know who.
- Well, what did he look like?
- Don't know.
- He was in advertising.
- Oh, Lord.
[Laughs ]
- Did you use a condom?
- Yes.
- Didyou use two?
- One on top ofthe other?
- One after the other.
- Oh, God!
- [ Laughing ]
- Do you despair of me?
- No.
- Yes, you do.
- I don't.
- Did you have a good time?
- Yeah.
- That's all that matters then, isn't it?
[ Giggles ]
I liked my mum as a person,
but I didn't know her.
I wish I'd known her.
- She loved you.
- Yeah, I know, but that's not in debate, is it?
My mum,
she resents me.
She kept you.
She fed you.
She clothed you.
She didn't giveyou away.
[ Sighs ]
- She could have.
- I wish she had.
No, you don't.
[ Exhales Deeply]
The thing is,
they're so secretive.
It's that back-home thing.
You know.
"Come out.
Big people are talking."
That sort ofvibe.
Soyou don't pursue things,
becauseyou're brought up not to.
Just let 'em
get on with it.
What I seem to do
is think about things...
I wish I could have
asked her.
Like what?
I don't know.
There's stuff
I wish I knew.
- There's stuffl wish I didn't know.
- No.
Ifyou knewyou had a limited amount
oftime, you'd sort it out.
You'd ask
your mum questions...
regardless ofwhether
she gotvexed.
Like, I don't know, what happened between
her and your dad, for example.
No. She didn't make
no effort for me...
so why should
I be interested in her?
And where's my dad anyway?
I don't wanna hear
her and Norbert havin' it off.
I don't want her to know
who I'm havin' it offwith...
and I don't want her
to see me drunk.
Don't want her to know
nothing about me.
Maybe that's becauseyou're frightened
that when you look at her...
you can seeyourself
in 20 years time.
- Please.
- We choose our parents.
How doyou mean?
We choose the parents in this life
that can teach us something...
so that when we go into the next life,
we get it right.
Zzzzoop!
[ Chuckles ]
Well, sometimes
it don't work, does it?
I'm gonna pop out
for a couple ofhours.
- What time will you be back?
- 4:30.
- Okay. Have fun.
- Thanks.
Sorry to interrupt.
Doyou thinkyou can fit these things in?
- Right.
- I'm a bit low.
- I'll give 'em a ring.
- Thanks.
"Seventeen-I."
[Breathes Deeply]
[Lock Clicks ]
- Hello.
- Bloody hell.
- Whatyou doing here?
- Thought I'd come and seeya.
Where's Monica?
She's at home, I think.
[ Chuckles ]
Gonna let me in then?
Yeah, of course.
- Doyou want a cup oftea?
- Yes, please.
- You all right then?
- Smashing.
Haveyou been working
down this way?
Yeah.
On the back ofTower Bridge.
IfI'd known you was coming,
I'd have warmed up the seat.
It's warm enough
I should think.
[DoorOpensAnd Closes ]
Does Monica know
you've come round here?
No. I didn't know
I was coming meself.
- She's okay then?
- Yeah, she's fine.
She's busy
with the house.
What doing? I thought it was supposed
to be a new house, you said.
- Stenciling.
- What, drawing?
No.
Stencils on the wall.
Decorating. You must've
seen it in magazines.
It's very effective.
Roxanne not in then?
She's got some bloke in tow.
- Has she?
- Shifty-looking bleeder.
- Walks like a crab.
- Hmm.
- Your tea's there.
- Ta.
- Do you want a sandwich?
- No, thanks.
- So she's all right?
- I only see her first thing in the morning.
She comes in, grunts,
then buggers offto work.
- You should be glad she's got a fella.
- I am glad, Maurice.
I want her to be happy.
But I'd like her to bring him 'round,
see who she's knocking about with.
-Just give her a bit oftime.
- You used to bring your girlfriends home--
front ofthe telly,
laugh, drink.
You didn't mind
me sittin' there, did you?
- [ Chuckles ]
- What's hername? Neverstopped talking.
- Tina.
And the other one,
wouldn't open her mouth.
- Maxine.
- That's it.
Dad liked her, didn't he?
Nice thighs.
So how's work then?
[Sips ]
Still at the same place?
Yeah.
I gotta get her something for her birthday.
It's her 2 1 st, Maurice.
- August the 7th.
- I don't know what she wants...
apart from me under a bus.
- That's silly talk.
- Me head in the oven.
- When you gonna come and see us then?
- Eh?
You know,
a bit of a get-together.
Come on Roxanne's birthday.
We'll have some champagne.
- What about Monica?
- [ Chuckles ]
- She'll be there.
- No. Won'tshe mind?
No. It was her idea actually.
Oh.
- How doyou fancya barbecue?
- Ifyou like.
Anyway, it's about time
you saw the house.
- Thought you was never gonna ask.
- I'm asking you now.
- Ya been there nearly a 1 2-month.
- Tell Roxanne.
She might not wanna come.
She'llsayno
just to spite me.
Yeah. Well,
I demand her presence.
- Tell her.
- What if she wants to bring him?
- Has he gotta job, this bloke?
- Scaffolding, she says.
Ahhh.
It's verywell-paid.
- Is it?
- Yep.
Twenty-one.
I can't believe it, Maurice.
I was carryin' her
when I was 21, wasn't I?
- You was good with nappies.
- [ Scoffs ]
Those safety pins though.
Neverstabbed herthough,
didyou, darlin'?
- Stabbed meself a couple of times.
- Seventeen, weren't you?
I was.
[ Sighs ]
Place is still standin',
isn't it?
Not for much longer.
You should see Dad's room.
- What's up with it?
- It's like the Niagara Falls up there.
- What, it's got a leak?
- Yeah.
Onlywhen it's rainin'.
I'll have a look.
Nice to have a man
about the place.
Wish I'd known
you was comin'.
It's dry at the moment.
The whole lot's
gonna come down.
Does look a bit dodgy,
I'll have to admit.
- You up-to-date on the rent?
- Course I am.
Give him a ring. Get him to do something
about it. It's his responsibility.
Don't be daft, Maurice.
He don't give a toss, does he?
I'll get someone to look at it.
I'll pay.
Look at all thisjunk.
Whatyou gonna do with it?
Give us a cuddle, Maurice.
[ Crying ]
Please, sweetheart!
Why have you left it
so bloody long?
Well, you know,
it-it's work and all that.
There's nothing the matter
with your dialing finger.
- You can ring me.
- You're always too busy, ain'tya?
- Look, um-- See here. Sityourself down.
- [ Continues Crying ]
You're the only one
I've got, Maurice.
You love me, don'tya?
Hold me tight,
Maurice, please.
Sweetheart!
My little brother.
Look atyou.
It's a good life forya.
[ Kissing ]
When areyou
gonna shave, eh?
Slapyour arse.
Why don'tyou
chuck it all out, eh?
I mean, look at it.
Some ofit hasn't been touched
since Mum died.
Can you use anything, Maurice,
in your new house?
Fill a space?
No, thanks.
Thought I might
move in here.
Front view.
See the world go by.
[ Sniffles ]
Remember this?
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah.
Now it's no use
to you, is it?
I don't think so.
You ain't gonna
make me an auntie now, are ya?
Sweetheart?
Listen, Cynth--
I-- b-bet--
better be going.
You'll let me know about the barbecue
then, will you, sweetheart?
Yeah, of course I will. Tell her if she
can't make it, I'll give her a clump.
- Not before I do.
- Hang on.
- Shall I say hello to Monica foryou?
- Ifyou like, sweetheart.
- Thereyou go.
- Thanks, darlin'.
- Seeya.
- Ta-ta.
What was your mum like
when your dad died?
- What doyou mean?
- How did she cope?
I don't know.
Tooyoung to remember.
She just got on with it, I suppose,
like everybody else.
Didyou have to
look after Craig?
What, you mean like your big sister
looked afteryou?
No, I did not.
My dad never said a word about my mum
after she died.
- That's men foryou.
- I hated him for it.
He must have been
in real pain.
Maybe just couldn't share it.
I didn't know what I felt.
I still don't.
Cynthia's antics
couldn't have helped him much.
- Doyou miss Craig?
- Whywould I miss Craig?
- He's your brother.
- He's in Saudi Arabia, isn't he?
Yeah.
Well, I don't
exactly miss him.
Why?
Doyou miss Cynthia?
Doyou think Roxanne's serious
about this scaffolder bloke?
Well, she's only known him
for five minutes.
Mind you, I was married
at her age, wasn't I?
- Yeah.
- I wonder if she knows.
What, about us?
- What's there to know about us?
- You know what I mean.
How would she know about that--
unless you've told her.
- I haven't told her.
- I hope Cynthia doesn't know either.
She doesn't.
That's all right then.
No, I meant if she knows about Cynthia--
You know, before she was born.
I don't know.
I mean, she's got a half-brother
or a half-sister, knockin' about somewhere.
- She's got a right to know.
- That's up to Cynthia.
You'dneversayanything,
wouldyou?
- Of course not.
- Good.
Anyway, she must have
told her.
She nevertold her
who herfather was.
None of us knew
who he was.
I wonder
if she ever misses him.
- Who?
- Roxanne.
- You can't miss what you've never had.
- Can't you?
[ Sighs ]
I was gonna kill him.
- Poor Cynthia.
- Saint Cynthia.
- She tried her best.
- Did she?
Yeah.
Yeah, she did.
She gave me a lot oflove.
- What shall I tell him ifhe phones then?
- Who?
- Maurice.
- I don't know. Tell him whatyou want.
- Areyou gonna bring your bloke or not?
- No, I ain't.
- Haveyou asked him?
- No!
- [ Ringing ]
- Hello?
- That will be him now.
- Let me talk to him.
- Shut it!
Well, there ain't
no one there.
- One ofthem perverts.
- Sweetheart?
Oh, will you stop going on
about this fucking barbecue?
You're going to see him now, ain'tyou?
You can ask him.
I don't even know
ifl want him to go...
and it ain't
for ages anyway.
Seeyou later.
- [ Minister] "I, Zoe,
- [ Woman ] "I, Zoe...
- "take you, Darren,
- "take you, Darren...
- "to be my husband,
- "to be my husband...
- "to have and to hold...
- "from this dayforward,
- "from this dayforward...
- "for better or for worse,
- for better or for worse--"
for richer--"
[ Continues, Indistinct ]
[ Minister Continuing ]
Darren and Zoe have given their consent...
and made their marriage vows
to each other.
They have declared their marriage
byjoining ofhands...
and by the giving
and receiving ofrings.
I therefore proclaim...
that they are
husband and wife.
[ Shutter Cl icks ]
Ai n't you seei n' hi m
tonight then?
I 'm havin' an early night.
- Keep me company?
- I've got a hangover.
You should stop in
more often.
You are lookin' afteryourselfwith him,
ain'tyou, sweetheart?
- Whatyou mean?
- You know, taking care.
I don't want to askyou
nothing personal, darling...
but areyou taking the pill?
That is personal.
- Why don'tyou bring him 'round?
- Leave it out.
I'd like to meet him.
I wouldn't know him...
- ifhe stood up in me soup.
- Don't holdyourbreath.
You don't want to leave it up to him,
darling. Men are all the same.
- Mum!
- I hope he uses a what's-name--
- Condoms.
- Mind your own business.
They can leak.
You want to be careful.
You're jealous, ain't ya?
Where is he tonight anyway?
- I don't know.
- Most likely out giving somebody else one.
That's how I got caught with you--
runnin' out ofthe pill.
- You could have a coil fitted.
- Change the record!
Dr. Mulholland,
make an appointment.
- You'd suit the sponge.
- Keep yourvoice down!
I got a Dutch cap floatin' around somewhere
upstairs. You could have that.
Run it under the tap.
A bit oftalcum powder. Whereyou goin'?
I don't have to listen to this!
Sweetheart!
Roxanne!
Sweetheart, darlin',
I'm onlytrying to helpyou.
- Leave me alone.
- I'm your mother.
- Get out of my room!
- It don't matter ifyou have a little baby.
- I'll look after it.
- I ain't gettin' pregnant!
- I'll give up me job.
- It's nothing to do with you!
Yes, it bloody is!
I'm not havin' you droppin' it at my door!
-Jesus Christ!
- I'm sorry, darling! I didn't mean--
Shut up!
You make me sick, you stupid bitch!
- [DoorSlams ]
- [ Crying ]
[Phone Ringing]
[Ringing Continues ]
- Hello?
- I'm sorry to trouble you...
but I'm trying to locate...
a Cynthia Purley.
Yes?
Is that Cynthia Purley?
- Yes.
- Cynthia Rose Purley?
- Of76 Quilter Street?
Yes. What is it
you want, darlin'?
Hello?
Did you want Roxanne?
She's gone out.
- No.
- She ain't in any trouble, is she?
- No, it's about Elizabeth.
- Elizabeth? Elizabeth who?
Elizabeth Purley.
Oh, oh, she's dead.
- No, she isn't.
- She is, darlin'. I should know.
I should know.
Look, sweetheart, she's me mother.
She went in 1 961.
No, I mean
baby Elizabeth Purley.
Baby Eliz--
Who is this?
She was born
on the 23rd ofJuly, 1 968.
At-- Sorry about this.
At-- Yeah.
At the Haven--
Wells Grange Avenue, Sutton, Surrey.
Look, I'm sorry.
I know this must be a shock toyou.
[ Throwing Up ]
[ Sighs ]
[WaterRunning]
[Phone Ringing]
[Ringing Continues ]
[Ringing Stops ]
L-Listen, darling,
what is it you want?
- I'm really sorry.
- You mustn't come 'round here, sweetheart.
- I didn't want to upset you.
- You mustn't do that.
And you mustn't
phone neither.
I just needed to know.
[ Crying ] Yes, butyou can't
come 'round here.
No one knows aboutyou, see?
- Right.
- Promise me you won't come 'round. Promise me.
Look, I've gotyour address. Ifl wanted
to come 'round, I'd have done it already.
[ Continues Crying ]
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
I'm a little bit upset.
- Promise meyou won't come 'round.
- All right, I promise.
Thankyou.
Um--
C-Can I meetyou somewhere?
No, I shouldn't
think so, darlin'.
See, I've got lots of, um--
I've got lots of questions I want to askyou.
Yeah, well, I gotta go now.
Please.
What's your name anyway, eh?
- Hortense.
- Hortense?
Yeah.
- Hortense what?
- Cumberbatch.
"Clumberbunch"?
That's a funny name, isn't it?
Yeah, I suppose it is.
You own a phone?
Yeah. Uh, doyou want
to take my number down?
Oh, I don't think
I've got a pencil.
I'll wait.
I got one.
Uh, it's 01 71...
21 9--
Sorry-- 61 9 4840.
- Yeah, ta-ta.
- [Hangs Up Phone ]
[ Sighs ]
[Phone Ringing]
[Ringing Continues ]
Hello? Hello?
Do you want to
meet me or not then?
- Oh, hello.
- Yes or no. It's up to you.
Oh, yeah.
Of course I want to meet you.
Well, then--
Are you sure about this?
- I mean, ifyou're not sure--
- Where doyou want to meet me?
Well, where would
you like to meet?
I don't know, anywhere.
- Not here though.
- No, of course not.
Uh, what about
outside Holborn tube station?
Holborn.
When?
What areyou doing
this Saturday coming?
Nothing. I'm never
bloody doing anything.
- Saturday then.
- What time?
- 7:30?
- Half past 7:00.
Now, listen, you mustn't phone me
here again. Doyou understand me?
Otherwise I won't
come and meetya.
Now, I'll seeyou on Saturday.
Hello?
[ Sighs ]
Don't even know
whatyou look like.
- [ Sighs ]
- [Hangs Up Phone ]
- Hello, sweetheart.
- What's for tea?
- Gotyou a bit of steak. Little treat forya.
- What for?
- Ain't you havin' none?
- I'll just fry meself an egg.
- Do you want a beer?
- We ain't got none.
- I got you some.
- Oh, didyou?
- You going out?
- No, I'm stayin' in.
I'm gonna have
a few early nights...
I've decided.
- Excuse me.
- What is it, sweetheart?
Are you Cynthia?
- Yeah. How'd you know?
- Hello. I'm Hortense.
Whatyou talking about?
Hortense Cumberbatch.
I spoke toyou on the telephone.
- Well, that was you?
- Yeah.
Oh, no.
No, sweetheart.
No, darlin'. You been ringin'
the wrong person.
- Cynthia Purley.
- Where'd you get my name from anyway?
It's on my birth certificate.
What you talkin' about,
your birth certificate?
- It can't be.
- It's got your name and your address on it.
There.
No, that's all wrong, darlin'. They've made
a mistake down in the offices.
You want to get down there,
get that sorted.
- That's someone havin' a joke.
- I don't think so.
Let me have a look at that.
I'm ever so sorry, sweetheart.
[ Crying ] That must be a bit
of a disappointment foryou.
Look, I really think
you ought to see these documents.
Why, what is it?
Why don't we, uh, go somewhere
and have a sit-down?
No, I think
I better be going, darlin'.
Look, you've come
all this way. Please.
Let's-- Let's go
and have a cup oftea or something.
There's places down there.
Come on.
I hopeyou find your mum,
sweetheart.
You keep lookin'.
Go on.
No, thanks.
I don't smoke.
Nor should ya.
My daughter smokes
like a chimney.
- You got a daughter?
- [ Inhales ] Yeah.
I ain't never
been in here before.
They shouldn't go raisin'
your hopes like that. It ain't fair.
Is this your signature?
This is stupid.
I don't understand it.
I mean, I can't be
your mother, can I?
- Why not?
- Well, look at me.
- What?
- Listen. I don't mean nothing by it, darlin'...
but I ain't never
been with a black man in my life.
No disrespect nor nothing.
I'd have remembered,
wouldn't I?
Oh, bloody hell.
[ Crying ]
Oh,Jesus Christ Almighty!
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
I'm so ashamed.
You shouldn't be ashamed.
I can't look atyou.
I didn't know, sweetheart.
Honest, I didn't know.
- What didn'tyou know?
- I didn't knowyou was black.
See, I--
I thought they got
the dates all wrong.
All this time, I thoughtyou was born six--
six weeks premature...
butyou weren't.
You wasn't.
Who was he?
You don't want
to know that, darlin'.
I do.
Listen, I want to be
honest with you...
but I can't tell you that,
sweetheart.
I'm sorry.
Look atya.
I expect that I'm a bit
of a disappointment toyou, ain't I?
No.
- You don't have to say that, darlin'.
- I know.
You've been better offwithout me.
I'll tell you that much.
I doneyou a good turn.
Your tea's getting cold.
What's your mum like then?
Does she mind you
looking for me?
- My mum died recently.
- [ Gasps ] Oh, I'm sorry.
What aboutyour dad?
He's dead and all.
Areyou married?
No, no, um,
I ain't, uh--
I ain't married, sweetheart.
- Are you?
- No.
I'll bet you got
a boyfriend though, ain't ya?
- No, not at the moment.
- [ Gasps ] A nice-looking girl likeyou.
Haveyou got a boyfriend?
I give 'em all
a wide berth.
They got me into enough
trouble in the past, ain't they?
[ Laughing ]
You got a job, haveya?
- Yeah.
- That's good.
- What doin'?
- I'm an optometrist.
- Eh?
- I test eyes.
Optician?
Are you?
Well...
there's a turn-up.
- What do you do?
- [ Sniffles ]
I work in a factory.
- Doyou like it?
- Well, it pays the rent.
How aboutyour daughter?
She works for the council.
- You got any sisters?
- No, two brothers.
Are they, um, adopted?
No.
What they do?
One's a computer salesman,
and the other one's got his own garage.
I'll betyour mum
was proud ofyou, wasn't she?
- Yeah, she was.
- Yeah, course she was.
I'd have been proud.
Why didn'tyou
want to see me?
Well, 'cause nobody
knows aboutyou, sweetheart.
I don't want to upset
my daughter, do I?
I mean when I was born.
Well, I couldn't.
I was too upset, see?
Theywanted me to look atya.
Theywanted me to hold ya.
But I couldn't. I just couldn't.
I didn't know
ifl was comin' or goin'.
I was only
a little girl meself-- 1 6.
I didn't have no choice.
Ifl had seen you,
I'd havewanted to keepyou.
You do believe me,
don'tyou, sweetheart?
I don't blameyou, darlin'.
You onlyjust found out?
No. I've known
since I was seven.
What, your mum and dad
told you, did they?
Yeah, they did.
They sound like nice people.
Yeah.
My mum told me on the plane
on ourway back from Barbados.
Little girl.
Was you upset?
I just looked out
at the clouds.
Um--
Haven'tyou ever
thought about me?
Yeah, course I have.
But it ain't no good pining
overwhatyou ain't got, is it?
But didn'tyou think
I'd look foryou?
No, I didn't, as it happens.
Wish you hadn't
bothered now, don'tya?
No.
I'm glad.
I don't want to disrupt
yourfamily or anything.
I just had to seeyou.
I had to know
whoyou were.
Listen.
I want to wish you all the best,
sweetheart, whateveryou do.
And I'll be thinkin' ofya.
Quiet, ain'tya?
What's up?
- Areyou goin' out?
- Yeah, in a bit.
You feelin' all right?
Oh, there's nothing the matterwith me,
sweetheart. Nothing at all.
- Didyoufindanything today?
- Frozen chicken.
- Where, in the road?
- No, in a bin.
Still cold.
Some dirty magazines.
- Did you bring 'em home?
- No!
So, I suppose
there are worse jobs.
Gotta laugh,
ain'tya, sweetheart?
Or elseyou'd cry.
[ Ringing ]
- Hello?
- Is that Hortense?
- Speaking.
- It's Cynthia.
Hello.
- I didn't thinkyou'd be in.
- I am.
Well, I just, um,
wanted to ring up and say...
how nice it was
to meetyou yesterday.
- That's all.
- Thankyou.
Been thinkin' aboutyou
all day.
I've been thinkin' aboutyou.
Yeah, well, um...
I just wanted to say that.
Thankyou.
Don't know what to say now.
Daft, ain't it?
Got home all right, did ya?
Yeah, thankyou.
What haveyou
been doing today?
Oh,just out the back
sunnin' meself.
- Whatyou been doin'?
-Just chillin' out really.
- Yeah, hot, ain't it?
- Yeah.
Well, that's all
I wanted to say, sweetheart.
Ta-ta then.
I'd really like
to seeyou again.
- Would ya?
- Yeah.
Oh, that'd be nice.
- Doyou like Italian food?
- Yeah, I'll eat anything, me.
Chinese, kebabs, the lot.
- What?
- Nothing.
It's great.
- [Maurice ]And--
- [ShutterClicks ]
- Okay. Otherside, please.
- [Winding Film ]
- And--
- [Shutter Clicks ]
Lovely. So ifyou bring your face
'round this way, please, I want--
Can you shut the door,
please?
Yeah, sure.
Sorry.
So, who did
your original photograph?
My dad actually. But my solicitor said
that theyweren't good enough.
- Doyou have a police photographer?
- No.
Just gonna come in
a bit closer.
So I hope you don't suffer
from claustrophobia.
- No, I don't actually.
- That's good.
[ Sniffs ]
Okay. So, I'm just gonna...
- moveyour--
- Thankyou.
Sorry. It's great.
And--
A little bit closer.
Now, I know
this isn't very nice.
It's got to be done,
hasn't it?
- I want it to look as bad as possible.
- Of course.
I lost myjob.
I was good at myjob.
What didyou do?
I'm a beauty consultant.
Okay. And ifyou just
bring your chin up.
Put it up here.
Lovely. And--
That's it.
So, what actually
happened to you?
My seat belt was broken.
I went through the windscreen.
Uh, it wasn't mycar.
I wasn't driving. It wasn't myfault.
- Yeah, you said.
- It wasn't!
You okay?
Mm-hmm.
Did the driver sustain
any injuries?
No, unfortunately.
He's obviouslynot
inyourgoodbooks.
I haven't seen him since.
I don't want to see him either.
Life isn't fair, is it?
Someone always draws
the short straw.
Okay, that's very good.
Yeah.
One more.
- Here's your receipt.
- Thankyou.
Give us a ring in the morning.
We'll see what we can do.
- Fine.
- Bye then.
Mind howyou go.
Oh, Maurice, that's terrible.
- How'dshe do that then?
- Car crash.
- Oh. She's so lovely.
- Not anymore, she isn't.
It's tragic.
She's gettin'an earful
from that dosser now.
Oh, he's been looki ng at me.
Gives me the creeps.
- I don't believe it.
- How much money do you think she'll get then?
- What?
- I nsurance.
Oh, if she's lucky,
1 5, 20 grand.
[ Sighs ] I don't know what I'd do
if it happened to me.
Think I'd kill meself.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- I didn't expect to seeyou.
- Well, I'm terribly sorry.
- Hello, Monica.
- Hi,Jane.
Just been for a facial.
I'm dyin' for a cup oftea.
- Look over there.
- What?
- That bloke.
- What bloke?
- See who it is?
- What, bythe lamppost?
Yeah. It's Stuart Christian,
isn't it?
- No.
- It is.
- But he's in Sydney.
- Is he?
- He's comin' over.
- Doesn't look very well, does he?
- It's that man.
- [Maurice ] It's all right,Jane. We know him.
- Do you?
- What's he want?
- God knows.
- Well, it's over to you then, buster.
Thanks very much.
[Door Opens ]
- Hello, Stuart.
- Maurice.
- [ Door Closes ]
- Long time no see.
Yeah. How's things?
Fine, thanks.
Fine.
- Good.
- You're looking well.
- You're still here then.
- Yep.
- Good.
- I thought we'd lostyou to Australia.
Wow.
- How's the wife and kids? Maureen.
- Monica.
- Haven't got anykids.
- Haven'tyou?
No. She's great, thanks.
- Good on ya, mate.
- [ Chuckles ]
- Are you still in the game?
- Look at all this.
What are you doing?
- It's lost its style, Maurice.
- Has it?
Looks like a dentist's
waiting room.
[ Chuckling ]
I'd kill for a cup oftea.
Ifyou're 21 or a millionaire,
it's great.
Oryou've got nine kids.
You're fine, brilliant.
Open arms.
But for guys
likeyou and me--
it doesn't matter how good you are--
forget it.
But it was an experience,
and now I'm back.
That's too bad.
- You were full of such big plans as well.
- Well, it's a bigplace.
- That's true.
- Too fuckin' big.
- [ Scoffs ]
- You're lookin' as gorgeous as ever, Monica.
So, Stuart, you thinkin'
about settin' up again?
No. Forget it.
Too much of a pain.
You know what it's like,
Maurice.
You sweatyour balls off
foryears...
and try and make people happy.
And whatyou get back?
Nothin'.
[Monica ]
Thanks.
By the way, Stuart,
this is Jane, my assistant.
This is Mr. Christian, the gentleman
I bought the business from.
- Hello.
- Hello,Jane.
- I hope he's treatin' you well.
- He's all right.
- You can work for me anytime.
- I'm all right where I am, thankyou.
Yourwife must have been
sorry to come back.
Which wife?
Ah, that bitch.
She never came out there
in the first place.
Oh.
- So, where areyou living at the moment, Stuart?
- Down at Grays.
- Essex?
- Yeah.
- Me mum's place.
- Must be nice forher.
- Havin' her boy to fuss over.
- She's dead.
- She died when I was still in Bangkok.
- Ohhh.
- [Maurice ]Sorryto hearthat.
- [Monica ] It's a shame.
Didn't see much ofher anyway.
It's my dad I miss.
You win some.
You lose some.
[ Teeth Chatter On Cup ]
- You must have had some
lovelyweather in Australia.
- Too hot.
It's too hot over there.
It's too cold over here.
- Hasn't changedmuch in here.
-Just a lick ofpaint.
- Still got the Bronica then.
- Yep.
I should have thought you'd be able
to afford a Hasselblad by now, Maurice.
I can.
- Well-off, are you?
- Hmm. Survivin', mate.
Yeah.
- You've done verywell out of
my business, haven't you?
- It's my business.
- No. It's mybusiness.
- No, Stuart. No. It used to beyourbusiness.
- I bought it from you. It's my business.
- Listen.
- This was an antique shop.
- That's right.
- There was nothing here.
- That's right. I know.
I gaveyou my good will.
I gaveyou my clientele.
- I gaveyou my fucking reputation.
- You gave me nothing, Stuart.
- With all due respect, your client list was shit.
- It wasn't.
I followed it up.
I wrote to them. I rang them.
I didn't get one bite.
Ifthere's any success in this shop,
it's down to me.
- That's bullocks.
- No, it's not bullocks, Stuart. It's the truth.
- How manyweddings doyou do?
- Oh, enough.
- How many?
- Oh, about 40 a year.
- I used to do 1 40.
- What, personally?
- No, not personally, no.
Nobody does 'em personally.
- I do.
Then you're a bloody fool.
You get people in, get 'em out there.
Ifthe work's there, take it.
You gotta grab it whileyou can.
It's not in my interest to get some tosser in.
I'll have no control.
- He could fuck up my reputation.
- I'm not a tosser!
- I didn't sayyou were.
- I'm not a fuckin' tosser.
- I'm not talkin' aboutyou.
- Don't call me a tosser!
I wasn't talkin'
about you, Stuart.
I can still do it!
I've still got an eye.
They can't teach you that.
I'm still a photographer.
Of course you are.
So ifyou want someone
to help you out...
no worries, mate.
- I'd be all right.
- Right, right.
I see whatyou're saying, Stuart.
Yeah. I'll bear it in mind.
- You could lend me a camera.
- Yeah, sure.
I had mine nicked.
Yeah, great.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
[Monica ] I thought we were never
gonna get ridofhim.
There but for
the grace of God--
Tea's on the table.
- ?? [TV: Music Hall]
- All right.
- Aren't you havin' none?
- No.
Why not?
I'm goin' out.
Where are you going?
- [TVPlaying, Indistinct]
- [Footsteps Descending Stairs ]
- I'm off now then, sweetheart.
- Ain't you gonna tell me where?
You never tell me
where you're going.
- You don't never go nowhere.
- Well, I'm going somewhere tonight.
- Ta-ta.
- Have fun.
- Don't wait up.
- [DoorOpens, Closes ]
She been actin' right funny.
- Where's she gone?
- Don't the fuck know. She wouldn't tell us.
He's all right though, Maurice.
He's always got plenty ofwine in and that.
- We'll get well-pissed.
- Yeah, nice.
- [Pub Chatter]
- [Billiard Balls Clattering]
I'm a little bit shy ofyou,
to tell you the truth, sweetheart.
Of me? Oh, you shouldn't be.
Oh, look at you sittin' there.
- You look like a model.
- Oh. Do I?
I betyou was a pretty
little girl, weren'tya?
Yeah, lovely.
- Don't do that. You'll stay like that.
- [ Laughing ]
Stop it.
Don't spoil it.
- I used to drive my mum mad pulling faces.
- Did ya?
- Bet she was a laugh, weren't she?
- Nah, not really.
- I thoughtyou said she was a midwife.
- Yeah, she was.
Well, I'd like to have been one ofthem.
I love babies.
- I'm sorry, darling.
- It's all right.
- Cheers.
- Is that all right foryou?
- Yes. Lovely.
- Wet, isn't it?
- [ Both Laugh ]
- Where's this food then? I'm ravishin'.
- [ Laughing ]
What?
[ Chuckles ]
There are so many things I wanna askyou,
but I can't rememberwhat they are.
Nice to have somebody
to talk to, isn't it?
- Give us your hand, dear.
- Oh.
God, you've got
beautiful skin.
- Right. Let's have a look atyou.
- What? Can you read palms?
I used to.
I ain't done it foryears.
Nobody's interested no more.
Ifl didn't knowyou, I could see just
by lookin' here what a nice girl you are.
Big heart. Oh, and you're gonna live
to a ripe old age and all.
- Let's have a look. Couple ofkids.
- Wow.
- Doyou want babies?
- I'm not sure really.
- No, don'tyou?
- Maybe. I don't know yet.
Yeah, of course you do.
- What star sign are you?
- Leo. I'm on the cusp ofCancer.
When's your birthday?
Oh, it's the 23rd ofJuly, ain't it?
You'd think I'd know that,
wouldn'tyou?
- That was the other day, wasn't it?
- Yeah. Sunday.
- Well, why didn'tyou say nothing
when I phoned you?
- It's no big deal.
- Did you have a party?
- No.
- What'd you do then?
- Stayed in, read me book, had a little drink.
- What, on your own?
- Yeah.
Ohhh.
Well, happy birthday for Sunday,
sweetheart.
Thankyou.
- You're out now, ain'tyou?
- Yeah, in good company.
With your mum.
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
You thought about havin'
some drivin' lessons?
- What for?
- I could getyou some foryour birthday.
- Don't be stupid.
- Getyourselfa little motor.
- Eh?
- Ain'tyou goin' out tonight?
- No.
- Why, what's happened?
- You goin' out?
- Yeah, later.
- Where you goin'?
- Down the pub. I hope you're
takin' care ofyourself.
- What doyou mean?
- You don't wanna go gettin' knocked up, doyou?
- Don't be so bloody cheeky.
- Not atyour age.
- All right.
- Missed a bit, darlin'.
[ No Audible Dialogue]
[ Both Laughing ]
- Who's this?
- Oh, don't startwith that again.
Come on.
Who is it?
- It ain't me, is it?
- No.
- Then who?
- Sylvester Stallone.
Oh. I can't understand
a word he says.
You like lookin'
at him though.
- No. He ain't my sort.
- What is your type?
- What, film star?
- Yeah.
Marlon.
I like a bloke
with a bit of meat on him.
What sort ofbloke
doyou go in for then?
Mm.
Intelligent.
Sensitive.
What, don'tyou care
what they look like?
Yeah, but they gotta have
somethin' goin' on upstairs.
You only have black boyfriends,
doyou?
Yeah.
How'd you
look afteryourselfthen?
You know, ifyou don't
wanna have babies.
[ Laughing ]
Condoms.
Oh, you just stop
at that then, doyou?
Yeah. It's the best way really.
- You can't be too careful, can you, these days.
- You gotta protectyourself.
[ Inhales, Sighs ]
It's my daughter's birthday
next week.
- How old is she?
- Twenty-one.
- Nice age.
- Well, she's your sister now, really, ain't she?
Yeah.
I suppose she is.
- Does she look likeyou?
- Yeah, a bit.
You look more like me
than she does.
We're the same build.
- What are her eyes like?
- Blue.
My brother's doin' a party for her.
That's nice. At least it takes
the strain off ofyou.
Yeah, well, there is that.
- Shameyou ain't comin' really.
- Ah.
Meetyour new family.
- Oh, sweetheart.
- What?
I nearly forgot.
- Oh.
- Happy birthday for Sunday. It's--
- Oh, you shouldn't have bothered.
- It ain't nothing much.
Ah.
Ah. Oh, thankyou.
Don't start cryin'.
- Perhaps I should ask him.
- What?
- Ifl can take someone.
- Oh, I don't know.
- It's a family thing, isn't it?
- Well, you're family, ain't you?
I'm proud ofyou.
Listen, Maurice, sweetheart.
- I wanted to askyou a favor.
- Oh, yeah? What's that then?
- You know the party Sunday?
- The barbecue, yeah.
Yeah.
Can I bring a mate?
Sweetheart?
- Hello?
- Is it a bloke?
Of course it ain't a bloke,
you silly bugger.
- Chance would be a fine thing.
- Good. Who is it then?
Oh,just someone at work.
We've been out a couple oftimes.
And I was meant to have
seen her Sunday, only I forgot.
- That all right then?
- I suppose so.
Whatyou mean,
you suppose so?
- That'd be fine.
- Smashing.
- I have to check it out though.
- Check it out? Who with?
Listen, ifl don't phoneyou
back, bring her, all right?
- I don't want to upset nobody.
- Ah, don't worry.
- Areyou sure then?
- Yeah, yeah. No problem. Yeah.
[ Cynthia ] Okay then, sweetheart.
Lookin' forward to it.
- [ Maurice ] All right. Well,
say hello to Roxanne for me.
- Yeah.
- Ta-ta then.
- All right, ta. Bye, Cynth.
Listen, I spoke to my little brother today,
and he says it's all right.
So, doyou wanna come then?
Ooh. I don't know.
I told him
you was me mate.
- I'd still feel a bit awkward.
- Oh, don't be daft, sweetheart.
You'll be with me,
won'tyou?
- It won't feel right.
- I thoughtyou wanted to come.
Yeah.
Oh, of course, ifyou've
changed your mind--
- I was lookin' forward to it.
- Oh, I know.
- Whatyou think then?
- All right. I'll come.
- You comin'?
- Yeah.
All right then, sweetheart.
Listen.
I'll giveyou a ring later in the week
and giveyou the address and everything.
- Okaythen.
- Okay. Ta-ta then.
Bye-bye.
[ Exhales ]
Jesus.
You should have
just said yes.
Make me look like a--
[ Sighs ]
- I can hardly say no now.
- It's up toyou.
Oh. I don't know anythin'
about this person, whoever she is.
Some new mate.
They've been out a few times.
- Oh, two hysterical nutters.
- I'm just glad she's got a friend.
[ Sighs ]
I'm gonna have a great time.
I thought
I'd askJane as well.
Anybody else
you want to invite?
We've only got
four garden chairs.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh. Give us
two ofthem painkillers.
Thereyou go.
Doyou fancy
some fish-and-chips?
Don't be sarcastic.
I wasn't.
Sorry.
[ Chattering ]
- [Knocking]
- [Taxi Departs ]
- There's a bell here.
- Don't do that. I just done the knocker.
All right.
- Hello there.
- Hello, sweetheart.
- You got here in one piece then?
- Long time no see.
Yes, that's right. Thankyou.
Hello, birthday girl.
- Hello, Monica.
- Oh, look atyou.
- This is Paul.
- Hello, Paul.
- How'd you do?
- Nice to meetyou.
- [Vehicle Horn Honks ]
- [Monica ] Oh, there's Maurice.
Now, come away in.
- Hi,Jane.
- Hello, Monica.
[ Sighs ]
Ah. Oh, this is Jane.
Maurice has just been
picking her up from the station.
[ Cynthia ] Here he is.
Hello, sweetheart.
- Hiya.
- [Roxanne ] You all right, Maurice?
I got you that.
- You didn't have to do that.
- It's all right.
- You all right?
- Yeah. [ Giggles ]
- This is Paul. This is Maurice.
- [ Chattering ]
- Ain'tyou got one for me then?
- Yeah, of course I do.
- Hello, darlin'.
- Don't kill 'im.
Coo! You've landed on your feet here,
ain't you, Maurice?
This is Jane,
my lovely assistant.
- I've talked toyou on the phone, ain't I,Jane?
- Yeah, that's right.
- Can I takeyour coats?
- Yes.
- What you want to drink-- red, white, rose, beer?
- I'll have white, Maurice.
- I'll have a beer.
- Oh, thanks a lot. Cheers.
- Cynth?
- I'll have white, please, Maurice.
-Jane?
- Rose.
Okey-doke.
- Where's the friend then?
- I have no idea.
- You got an ashtray, darlin'?
- There's one on the coffee table, Cynthia.
I didn't think
you would have given up.
Oh, one of the few
pleasures in life, Monica.
- These are very bright.
- Don'tyou like 'em?
I'll just put them
in a vase.
- [Roxanne ] Whatyou got that up there for?
- [ Maurice ] We like it.
Well, don't laugh.
It's stupid.
It's one ofmyearlyworks.
- The miserable little git.
- [Roxanne ] He was fuckin'
around behind the camera.
Oi. Mind your language,
you little sod.
[ Laughing ]
- So, how's work then?
- Oh, it's all right. Yeah.
- You still enjoying it?
- Yeah. It's all right.
- When you goin' to college again?
- Shut up about college.
- You're goin' to college, ain'tyou?
- No, I ain't.
- You should. You got a good brain.
- I don't wanna use it though.
- Well, suityourself.
- Yeah, I will.
- Paul's a scaffolder.
- Yeah. Your mum said.
- Bet it's hard work, isn't it?
- Can be, mate.
- Yeah, especiallyin the winter.
- That's right.
- I wanted to give it a Mediterranean feel.
- It's a lovely kitchen.
- And this is-- Oops.
- Oh, it's a big lavatory.
- This is the downstairs toilet.
- That's handy, isn't it?
'Cause ifyou're in the garden--
Exactly.
It's really convenient.
- And I think the peach tones
make it quite tranquil.
- Yeah.
So, you know where it is
ifyou need it.
Now--
Excuse me,Jane.
- This is the garage.
- [ Laughs ] I thought it was the cupboard.
- Is that a new car?
- Yes. That's my car.
- What was the matterwith your other one?
- Nothing.
I'll showyou upstairs.
Ah. We'll start with this.
- There's the tank.
- That's where I keep my towels and bed linen.
-Justyour ironing cupboard.
- Mm. It's not very capacious.
And this is Maurice's bathroom.
It's green.
Matches your tank.
- These all new carpets, are they, sweetheart?
- Oh, yes.
And this
is the masterbedroom.
Coo! It's more like
the bridal suite.
- It's beautiful.
- I've always wanted a four-poster.
- I can see Maurice thrashing about in there.
- It is a king-size.
It's like somethin'
out ofa fairy tale.
- I bet this cost a bob or two.
- It certainlywasn't cheap.
And here's another lavatory.
Oh, that bathroom's mine,
the en suite.
You've got the one each, haveyou?
That's nice, ain't it,Jane?
- It's like a hotel.
- We don't want to be trippin' over each other.
Ah, you got everything, Monica.
- [Maurice ] So, where's this friend then?
- He's here, isn't he?
- No. Your mum's.
- What you talkin' about?
She rang me at the shop and asked me
if she could bring a friend from work.
- That's the first I've heard ofit.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
- What, she nevermentionedit?
- No.
- Peculiar.
That must be who she's
been goin' out with.
She's a dark horse,
isn't she?
- [Hortense ] Hello.
- No, I'm sorry.
I'm a friend ofCynthia's.
Yes. Yes, of course.
- Hello, sweetheart.
- Hello.
- I thought you were, uh--
- Come on in.
- That's me mate, Hortense.
- Hi.
- That's me brother's wife.
- Oh, pleased to meet you.
- Monica.
- Hello, Monica.
- Come on out in the back. Meet me brother.
- Okay.
- Can I take your coat foryou, um--
- [ Both ] Hortense.
Thankyou.
This is me little brother,
Maurice.
- Hello. Pleased to meetyou, Maurice.
- How doyou do?
Ain't that little, is he?
That's Hortense.
- Hortense.
- Yeah, that's right.
- And this is me daughter, Roxanne.
- Oh, happy birthday.
- Oh, you didn't have to do that, sweetheart.
- Hereyou are.
- It's okay.
- That's Paul, her intended.
- He ain't me intended.
- And this is, um--
-Jane.
- Maurice's assistant.
- Hi.
- Very nice to meet you.
- That's nice, isn't it?
- What would you like to drink?
- Red, white, rose?
- White wine, please.
- Thanks. That's really nice.
- You're welcome.
- We'll have it later.
- No. Don't waste it.
I've got some for later
to have with the cake.
- We thoughtyou'd got lost.
- Well, I took a couple ofwrong turns.
- Did you come in a cab?
- I drove.
- She got a car.
- That's really nice. Thanks.
- Thereyou go.
- Who wants to top up?
- I'll have one with you, Maurice.
Not for me, thanks.
- You all right?
- Yeah, so far.
- Would you like a crisp, Hortense?
- No. I'm fine, thanks.
I only met Paul for
the first time today, Hortense.
- Really?
- He's a scaffolder.
- Yeah.
- Another one bites the dust.
- [ Monica ] That must be quite dangerous, Paul.
- Well, it can be.
Come have a look over here.
- Doyou have to go up really high?
- Sometimes.
-Justyou and the elements really.
- Ever fallen off? [ Laughs ]
- Would you like any crudites?
- Thankyou, no.
- I think I'll wait till later.
- Oh.
- Soyou workwith my mum, yeah?
- Yeah.
- On the machines?
- No.
- You comin' 'round tomorrow night, Paul?
- Well, it's--
- We're goin' out.
- You'll come 'round before, then, have a drink?
- It's her 21 st.
- It's no big deal.
- I ain't giveyou your presentyet.
- Chicken drumsticks.
- Doyou want some salad, sweetheart?
- Yes, please.
- I'll getyou some.
- You doin' somethin' special
tomorrow night, you two?
- No. Down to the pub, as usual.
- Can we use fingers?
Use whatyou like.
Useyour feet ifyou want.
- You've a knife and fork there,Jane.
- It's a bit late now.
- Whatyou do at the factory?
- This looks really lovely.
- I hope it don't kill you.
- There's salad servers there, Cynthia.
- You ain't her boss, areyou?
- No.
Hereyou are, sweetheart.
Doyou want some salad, Paul?
- No. I'm all right.
- It's good foryou. Makeyou grow.
He don't want none!
What aboutJane?
Does she want salad?
Yes. Not very much.
- What doyou do then, Roxanne?
- I work for the council.
- What, down at the hall?
- No. I'm a road sweeper.
- Wow.
- Are ya?
- Who's for a potato?
- She's got my plate.
- Here you are, sweetheart.
- One foryou, Hortense?
- Yeah, I'll have some ofthat.
- "Please."
- You do get girl road sweepers, don't you?
- Right. Burgers and bangers.
- Nice one.
That's your one, Roxanne. That's the one
with your name on it, the burnt one.
- All right?
- Potato foryou, Paul?
- Please.
- A nice big one.
- Hereyou are, darlin'.
- One foryou, pet?
- Shall I do you, Monica?
- I can see to myself, thanks.
Why don'tyou sit down?
What about Maurice?
Who's lookin' after the worker?
Don't worry about me.
I've been pickin'. I'll eat later.
- Your potato's on your plate, Cynthia.
- I'll have some salad.
- Can I have my tongs back, please?
- Got butter?
- Yes.Just a minute.
- I'll have some mustard whileyou're there.
- You like the American, don'tyou, Roxanne?
- Yeah. Ta.
All right.
I'll just get some salad.
- Doyou want some butter, Paul?
- Areyou all right, darlin'?
- Yeah.Just waitin' for the butter.
- Thereyou go, Cynth.
- Oh, Maurice!
- That'll shutyou up.
- Oh? You havin' a steak, areyou, Cynthia?
- Yes, thankyou, Monica.
Oh. That'll put hairs
on your chest.
Like some mustard,
orwould you prefer the French?
- This looks lovely, Maurice.
- Right.
Thereyou go, mate.
Halfa cow foryou.
- Look at the size ofthat!
- That's ridiculous.
- There's enough for all of us.
- That'll put color in your cheeks, Paul.
- You're sure no one else wants a steak?
- Ain'tyou havin' one?
- No, he's not, Cynthia.
- Not allowed.
- Would you like some mustard, Paul?
- Oh, it's lovely.
Can't get rid ofit, can you?
- Oh, it's a real communal thing, eating.
- Yes.
- This is a lovely house.
- Well, we like it.
- I'll showyou around later, ifyou want.
- Thanks. That'll be nice.
Yeah. It's brilliant.
- Doyou live in a flat then, Hortense?
- Yeah.
Yeah. It's her own.
She's got a mortgage and everything.
- Whereabouts areyou?
- Kilburn.
That's a bit ofa schlep, isn't it,
the Old Kent Road and back every day?
- You just get on the tube.
- She drives!
I drive to the station.
- You've got a bedsit, ain'tyou, Paul?
- That's right.
- Oh, that's a shame.
- Wish I had a place of me own.
- Doyou still live at home then?
- No chance.
So, doyou two
work on the same machine?
- No. I'm the only one on slits.
- Hmm.
- Doyou chooseyour own
working hours then, Roxanne?
- Not bloody likely.
Just bidin' her time
till you go to college, aren'tyou?
- I ain't goin' to college.
- Hortense went to college.
- Mm. What did you study?
- Optometry.
- What's that then?
- It's to do with the eye, isn't it?
- That's right.
- Testing.
- And you've given that all up now, haveyou?
- Not exactly.
Whatyou doin' workin'
in a cardboard-box factory then?
- I'm doing research.
- Oh.
- That's interestin'. What sort of research?
- Medical.
- What, you lookin' at her head?
- [ Laughs ]
Take no notice.
There's nothing wrong
with her head.
- Did you go to university?
- Yeah.
- Did you do a degree?
- Yes, I did.
- She just looks at our eyes, don'tyou?
- Yes, I do.
What for?
Oh, you can tell a lot about people
from lookin' at their eyes.
- That's true.
- Can you?
- Windows toyour soul.
- That's a nice way of puttin' it.
- It's true, though, ain't it?
- Who wants to top up?
- Hortense?
- No, thanks. I'm drivin'.
- Yes, please, sweetheart.
- Yeah, Maurice.
- Oi, greedy guts.
- You wanna take a leaf out ofher book, Paul.
- Lost his license.
- All right, Mum!
- Did you have an accident, Paul?
-Just had one too many. That's all.
- Thereyou go.
- The demon drinkie.
- Is that whoyou been goin' out with then?
- Yes.
- She thought I'd been seein' a bloke.
- [ Laughs ]
Could've been, I suppose.
I can still turn a few heads.
You turn stomachs.
- [ Loud Pop ]
- [ Gasping, Laughing ]
- I didn't think this'd go off.
I was just playing.
- Here. You pop one, Hortense.
[ Monica ]
We might as well pop the lot then.
- [ Roxanne ] No!
- [ Loud Popping ]
? Happy birthday toyou ?
[ All Joining In ]
- [Thunderclap ]
- [ Maurice ] ? Happy birthday, dear stinker ?
[Roxanne ]
Oh,yeah, Maurice, veryfunny.
-? Happybirthdaytoyou??
- Come on, darling.Join in.
- [ Cheering ]
- Nice one. Champagne.
- Oh, I need my camera. Did anybody bring it?
- It's there, Monica.
- Doyou have to, Monica?
- Of course I have to.
-[Cynthia ] Watch whereyou
point that, Maurice.
- [Maurice ]All under cover.
- Okay, and-- whoop.
- [ Mild Pop ]
- Yea!
Come on.
Blowyour candles out, Roxanne.
- [ Groans ]
- Everybody else, gather round.
- Come on, darling.
- Cynth, you tuck in there.
Okay. Hortense, in there.
Come around there.
Hurry up! It's burnin'
me eyebrows off!.
Right. Make a wish.
One big blow.
- And--
- Cheese!
- Yea!
- I hope yourwish comes true, pet.
- [Maurice ] Here, Roxy.
- Ta!
- All right, Cynth.
- Here you are, sweetheart.
- Oh, that's nice. Mm!
- And Paul.
- Got one.
- All right.
- Cynth again.
- Thankyou, Maurice.
- Coo! This is livin', ain't it?
- [Jane ] Yeah. Thankyou.
Okay. One forme.
All right.
You go ahead.
Oh, yeah. Okay.
Uh--
- I would like to propose a toast.
- [ Moans, Laughs ]
To Roxanne,
on her 21 st birthday.
Nowit's all legal
and twice as boring forit.
It's been legalsinceyou're 18 anyway,
so I don't know what I'm talkin'about.
- Happy birthday, sweetheart.
- [ Maurice ] To Roxanne.
- [ Quietly ] Happy birthday.
- Happy birthday.
- There you go.
- What's that?
- A book token.
- Don't be stupid. Mm.
Fuckin' hell, Maurice.
Thanks.
- Yeah, well, it'syour21st, isn't it?
- Thanks, Monica.
Oh, happy birthday, pet.
Don't spend it all
in one shop.
- Here. Happy birthday.
- [ Giggles ]
Wish I'd brought
my present with me now.
You can give it to her tomorrow, can'tyou?
That's her birthday.
It's a bet, though,
if she's there tomorrow.
Areyou gonna sit down,
darlin'?
Yes. Come and sit down,
everybody. Have some cake.
Hortense.Jane.
- [Roxanne ] Where am I goin'?
- [Maurice ]Anywhereyou like.
- Uh, yeah, we need another chair.
- Come here, Paul.
Hortense, that's foryou.
Where's the bathroom?
It's just through there, sweetheart.
[Maurice ] It's the doorstraight ahead,
and the light's on the left.
Thankyou.
Yeah.
[ Exhales Deeply ]
- She's a nice girl.
- Yeah, she is, Maurice.
- Seems very pleasant.
- Yeah, she's all right.
- [Monica ] Howyou doin', Paul?
- All right.
- Your shirt dried off now?
- Yeah. It's fine.
She takes after her mother.
- [Maurice ] Does she?
- [Monica ] Doyou know heras well?
[Maurice ]
Work at the factory, does she?
- You're lookin' at her.
- Eh?
She's my daughter.
What's the matter with ya?
Maurice, it's me daughter.
Don't be stupid.
She's had too much to drink.
She can't be the one that--
What?
Hortense, sweetheart...
she's your sister.
[ Crying ]
What?
It's her own sister, Paul.
[ Sniffling ]
You eat your cake, sweetheart.
Thanks.
- What's the matter?
- I'm all right, darlin'.
[Sniffling]
I told 'em.
[ Crying]
Tell 'em whoyou are,
sweetheart.
It wasn't supposed
to happen like this.
Yeah, well, it has, ain't it?
So you tell 'em. Go on.
[ Continues Crying]
- Is it true?
- Yes, it is.
[Maurice ]
You nevertoldherthen.
I'm sorry, darlin'.
Someone tell me
what the fuck's goin' on?
She's your sister!
Maurice?
Monica?
I always said
she had a right to know.
No! Roxanne, sweetheart!
Don't!
- Please!
- Ifyou touch me, I will smackyou!
You slag!
You fucking slag!
It ain't enough you had one bastard!
You had to have two!
- [Maurice ]Stop it. Roxanne. Roxy.
- [DoorSlams ]
Sit down, darlin'.
Sit down, Paul.
Cynthia, I think I should go.
No. I don't want you to go,
darling. You sit down.
Eat your cake,Jane.
You don't half choose
your moments, Cynthia.
But when's the right moment,
Maurice? You tell me that.
- Paul, get my coat. We're going.
- Don't go, Roxy.
- Why didn'tyou tell me?
- I thoughtyou knew.
- You used to tell me everything.
- I'm sorry.
- Well, you fuckin' well let me down!
- Don't say that.
As foryou, well,
thanks for the present!
You've ruinedmyparty,
and I hopeyou're happy!
Roxy. Roxanne.
She don't mean it, darlin'.
She's just a little bit upset.
- Where areyou going?
- I don't know.
It's all been a bit of a shock,
isn't it? Eh?
Look, I don't get it.
Did you know about her?
- I always thought she'd had a boy.
- She's a slag.
- No, she's not.
- Yes, she fuckin' is!
She loves ya.
We all love ya.
- You comin' back?
- No.
- You got to.
- Why should I?
- You got to face up to it.
- Face up to what?
[Footsteps ]
She's left her card.
- Oh, well. I'll post it on to her.
- [ Cynthia ] I'll take it.
The state she's in, you'll be lucky
ifyou ever see her again.
Oh,you'dlike that,
wouldn'tyou, sweetheart?
- Would I?
- You've been workin' at it for
1 8 years, ain't you, Monica?
- Would I?
- You've been workin' at it for
1 8 years, ain't you, Monica?
You turned my father
against me.
You turnedmyMaurice
And you turned me daughter
against me.
You'll be havin' a go
at her next, I expect.
I'm sorry about this, Hortense.
You finished there,Jane?
- Why don'tyou sit down?
- You've got a short memory, ain'tya?
- What areyou talkin' about now?
- You wouldn't have none ofthis...
ifl hadn't given Maurice
the money to start with.
That moneywasn'tyours to give.
That was your father's insurance money.
- That moneywas for me and Roxanne.
- And Maurice.
He didn't want none ofit
till he come home and talked toyou.
- He was entitled to it.
- I was goin' out cleanin'
at 5:00 in the mornin'...
comin' home,
takin' her to school...
- and then goin' out again
to do a full-day's work.
- And didn't we know it?
You've done nothing but spend his money
since the dayyou clapped eyes on it.
What areyou supposed to
do with money but spend it?
At least we've made
somethin' of ourselves.
Oh, haven'tyou? Justyou
wanna try bringin' up a kid on your own!
She can't help it.
She's never had enough love.
- And you've never got on.
- But it ain't my fault.
I know.
But she needs you.
- Come on.
- I don't want to.
What doyou think, Paul?
I think he's right, darlin'.
- Doya?
- Yeah.
- Well, I ain't sayin' nothin'.
- You won't have to.
You just have to listen.
Come on.
[ Cynthia ]
I'm sorry, Roxanne.
Itjust came out, darlin'.
I didn't mean
to spoilyourparty.
- Tell her, Maurice!
- Leave her alone, Cynth. J ust tell her the truth.
Darlin'.
I got pregnant
when I was 1 5.
And your granddad
sent me away to this place...
didn't he, Maurice?
I didn't know she was gonna
come lookin' for me, did I?
But I gotta tellyou
the truth, darlin'.
I'm gladshe did.
It ain't herfault,
sweetheart.
She didn't even wanna come. She didn't
wanna hurtyou, no more than I did.
- Oh, you tel I her, sweetheart.
- I t's true.
She didn't wanna upset you.
I 'm sorry.
You all right?
She said you weren't
never gonna come back.
- [Maurice ] Who did?
- I never said any such thing.
- She's twisted everything as usual.
- Yes,you did, Monica.
You was wrong, weren't you? 'Cause she
has come back, ain't you, sweetheart?
I always thought you
should have known, Roxanne.
- [Maurice ] You should've told her, Cynthia.
- Ofcourse I should've told her...
but I didn't think there was
ever gonna be no need to.
You seemed to have told her
all and sundry.
Meanin' me, I suppose.
And why shouldn't he?
- I'm his wife after all.
- Then whydon'tyou behave like his wife?
- What?
- Whyain'tyou give him no kids?
- Be quiet, Cynthia.
- That's between Maurice and me.
You're so selfish, Monica.
You might not have wanted 'em, but he did.
- Shut up, Mum!
- [ Maurice ] You don't know
whatyou're talkin'about.
- Don't I?
- There are things you know nothing about.
- Maurice.
- Like what?
Tell her.
Tell me what?
Why can't you tell her?
[ Sniffles, Swallows ]
She can't have kids.
Simple as that.
She's physically incapable
ofhaving children.
We've hadeverytest
known to medicalscience.
She's been pushedaround,
prodded, poked, had operations.
- We've had 15 years ofit,
and she can't have a baby.
- [ Sobs Quietly ]
I love you to bits...
but it's almost destroyed
our relationship.
You know it has.
There.
I've said it.
So where's
the bolt oflightnin'?
Secrets and lies.
We're all in pain.
Why can't we
share our pain?
I've spent my entire life
tryin' to make people happy...
and the three people I love the most
in the world hate each other's guts!
I'm in the middle!
I can't take it anymore!
[ Sniffles ]
I'm sorry, Hortense.
Butyou are a very brave person.
- Very stupid person.
- No, you're not.
You wanted to find the truth, and you
were prepared to suffer the consequences.
And I admireyou for that.
I mean it.
[ Gasps ]
[ Sobbing ]
[ Continues Sobbing]
You're so lucky, Cynthia.
[ Sobbing ]
Have you really been
working in the factory?
No.
- What you do then?
- I'm an optometrist.
Hmm.
Well, welcome to the family.
[ Sobs ]
Maurice. I wish
I'd had a dad likeyou.
You're lovely.
His name's Bingham--
yourfather.
He's fromAmerica.
I met him on holiday.
Benidorm.
He was a medical student.
Then one mornin' I come down,
and he wasn't there no more.
But he was a nice man.
He was.
Was my father "a nice man"?
Oh, don't break my heart,
darlin'.
[ Crying ]
[Continues Crying]
[ Cynthia Sobbing]
I'm all right.
[ Continues Sobbing ]
Oh, please,
Roxanne, sweetheart.
[Sobbing]
Please!
Please.
I'm frightened.
Why?
You don't love me anymore.
Not like you used to.
Maurice.
You don't know
how much I love you.
Do you?
We've got each other,
haven't we?
[ Sighs ]
Bet you never seen
so much shit, have ya?
[ Laughs ] You wanna see
my mum's house.
Doyou miss her?
Yeah.
- Did you get on with her?
- She used to drive me mad.
- That's what they're there for, though, ain't it?
- Yeah.
- That's me oldchairthere.
- Ah.
I always wanted
a little sister.
No. It's just that my brothers
were much older than me...
so I ended up playing on my own
most of the time.
I know what you mean.
[ Laughing ]
What you laughin' at?
Doyou feel
like we're sisters?
I don't know. Doyou?
[ Exhales ]
- It's a bit weird.
- Yeah.
- I don't mind it though.
- No. Nor do-- Nor do I.
- I don't even knowyou yet, do I?
- [ Laughs ]
- Doyou wanna go out one night?
- Yeah.
Yeah. You can take me
to one ofyour pubs.
Yeah, all right.
How would you
introduce me?
- As your half-sister?
- Yeah.
- No, man. Too much explainin' to do.
- It's what I'd say though.
- Would ya?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Best to tell the truth,
isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
That way, nobody gets hurt.
Hereyou are, sweethearts.
Tea's up.
- [ Hortense ] Oh.
- Go on, darlin'.
- Want a biscuit?
- No. I'm all right, thankyou.
Well, sityourself down.
- You all right with that?
- Yeah.
That's it.
Coo.
Who'd have thought it, eh?
Look atyou two sittin' there
like a couple of garden gnomes.
[ All Laughing ]
Coo.
Oh, this is the life,
ain't it?
[ Roxanne, Hortense ]
Yeah.