My name is Dalton Russell.
Pay strict attention
to what I say
because I choose my words carefully
and I never repeat myself.
I've told you my name.
That's the "who."
The "where" could most readily
be described as a prison cell.
But there's a vast difference
between being stuck in a tiny
cell and being in prison.
The "what" is easy.
Recently I planned and set in motion events
to execute the perfect bank robbery.
That's also the "when."
As for the "why," beyond the
obvious financial motivation,
it's exceedingly simple.
Because I can.
Which leaves us only
with the "how."
And therein, as the
Bard would tell us,
lies the rub.
So, your mother tells me about
a certain young lady who's helping you
with the Triborough Bridge project?
- Okay?
- All right, okay.
He's crazy.
- Now? On 51st? 50...
- Yeah, that's where he is right now.
He's on 40, he... No, he's still on 47th
Street, but it's a much smaller space.
What do I have to...
Yeah, we'll get lobster. I'll put it on Mr.
Ansinori's card.
Whatever. It's a meeting with one
of his clients or something.
Because it's been like
over a year now. Yeah.
I want to snap this guy's
neck, I swear to God.
So what?
So what? They're flowers. They
could've been to his grandmother.
They could've been to me.
It's my birthday, so...
Okay, so maybe it's a client's.
Okay. This is funny.
I got this guy in front of me that
thinks I don't see him looking at me.
Fantastic. God damn it.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah.
Can you lower your voice
just a little bit, please?
You're getting a little
loud on your phone. Please.
Yeah. Fine.
I don't want you disturbing
the other customers.
- Sorry.
- All right?
- Yeah, you got it.
- Thank you.
It was a security guy.
I didn't know I was in a library.
It's a fucking bank.
Manhattan Trust.
...from Yale. And this fucking
rich prick I work for.
Thank you.
Excuse me. Sir?
Easy.
Everybody get down on
the fucking floor! Now!
Get down on the ground!
You have four seconds!
Anyone still standing gets shot!
One! Two! Three!
Back away from that counter! Get
your hand away from that button!
Put your hands on the floor!
Now!
Oh... What the... What is this?
- Todd, what are we gonna do?
- What the fuck do you want me to do?
- Keep your head down, fat man!
- All right!
Get your fucking
face on the floor!
You get the same treatment
as everyone else, Rabbi.
Get down.
Now, my friends and I are making
a very large withdrawal
from this bank.
Anybody gets in our way
gets a bullet in the brain.
Lie down, old man! Put
your fucking hands down!
- Get your face on the floor.
- All right, I'm down! I'm down!
Hey, Officer, there's smoke
coming out of there.
Possible 10-30. Manhattan Trust.
20 Exchange Place.
I have got hostages.
You fucking cops come near this
door, I start killing people.
I not fucking kidding, man.
Central. Give me an 85.
Back up, sir! Back up! You!
- Shit!
- Back up! Back up!
Stay around the corner!
Central, give me an 85.
Perp with a gun.
Possible hostages.
I repeat, possible hostages. 20 Exchange.
Manhattan Trust.
Baby, I'm fighting for
my life over here.
Keith, every time we have this
conversation, it's the same thing.
- "Not now."
- Listen. Listen.
Do you know what kind of
thin ice I'm on right now
with this check-cashing thing?
They want to lock me up.
If this $140,000 doesn't
show up somewhere soon,
- things gonna get rough for me.
- But you didn't take it.
Of course I didn't take it, baby.
It's just some lying drug dealer
trying to save his own
ass by fucking me over.
- Eventually, it'll go away.
- Then what?
- What about us?
- Then, you know, I'll make First Grade
and we'll have enough money to buy a
bigger place and then, you know...
Why we got to have this conversation
every time your brother gets locked up
- or gets caught stealing a car?
- He's the only family I've got.
All right, I'm sorry, baby.
You okay?
- You still love me?
- I'm sorry, too.
- I love you, baby.
All right. Big Willie and the
twins for you when I get home.
- I got the handcuffs.
- I got the gun.
Bye, Big Daddy.
- Big Willie and the twins, huh?
- That's correсt.
Her lowlife brother, he's got three
priors, one for armed robbery.
17-year-old high-school dropout. Doesn't
have an honest bone in his body
and he's too fucking stupid to amount
to anything. Even as a criminal.
- Can't you get rid of him?
- I could, couldn't I?
No, she loves him. What am I gonna do?
Put him out in the street?
- How's he feel about you?
- Oh, he's thrilled.
To have a deteсtive
sleeping in the next room,
banging his sister. Then she tries
to bring it all back on me.
You know, "if we had a bigger place,
we wouldn't have this problem."
Of course, if we got married
then things would be different.
- And what's wrong with that?
- A wedding. Furniture. Kids.
You know what a
diamond ring costs?
- Come on, man. You've been married.
- Please. I was 21.
- Yeah, but you give her a ring?
- Yeah, but she won't call me back.
- You guys cops?
- Oh, shit! He made us!
Christmas came early
for you this year.
Bank robbery. Hostage situation.
20 Exchange Place.
- What?
- Grossman's on vacation. You're up.
What about the Madrugada thing?
The check-cashing thing?
- I thought I was in the doghouse.
- I just threw you a bone.
As far as I'm concerned,
you still work here,
- but if you don't think you're ready...
- No, no, he's ready!
Oh, good. Good.
I'm giving you a break, here.
Don't make me look like a fool.
- This is it, baby. The show!
- Yeah.
You got the call, man. God damn!
I guess I should be happy. I
might get to put off I.A. B.
Here's all you need to know.
You walk in unarmed.
Head bad guy puts a gun to your head
and makes you get on your knees.
You look around. There are five
armed men pointing Uzis at you.
Just picture them
in their underwear.
How about orange
jumpsuits and shackles?
- There you go, Keith. You can do this, man.
- Look out, bad guys. Here I come.
Get back around the corner!
Get back!
I told you, move it! Move it!
Get those people back! Get
them the hell out of here!
All right, guys, as soon as we
pull up, I want everybody out.
The second floor window. Now.
- Let them in there!
- Let's go! Go now!
Sarge, what do you got?
I got a perp in the bank.
Possible hostage situation.
Who's on today? Who's your boss?
- Sergeant Hernandez. I'll get him over here.
- Get him down here.
- Sergeant Hernandez, you on the air?
- On the air. Go.
Sarge, I got Sergeant Collins over here.
He called this in.
Can you come over
to the other side?
Redirect, on my way. Let's go.
Back up! Go around,
around the corner.
- Pull back. Pull it back.
- We got to keep this secure.
- Collins? What you got?
- Hernandez.
I got a perp inside with a gun. He
claims he's got some hostages in there.
Everyone, heads up!
Let's clear the way!
Let's go. Set them up.
All right.
We've got it under control.
Step back, please!
- Step back!
- Get back! Thank you.
There's nothing going on.
You'll see it on
the news tonight.
Step back, please.
Mr. Case?
Oh, good morning, Katherine.
What can I do for you?
Sir, there's a robbery in
progress at one of our branches.
Oh, my.
- Has anybody been hurt?
- I don't think so, but there are hostages.
Oh, how awful.
- Which branch is it?
- Number 32. 20 Exchange Place.
- Which one?
- 20 Exchange Place.
Thank you, Katherine.
I'm sorry, Mr. Case.
Oh, dear God.
Get these people out of here. Come
on, open these gates. Back up.
Up on the sidewalk. Come on in.
Sergeant Collins, first on scene.
Are you the hostage negotiator?
That's right. Detective Frazier. This
is Detective Mitchell. What do you got?
Not much. Saw the bank
was filled with smoke.
The door was locked. I tried
to take a look inside
and one of the gunmen opens the
door, sticks a .357 in my face,
screaming in some foreign
accent about killing hostages.
- See any other gunmen?
- No, sir. I couldn't see anything at all.
- You hear anything inside?
- No, sir,
but with that .357 sticking in my face,
I can't really be sure. I'm sorry.
Okay.
Good, good. Good, good, good, good.
You did a good job, Sergeant.
You ever had a gun stuck
in your face before?
- Yeah, once.
- Really?
Yeah, by a 12-year-old.
- What was that like?
- Not one of my better days.
I bet. All right, well, look.
As soon as we get this thing cleared
up, we'll cut you loose, all right?
If you don't mind, I'd
rather hang around a while,
at least until we make contaсt.
That's what I like
to hear, Sergeant.
What? Come on. Why you doing this?
Why you doing this to me?
Pop, what's going on? Yo.
All bank employees,
raise your hands!
Bank employees, this side!
Everyone else, over there!
Now, I need everybody to take
your cell phones and your keys
out of your pockets and handbags
and hold them in the air.
- What's your name?
- Peter.
- Peter what?
- Peter Hammond.
- Where's your cell phone, Peter Hammond?
- I left it at home.
Peter, think very carefully about
how you answer the next question
because if you get it wrong,
your headstone will read,
"Here lies Peter Hammond, hero,
"who valiantly attempted to
prevent a brilliant bank robbery
"by trying to hide
his cellular phone,
"but wound up getting shot
in the fucking head."
Now, Peter Hammond,
where is your cell phone?
I'm telling you, I did.
I left it at home.
Okay, I fucked up. I'm sorry.
Please.
Hey. Don't worry about it.
Just let me talk to you!
Please, please, listen to me.
Let me explain.
Help! Help me.
Stop!
Anyone else here
smarter than me?
- And you are?
- Vikram Walia.
Vikram Walia. Thanks, Vikram.
Hey, mister.
Keep it.
Men here. Women here.
Move!
I need all of you to strip
down to your underwear.
Now.
Lady?
Believe me. This is the only situation
where I'd ask you to do this.
- But take off your fucking clothes.
- No.
You should be ashamed
of yourself.
What's with you mishegoyim?
Go ahead. Make my day.
- Take your fucking clothes off, lady.
- No!
Stevie?
Let's go!
Now, I need all of you
to put on one of these
suits and these masks.
I'm Shon Gables, with CBS 2 News,
outside Manhattan Trust Bank,
where we have just been
told by investigators,
the bank has been robbed.
The suspect or possible
suspects are inside,
holed up with an unknown
number of hostages.
- Captain Darius?
- Yeah.
I'm Deteсtive Frazier. This
is Deteсtive Mitchell.
Hey.
You may remember, we worked
that hospital thing on 93rd,
during my training?
Oh, yeah. That was a real shame.
Yeah, it was. It was.
So, what do we got?
I got an unknown number of suspects
and an unknown number of hostages,
and a bank, and about a million spectators,
and I can't see shit inside there,
- so I'm kind of busy.
- I understand.
The way this works, Mr. Frazier,
is I deal with Mr. Grossman.
So if you need anything, you
can speak with him, okay?
No, it's not okay, Captain.
Detective Grossman
is away on vacation,
so Deteсtive Frazier is the
big dick today, all right?
Now, if you need anything, you
can speak to me, all right?
I guess it'll have to be.
That's the way it's gonna be.
You got vests for us?
- Berk!
- Yo!
- Get these guys some vests!
- Okay.
- And check them into the command log.
You know what? I'm gonna
get out of your hair
and let you get control of
this crime scene, okay?
You'll let me know when you're
ready with a detailed briefing?
- Okay.
- We're gonna take a walk down to the diner.
Don't go in the bank without
calling us first, all right? Okay?
- All right.
- Good to see you, Captain.
Shouldn't we be in there?
Let's give him some time.
See what he does. Come on.
Until he secures his position
and gets the physical layout,
he'll only dump on us.
If the show starts, he'll call us.
Trust me. I've seen him work.
Your call, Keith.
Can you get that for me?
I guess it is, isn't it?
That's the one thing I
learned from Grossman,
is these guys don't have
much respect for what we do.
- How do you mean?
- Well, to them it's a tactical situation.
Us being here means there's a mental
side to it that they don't get.
- Told you, you could handle this.
- Yeah.
I keep waiting for someone higher up
on the food chain to show up and say,
"Here's what we do."
What happened at the hospital?
Guy shot himself, shot his girlfriend.
Thank you.
I told you, I've got
a heart condition.
Get up.
Put down
your fucking weapons!
- Don't move! Don't move!
- Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
- Don't move! Don't move! Come here!
- I haven't got...
- Come here, come here, come here!
- I work in the bank!
On your knees! Down
on your knees now!
- They sent me out here!
- Now!
- He said stay away!
- Cuff him.
If you come near the bank, he'll
throw out two dead bodies!
- Who said this? Who?
- I don't know who!
The guy with the
big fucking gun!
- That's who!
- All right, get on your feet. Let's go.
- There's four of them in there!
- Come on.
Christ!
- Calm down!
- Let's go!
- Am I gonna be on TV?
- Yeah. A big star. Let's go. Come on.
Was it a time when I thought I might
not see my family again? Yeah.
Yeah, I thought about it. I
mean, at first, I wasn't...
It was too much to think
about at that point.
You know, with a gun in your
face, but after a while I...
You know, I thought about...
Yeah.
My wife, you know, not
seeing my wife again.
My kids. I got a 10-year-old
son, 17-year-old daughter.
Yeah, I thought about it, man.
What do you think?
Those are my babies.
Beautiful.
Go ahead.
Miss White, I want
you to rest assured
my only intention is to spend
time in your wonderful city
and to enjoy all that
it has to offer.
And no business with your uncle?
In truth, I have very little
to do with him these days.
I'm told you haven't seen him
in nine years. Is that right?
- You are extremely well informed.
- I have to be. Yes?
I have a Mr. Arthur Case
on the phone for you.
We'll need to end this here.
I'm gonna need a copy of
your purchase agreement,
your mortgage application,
and the other documentation,
- and I'll be in touch.
- Thank you, Miss White.
Right this way, sir.
Arthur Case? You sure?
- That's what he said.
- He said his name, just like that?
It wasn't his secretary
saying he was on the line?
- No, ma'am.
- All right. Put him through.
Okay.
- This is Madeleine White.
- Miss White, I'm Arthur Case.
Oh, good morning, Mr. Case.
- Have we met formally?
- No, sir, I don't believe we have.
Yet, you're always turning up
at my July 4th parties
in Southampton.
Yes, we know some
of the same people.
It seems.
I'll come right to the point.
I have a small problem
which requires someone
with very special skills
and complete discretion.
Are you such a person or
have I been misinformed?
Go on.
Can I pick you up in front of your
office building in five minutes?
- I'll be downstairs.
- Thank you.
They had a kind of genius plan
for throwing us out of whack
and depriving us of any kind of
way of controlling ourselves.
They were... They were very
insistent, and yet,
strangely detached.
All I know is that they called
each other a variation of Steve.
Steven, Steve-O, Stevie.
And they called you what?
They didn't call me anything.
They just told me...
You're lying to me. Tell me the truth, now.
You're lying to me.
Tell me the... Look at me
and tell me the truth.
They had AK-47s out.
Four of them.
- You know a lot about guns.
- No.
- I don't know anything about guns, except...
- But you know they had an AK-47.
- Everybody knows what an AK-47 is.
- Everybody?
Anybody who's ever watched a
decent aсtion movie would.
- You ever rob a bank before?
- Are you kidding?
Me rob a bank? No.
- Never stole a dollar?
- Never.
- Never?
- Not ever.
- You know what?
- That one time. That one time, that one time.
I stole a nickel from my
grandmother's pocketbook once.
She was Polish.
I used to go up to her and say,
"Mama, toh nicklah, toh nicklah."
One day, I opened her pocketbook
and there was a nickel.
I took it.
That was the only
thing I ever took.
Look, Detective, I didn't mean to
give you a hard time back there.
Forget about it. What's
the story, Captain?
Well, the hostage they let
go was Herman Gluck, 73.
He was having chest pains.
Paramedics have him.
They told him to say that if
any cops came near the door,
they'd throw out
two dead bodies.
He thinks there's four perps. Says
they came in dressed as painters.
There's a video
system in the bank.
We're working on
getting a download
from Manhattan Trust's central security
office, but it'll take a while.
We got the block locked up.
I got men in the windows.
We're checking on the sewers with D.
E. P.
What about the phones?
Cut and diverted into M.C.C. We're
the only ones they're gonna call.
Cell phones are monitored and we
can jam the air whenever you say.
But we like to leave it clear in case
a hostage is able to get through,
but so far nothing.
- 911?
- It's up on the screen.
Any call about a bank gets
routed straight to us.
Well, that's my end
of it, Detective.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm not calling them yet.
Beg your pardon?
Doesn't feel right yet,
you know what I mean?
I'm not gonna call him and
ask what I can do for him.
Let's see what he does.
Your call.
Now, Mr. Case, why don't you let
me explain to you how I work?
Please. That would be nice.
Well, you say that there are family
heirlooms inside your safety deposit box.
That's fine.
But in my experience, people like
you have people working for them
that handle these
kinds of things.
And when they can't, well,
they don't call me.
Their people call me.
So, immediately, I know that
there's something in that box
that you don't even want your
closest aides to know about.
No problem with me.
You tell me I don't need to know what's
in that box and I don't need to know.
But if you tell me that it's a
bunch of old baseball cards
and I find out that it's the launch
codes for a nuclear missile,
then let's just say we no
longer have an agreement.
- Have you finished?
- Yes.
What's inside that
box, young lady,
has belonged to me since
before you were born.
It's very valuable and poses no
danger whatsoever to anyone.
Except you.
Okay. Well, first, there are
men with guns in there,
so I can't guarantee any results.
Agreed?
- Of course.
- All right.
Now, what makes you think that
they want to rob your box?
I don't.
Well, why don't you tell me how
you would like this to end?
I'd prefer that nobody ever
touch my safe deposit box.
Not them, not you,
not the authorities.
And the sooner this situation
ends, the happier I'll be.
- Is that specific enough for you?
- No.
The contents of that box
are of great value to me.
So long as they
remain my secret.
And if they're exposed?
I'll face some
difficult questions.
- So, it stays locked or it disappears.
- Precisely.
- Can you make that happen?
- Yes.
I hope so. I have to say, I
can't help but be skeptical.
Whoever gave you my
number got the same deal.
Clearly, they must
have been satisfied.
Steve?
It's time for Steve-O.
I came out here to take a look
at the perimeter they laid down.
Guess what I found?
That hostage they let out said these guys
came in dressed like painters, right?
Yeah.
Probably stolen.
Have them run it and
check it for prints.
- Everybody on?
- Yep, I'm there.
- Sure you got the right number?
- Absolutely.
Okay. Nothing yet.
We got video.
Let's have it.
What happened to
that camera right there?
Wait. Hold on,
hold on, hold on.
Yeah, there it is.
That guy right there.
It's like he blinds the
camera with the flashlight.
It's weird, isn't it? It's
like nobody else sees it.
- You'd think it'd be pretty bright, huh?
- Lt could be infrared.
- What's that?
- Infrared bulb.
See, humans can't see it, but a
video camera will pick it up.
He could knock out the cameras
without no one knowing.
Right,
right, right, right.
He knocked out
the cameras about 10:00.
So, for approximately
two minutes,
we got no evidence of people leaving
or entering the bank. That's great.
Miriam, how long were
you there before it began?
It was just a few minutes.
Well, can you tell us what happened
after the explosions and the smoke?
They just told us to put our heads down.
And then close our eyes.
And then I just
remember one of them
telling the others to just
go down and fix the cameras.
- The video cameras?
- I don't know.
Anything else you want
to share with us?
No, just...
- You sure?
- Yeah, I...
Could you give us the names
of the bank robbers, maybe?
I'm just messing with
you, sweetheart.
- You okay?
- Thank you.
Okay.
- It was pretty awful.
- Was it bad?
I mean, they made us strip.
They made us
take off our clothes.
I don't understand why
they had to do that.
I really just thought...
I thought I was gonna be killed.
Well.
- All right, my dear.
- Okay.
- I can go?
- No.
- No?
- No, you got to stay.
- You got to stay.
- No, you can go.
No, stay. No, go.
Did you rob the bank?
- You did.
- Did you rob the bank?
- No.
- You sure?
- There's movement at the front door.
- Let's go.
- Put down the fucking weapon!
- Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
Don't move!
He's got a
device on him there.
I said put your hands on your head
and get down on your fucking knees!
I said put your hands on your
head and down on your knees now!
- Hands are tied!
- Hands are tied.
- Jesus, pat him down.
- All right.
- I'm one of the hostages!
- Careful.
Easy, be very
careful, now. Easy.
I can't see
him from where I'm at.
- I can see him. I got a clear shot.
- Any weapons?
- Who are you?
- Vikram Walia. I work in the bank.
Okay. Vikram? Is this a bomb?
- Oh, shit! A fucking Arab!
- What? No. I'm a Sikh!
- Is that a bomb?
- No.
- Answer me, Vikram. Is this a bomb?
- Are you booby-trapped?
- No, fuck, no.
Okay, Vikram, I
need you to relax.
- Jesus, give me a hand.
- I don't know.
Just watch. There's a
lot of movement in that bank.
- Team, take him down.
- Mike, now, get him.
What the fuck? Easy, easy.
Get off my... That's my turban.
Get off. Easy.
Get... My turban! Look,
fuck, give my turban back!
Come on, shut up. Relax.
What the fuck are you doing?
Give me my turban back.
- You can't fucking rip my turban.
- Shut up, already.
- What the fuck?
- Come on, move it.
Get your fucking hands off me!
And the 11:00 and 12:00...
And don't forget about your 1:00
with Chancellor Joel Klein.
- Oh, Madge. What a day...
- Your Honor.
Madeleine! How are you?
I'm just fine, but thank you for
seeing me on such short notice.
- Sure. Madge, are we through here?
- Yes, Mr. Mayor.
This way, Miss White.
I always have time to put on a tux
and eat free food for a good cause.
Who are we saving this week?
Well, I'm doing a
round of support
for the Joseph Freidkin Memorial
Fund for Spinal Cord Research
and we're having our annual
fundraiser next month.
If you could attend, it
would give us such a boost.
It would be my pleasure. Is there
anything else I can do to...
- What the fuck do you want?
- A favor.
- No shit. Which kind?
- The last one I'll ever ask of you.
That's the kind I had in mind.
You know about this
hostage situation.
On my way. What's
it to do with you?
All right, well, I need
to keep an eye on it.
So, I want you to bring me down
there and tell whoever's in charge
to extend me every courtesy.
You're out of your fucking mind.
If it was easy, it wouldn't
square us, would it?
- It's impossible.
- Nothing's impossible.
You just have to call in a
few markers, that's all.
I may have to give out a few.
Then that's exactly
what you'll do.
You're a magnificent cunt.
Thank you.
It's been a very tense situation
for several hours now.
It's unclear how many
hostages are inside
and how many robbers
police are dealing with.
Officials say this all started out
as a robbery at Manhattan Trust,
but has turned into
this hostage situation.
Negotiators are here on the
scene, working very hard
and it's still unclear on
any possible injuries.
Of course, we'll keep you up
to date with the very latest
and we will remain here on the
scene as this all unfolds.
That's the latest from
here in lower Manhattan.
Reporting live, I'm Sandra Endo.
Back to you.
"Protect and serve" my ass.
Where's my turban?
I'm not talking to anybody
without a turban.
It's part of my religion, to cover my
head in respect to God. I'm a Sikh.
Okay,
we'll find your turban.
Not an Arab, by the way, like
your cops called me outside.
Now, no, I don't think
you heard that.
There was a lot going on. You
were probably disoriented.
- I didn't hear that.
- I heard what I heard.
I'll give you all the
information you want.
I don't need this. I need my turban.
It's part of my religion.
- We'll get you your turban.
- We'll find it for you.
No, no, no. Not "get me."
I want my turban now.
You just got to start thinking about
the people inside the bank now.
It's a dangerous situation.
You got to start telling us about
what's going on inside the bank.
We can talk about this later. We'll
get an officer to come down.
You can write a
formal complaint.
But for now, we got to
deal with this situation.
First you beat me, and
now you want my help.
You need to start thinking
about your coworkers.
I could apologize on behalf of the NYPD,
but that was not us. We are deteсtives.
- We're gonna try and find out...
- What do you want to know?
- How many were there?
- I think there were about four.
- How many hostages?
- I don't know how many hostages, 20, 30.
I'm fucking tired of this shit. What
happened to my fucking civil rights?
Why can't I go anywhere
without being harassed?
I get thrown out of a bank. I'm a hostage.
I get harassed.
I go to the airport.
I can't go through security
without a "random" seleсtion.
Fucking random, my ass.
I nearly lost my job...
I bet you can get a cab, though.
I guess that's one of the perks.
Put the ice on your face.
"Two buses with full gas tanks.
One jumbo jet with full gas tank"
"and pilots at JFK, parked
at the end of runway."
They give us until
9:00 pm to do this,
then they kill one hostage every
hour in front of TV cameras.
"Bank is secured with Semtex. We
will demonstrate if necessary."
- Whatever you do, don't give them a jet.
- There's no plane. Maybe a bus. Maybe.
Till I talk to them, they get nothing.
Not even a cup of coffee.
For now, we wait.
Let's let them wonder
what we're doing, okay?
Excuse me, Detectives.
This is Arthur Case.
- He's the...
- I'm Chairman, Board of Directors.
- Of the bank. You wanna talk to him?
- Absolutely.
Mr. Case, how are you?
I'm Deteсtive Frazier.
Anything in particular you
think we should know?
No. I just wondered if I
might be of some assistance.
- Have they made any demands?
- They want a jet.
Oh, I see.
Would you like me to
arrange one for you?
I'm so sorry. I must
have misunderstood.
That's quite all right, Mr.
Case.
Where can we reach you
if we need anything?
Well, those are my people
in there, you know,
and I would like to stay here for a while.
And I won't disturb you.
- I'll be very quiet right down...
- Sergeant Collins!
Mr. Case, we'll try and keep
you posted as best we can,
but you're gonna have to
excuse us for now, okay?
- Right this way, sir.
- Thank you very much.
- Absolutely.
- This way, sir.
- Thank you very much.
- And thank you all so much.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
This way, sir.
"Fifty hungry people
need food now."
All right. Are we ready
with the listening devices?
I'm gonna need 15 minutes
once we get the food.
Pizza's the best. No sandwiches.
- Is she for real?
- Are you for real?
Well, if we send in, say, 10
pizzas boxes with transmitters,
maybe we'll get some conversation if we
give them something to group around.
Give them each a sandwich,
it's hit or miss.
They can move around and I
don't have 50 transmitters.
- What's this?
- It's a digital recorder.
You click it, and it'll
record for half an hour.
- James Bond shit.
- Well, you can get them on Amazon.
- You gonna ask for a hostage?
- He already gave us one, didn't he?
I ask for another one,
he says no, then what?
No, he knows what he's doing.
He gave us a hostage.
We'll give him some food.
I don't want to get
caught bluffing this guy.
Fuck this shit. Look, they want to shoot me
for taking off my mask, they can go ahead.
Do you wanna get us all killed?
You wanna relax? What the
hell is the difference?
They're out there
robbing the bank!
- Can't you see they fucked him up?
- Shut up.
You think they dressed us
like this for fun, puñeta?
- I have no idea.
- Please shut up.
...why they made us put
on all of this crap.
Probably so when the cops
break in and try to rescue us
- we all get fucking shot.
- Oh, my God!
It's a great plan,
but, no, thanks.
I told you to shut up!
Leave him!
No! Don't do this to me!
Please, don't.
I'll do as you say!
No! Help! Help!
Please, don't! Don't!
One guy did most of the talking.
He told everyone
else what to do.
- So they were talking amongst themselves?
- We couldn't hear them.
They had us in these rooms.
The doors were
locked all the time.
We didn't know what
they were doing.
- Did you hear anything they said?
- I have problems with my hearing.
- I see.
- I wear hearing aids.
- Where are they?
- They're in my ears.
- Let's see.
- Let me see them.
- Yeah, let's take a look at them.
- Yeah, it's a hearing aid.
That's your other one, there?
What's the red part, there?
What does that do?
They're different colors.
You need two different...
And to distinguish
right from left, also.
- Distinguish right from left?
- Yeah.
Right from wrong.
I don't understand.
- Steve?
- I'm sorry?
- I didn't say anything.
- Oh.
Steve. Is that your name? Steve?
Stevie? Steve-O?
- How much are they gonna pay you?
- I'm sorry?
- You heard me.
- No, I didn't.
- How much are they going to pay you?
- Who's gonna pay me?
- Were you involved in this robbery?
- Absolutely not.
Were you involved
in this situation?
- What situation?
- Don't lie. Don't lie.
If he gives us a
tip, I'm keeping it.
- Put that gun down!
- Check that weapon!
All right, everybody, relax.
Calm down. Calm down.
Calm the fuck down!
How you doing?
I'm Detective Keith Frazier,
Hostage Negotiation Team.
How's it going?
Okay. I hope the pizzas are okay.
They might be a little cold.
Listen, you pick up the
phone anytime you want.
It's a direсt line to me.
I would love to talk to you.
Nice talking to you.
Shit. Fucking Russians.
Call Operations. See if they can get
a Russian translator over here ASAP.
And get some fucking body bags.
I hope you know
what you're doing.
Because if my guys got to shoot it
out with those fucking savages...
Okay, okay, okay. Mitch?
Check with either one
of the hostages.
Find out if they heard any Russian or
Russian accents when they were in there.
We'll be all right.
No!
Down on the floor!
Come on, sweetheart. Let's go.
Let's go.
Stop crying! Shut the fuck up!
Get in there! Sit down!
Put your masks on!
Come on, let's go.
Come on, boobs.
- "Boobs"? Who the fuck you talking to?
- Let's go. You heard me! Shut the fuck up!
- Why?
- Move that fat ass! Let's go! Come on!
"Fat ass"? Are you kidding me?
If you don't shut the fuck up, I'm
gonna put my foot up your fat ass!
Put your masks on!
Put your hands on the ground!
Okay, okay.
On the floor.
Hands are on the floor.
Masks on!
Put your hands on the ground!
Come on, boobs, let's go.
Oh, shit. Sit down! Sit down!
She was on
line in front of me.
He was the teller on my line.
This guy was to my right and
his kid was in front of him.
He was playing
with a video game.
I remember her.
- Why do you remember her?
- Great tits.
- You remember seeing any of them after?
- Yeah, I saw her one time afterwards.
- How are you sure you saw her again?
- I could see under the suit.
Can't hide quality like that.
This guy, he almost
got us all killed.
How?
They put eight or nine of us
in an office for a while.
This guy took off his mask and was
talking like he wasn't afraid.
"I don't have to wear this
damn mask," you know?
So, they come in, pull him out of the
room and smack him around a little.
- You see him again after that?
- No.
- Was he okay?
- Seemed fine.
- You recognize anyone else from that room?
- I can't be sure about the others.
No one?
- Why don't you keep looking?
- You know, I was terrified.
What about before it began?
You didn't look around while
you were waiting in line?
I was talking to my
girlfriend on the phone.
You wanna take another picture?
I could bend over and
pick up a pencil.
Whatever.
This guy.
Asshole.
What the fuck? This
ain't Russian.
No? What the hell is it?
It's not Polish. Not Hungarian.
Bulgarian, maybe.
It's Central European. Sort of.
That's it? I mean, you're
the language expert.
What? No.
- What do you think?
- Well, okay.
Well, this is New York City.
Somebody on the street
must know what it is.
Probably the hot-dog man.
Berk, play that over the speaker for me.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Does anybody know what language
they're speaking? Anybody?
Yo, my man.
Hey, Phil, let that guy through.
Come on.
- You know what language they're speaking?
- Yeah, they're speaking Albanian.
- Albanian?
- Albanian. From Albania.
What am I doing here?
Yo, am I getting
arrested for something?
No, you're not getting arrested.
Come on. Come on.
Whoa.
- Okay. What are they saying?
- I have no idea what they're saying.
You got no idea? I thought
you said you spoke Albanian.
No. I never said I
speak Albanian.
You said you spoke Albanian.
I never said I speak Albanian.
Well, how do you
know it's Albanian?
My ex-wife and her
parents are Albanian.
Her parents couldn't
speak English for shit.
I have no idea what
they're saying,
but I'll tell you right now that
the language is 100% Albanian.
- 100%?
- 100%.
Call the Albanian Consulate. See
if they can get somebody over here
to translate this for us.
Make it happen fast.
Okay, you hang out in
the back for me, okay?
Oh, man, not again.
Van was stolen two days ago,
but it's clean. No prints.
- Nothing?
- Nothing.
Albanian?
My man, like I told
you, 100% Albanian.
Undeniable.
- Hey.
- Thanks.
Yo, yo, yo. There
go that motherfucker right there.
Hey, yo, you thought you was gonna
get away with that shit, didn't you?
How does this game work?
You get points for doing dirt, like
jacking a car or selling crack.
And you lose points if someone
jacks your ride or shoots you.
Come on, baby.
Take that! Take this!
What? What? What?
Talk shit now! I don't hear you!
Eat this! Eat that! Eat this!
Eat that!
You're gone, baby! You're dead!
Bye-bye!
Jesus!
What's the point of this?
Like my man 50 says, "Get
rich or die tryin'."
Yo, you'd get mad points for
knocking over the bank.
- You think that's cool?
- Hell, yeah. You trying to get paid, too.
Finish your slice. I'll take
you back to your father.
I got to talk to him
about this game.
- Is it good?
- No doubt.
It's gonna be okay.
Cool.
You'll be home soon.
That's whassup.
- Sir?
- Yeah.
- No luck with the Albanian Consulate.
- What do you mean?
I couldn't tell what the guy was talking
about. I think he wanted money.
And I tried the State Department.
That takes a month.
Okay.
- Call her.
- Are you crazy?
- I hate that bitch. Come on.
- You said she speaks Albanian, right?
- Yeah, she was born there.
- Call her.
I'm gonna regret this.
- Who's Deteсtive Frazier?
- Right here.
- I have llina Maria over here.
- Miritia.
- Oh, how you doing?
- Hello.
How you doing?
- What's this?
- Parking tickets. You can fix them?
Yeah, I'll see what I can do.
Can you listen to this and
tell us what they're saying?
You can't smoke in here.
Shit. Go ahead.
What's so funny? What, you know
what they're talking about?
I know what they're talking about.
I even know who it is.
You know who it is? You
mean you know their names?
- Who? I mean, who is it?
- Parking tickets?
- They're taken care of. Who is it?
- It's Enver Hoxha.
- Who?
- He was the president of Albania.
Wait.
You're telling me the former president
of Albania is in there robbing a bank?
Enver Hoxha's dead.
That's a tape of him discussing how
Albanian people are great people.
They are immortal people.
I wouldn't worry.
It's a tape. You're
sure about that?
I had to listen to all
this nonsense in school.
"Communism is great. Capitalism is evil.
Lenin, Marx, blah, blah, blah."
It's Enver Hoxha. It's a tape.
Okay. Okay, well, Officer,
you can take her home.
And do me a favor, huh? Watch
where you park next time, okay?
So, they're playing
tapes for us now.
They knew we were
gonna bug them.
Yeah, you're damn right they knew we
were gonna bug them. And they knew how.
What makes it even worse,
they wanted us to bug them
so they could send us
on a wild goose chase.
Last time I had my johnson
pulled that good, it cost me $5.
$5?
Yeah, Tijuana. Don't ask.
Look at the... Oh, fuck that.
- Detective Frazier. Nice to meet you.
- My pleasure.
This is Madeleine White.
- How do you do, Miss White?
- It's an honor, Detective.
Miss White may be
able to assist you.
Good. Good. What do
you have in mind?
She has a certain amount of
influence in these matters
for reasons which I
can't share with you.
What are you trying to say, sir?
What the Mayor means is that
there are matters at stake here
that are a little bit above
your pay grade. No offense.
And he's offering to help you.
Well, why don't you just tell the Mayor
to raise my pay grade to the proper level
and problem solved.
From what I hear, that would
have happened a long time ago
if you'd been a little bit more diplomatic.
But we can certainly discuss it.
Look, I'm kidding. I mean, I make
First Grade when I make First Grade.
You want to speed that up, I'm
not gonna talk you out of it.
Then there's also the matter of
$140,000 that seems to have walked away
from the Madrugada
check-cashing bust.
Oh, I see.
Well, I had nothing
to do with that.
Yeah, Collins, we got
snipers in the windows here.
We got guys in the building next door.
Guys up on the roof.
We're trying to get the
blueprints for the bank
so we can figure out the ventilator shaft.
Maybe we can come down.
- Well?
- Is this the President of Albania?
- Speaking.
- Pretty funny.
- You shouldn't eavesdrop on people.
- Well, you better get used to it, pal.
There's not gonna be much
privacy where you're going.
You're damn right.
This time next week, I'll be
sucking down piña coladas
in a hot tub with six girls
named Amber and Tiffany.
More like taking a shower with
two guys named Jamal and Jesus,
if you know what I mean.
And here's the bad news,
that thing you're sucking
on, it's not a piña colada.
- Maybe you like that kind of thing, huh?
- You really want to piss me off.
All right, here's
where we stand.
I don't need your fucking
status report, Serpico.
I tell you where things stand.
- Sure, sure. I just meant...
- Here's where things stand.
You're getting me
what I asked you for.
You'll have it ready
in the time I gave you
or you'll sit by and you'll watch me
do just what I said I would do. Clear?
Very clear. I'm trying to
get you what you want.
But you got to understand this.
You know, it's not like the City of New York
has 747s waiting around for days like today.
I understand that if you
don't get my plane ready,
- then you might as well send a hearse.
- Please.
Let's focus on how we can both
get what we want, all right?
Hey! You're not listening.
You get me what I want,
I won't kill anyone.
All right. I'm on it. I'm on it.
Let's just try to keep
everybody calm, okay?
- Don't I sound calm to you?
- Yeah, you do.
Yeah, you do.
- So, Mr. Damerjian...
- Damerjian.
- Damerjian. Is that Albanian?
- Just call me Kenneth.
- Kenneth?
- Is that Albanian or...
It's Armenian.
What's the difference?
Detective, I was born in Queens.
I've never been to Armenia, Albania.
I went surfing in Australia once.
Can I have a glass of water?
- Are you thirsty?
- My throat's parched.
- I'm not nervous.
- Your throat's parched?
- My throat's parched.
- His throat is parched.
- I just want a glass of water.
- Oh, shit!
When you start telling us
what really happened...
- I just want a glass of water.
- His throat is parched.
- Here. You want some coffee?
- No, that's all right.
- I don't drink that stuff.
- No, go ahead.
Did you know they were
robbing the bank?
I didn't know they were robbing the bank
until they pulled a gun in my face.
Is that why you held the
door open for them?
How do you know they
robbed the bank?
Because they pulled
a gun in my face...
That doesn't mean they
were robbing the bank.
Did they take money? Did
you see them take money?
I was in a bank and I was locked
up for who knows how long.
- Okay.
- Tied up in a room. I saw you see me.
You saw me see you?
- Is that what you just said?
- Yeah.
I was locked up in the room. You
saw me gagged when you came in.
Listen, I can't work miracles over here.
I'm gonna need more time.
Well, perhaps if you'd use the time
that I gave you more efficiently,
you wouldn't be
having this problem.
- What do you want me to say?
- That my plane is ready.
Okay, listen.
I promise you, as God is my witness,
I'm working on it as hard as I can.
It's just gonna take
a few more hours.
Why should I give
you any more time?
Well, it's simple. You give me
more time, you get what you want.
You don't give me the time,
you don't get what you want.
You got nothing to lose.
Meanwhile, we'll send
in some more food.
I got a question for you. You get
it right, I give you more time.
- And?
- You know what happens if you don't.
Which weighs more?
All the trains that pass through
Grand Central Station in a year,
or the trees cut down to print
all US currency in circulation?
Here's a hint. It's
a trick question.
What the hell is that?
Playing games now?
It's the trains.
US money isn't printed on paper at all.
It's cotton.
- Yeah, I heard that.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Okay.
- So no trees were cut down.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah. 100%.
Okay.
I got it.
- Wait a second. Wait a second.
- I'll call you back.
It's a trap. They
both weigh the same.
Tell him they both weigh the same.
They both weigh nothing.
They both weigh nothing or
they both weigh the same?
Tell him they both
weigh the same.
Tell him they both weigh the same.
Do it now.
They both weigh the same.
Got it.
- Well?
- They both weigh the same.
This time, send sandwiches.
That's pretty good.
This guy's nuts.
He said, "Grand
Central Station."
Grand Central Terminal
is the train station.
- Grand Central Station is the post office.
- Is the post office.
- He's wrong.
- Who's wrong?
Perp One. Trains don't pass
through Grand Central.
It's the last stop
for every train.
- What about the subway? They run through.
- Metro-North goes there.
- How the fuck do you know?
- Metro-North goes there!
No. Metro-North starts there.
What are you guys talking about?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
- Metro-North goes through!
- Let's just get the sandwiches.
- Metro-North...
- Deal is, he said, "Passes through."
Yeah, but the Metro-North
goes up there, though.
Look, shut up. It
doesn't matter, anyway.
I know what he meant.
What he said is one thing, but
what he meant is another.
Yeah. That's always
a problem, isn't it?
Sandwiches.
I'm on it, I'm on it.
You know, right now I could go
for a nice kosher hot dog and a beer.
I had Met tickets tonight.
And Pedro's pitching!
They're gonna get
their asses kicked anyway.
- Tell me about it. I'm better off here.
- I'm glad they didn't separate us.
- Do you think they're terrorists?
- They're robbers, not terrorists.
How do you know? They
could be Al-Qaeda.
Trust me. I've studied
these things.
- What are you, Mossad?
- No. I was a lawyer.
Now I teach courses at Columbia
Law on genocide, slave labor,
- war reparation claims.
- Mira.
- Can I sue anybody when this is over?
- Oh, sure. Go nuts.
Go meshuga.
Now that's a good
looking shithole.
- Hello?
- Hey, baby, how you doing?
Baby, I'm worried about you.
You coming home?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Soon.
It's gonna be a long night,
though, so don't wait up for me.
Why don't you let
me come down there?
Because I don't want to be
distracted by you, that's why.
Well, if you're still there when I come
on duty in the morning, you will see me.
- I cannot wait. I cannot wait.
- So, how you doing?
It's all right. We got a couple of
the hostages out. Thanks a lot.
- No, no. How you doing?
- I'm doing okay. I'm doing all right.
Oh, I saw the Mayor on TV. He said you're
doing a great job. I saw you, too.
- You saw me on TV?
- Yeah.
- How'd I look?
- You looked good, baby. Real good.
- All right, listen. I got to go.
- All right. Hey.
- Keep your head down.
- All right, I will. Love you.
Come on.
So, are we clear about
the ground rules?
- There's no need to worry, Detective.
- I get paid to worry, okay?
I just need you to
look me in the eye
and make me believe that you
understand everything we talked about.
- I understand.
- Okay.
Someone here wants
to talk to you.
- Hello?
- Who is this?
Let's not get into any names.
- What matters is what I can offer you.
- And what's that?
Well, if I can be assured that
certain interests are protected,
I might be able to help you
get what you came for.
I doubt that.
Tell me about these interests
that you are trying to protect.
Why don't you let me
worry about that?
Now, what is it you were
hoping to get out of all this?
- Rich, of course.
- Of course.
But you may have bitten off
more than you can chew.
- How?
- I can't discuss that on the phone.
- You work for the bank?
- No.
And you're not a cop.
That's right.
Come on in.
You got 10 minutes. No more.
If you're not out before
the lights come back on,
you can stay inside until
this thing is over.
- You don't need to threaten me.
- That's not a threat, lady, but this is.
I know this game is a mile over my head, but
I'm telling you, if you fuck me over...
I got where I am by collecting
friends, not enemies.
Trust me, okay?
You're on your own.
What makes you
think I need help?
Well, the hundred
people outside, for starters.
It's not a problem.
And they're fueling your
jet right now as we speak.
Come on. You're not that stupid.
Here's what I'm thinking.
If you give up now, I can ensure
that you'll serve the minimum.
I'm thinking three years,
four years at the most.
You can arrange that?
Well, you haven't hurt
anyone or stolen anything,
so yes, as a matter
of fact, I can.
- It's not good enough.
- Well, I wasn't finished.
When you get out,
you'll have $2 million.
Will I? How?
We'll put it someplace safe and it'll
be waiting for you when you get out.
Thanks.
But no, thanks.
Oh, come on. I made you
such a sweet offer.
I really don't think you have
much in the way of alternatives.
Why don't you talk to me about these
interests that you're in here to protect?
- I'm afraid I can't.
- I can.
Let me tell you a story.
During World War ll, there was an American
working for a bank in Switzerland.
Now, I don't need to tell you
that this period in history
was rife with opportunity
for people of low morals.
People like this man.
He used his position with the Nazis to
enrich himself while all around him
people were being stripped
of everything they owned.
Then he used his blood
money to start a bank.
Now,
does this sound like it might
be the man you work for?
Or am I just whistling
Dixie out of my ass?
- I believe we understand each other.
- Good.
So, what the hell
can you do for me
since I clearly know more than you do,
and I've planned this to perfection?
Believe me, if I need to, I can
change your entire program.
So, the sooner that you
stop being my problem
and you start becoming my solution,
the better off you'll be.
- What is it you want?
- Two minutes.
The safety deposit box room. I
just need to go to one box.
Looking for this?
This could be very
embarrassing to your employer.
He should have destroyed
this a long time ago.
He didn't, so now it's mine.
Now, if the day ever comes where
I have to stand before a judge
and account for what I did here,
you and your boss will do
whatever it takes to help me.
You get out of here
with that envelope,
and we'll pay you
a lot of money.
I'll keep that in mind.
You're not gonna tell me how you're
planning to get out of here, are you?
I'm gonna walk right out the front door.
Anything else?
- How did you know about all this?
- Doesn't matter.
Fact is, all lies, all
evil deeds, they stink.
You can cover them up for a
while, but they don't go away.
- Murder will out?
- Precisely.
Well, I still don't get
what you're doing here.
Really?
Good.
So, we spoke.
Oh, no. You're gonna have
to give me more than that.
- Let me have this window, fellows.
- Yes, sir.
I told him that, well, since
he hadn't killed anyone,
it wasn't too late to surrender and
get off with a lighter sentence.
And?
And that was basically it.
You know, I don't
ordinarily get offended
the first time somebody treats me like
an idiot, but you are pushing it.
Now, I know you did not go in there to
tell this guy something he already knew.
Talk to me.
Look, Detective.
Our arrangement doesn't include me
giving you a detailed explanation.
I say it does, okay?
Okay, you don't own me.
This check-cashing thing, this coke
bust, I can face that on my own.
I know what I did and
what I didn't do.
- Talk to me.
- Off the record?
"Off the..." Everything about you
is off the record. Just talk to me.
- Well, I gave him an incentive.
- Okay.
- Did he go for it?
- No. But I'd say he's considering it.
He's smart, isn't he?
- He thinks he is.
- Yeah.
One of your types, like
the lvy League type?
- Clearly well educated.
- That's what I'm talking about.
That's exactly what
I'm talking about.
You talk like him, so think like him.
What do you think he's gonna do?
- Well, he's not gonna kill anyone.
- How do you know?
- Because he's not a murderer.
I got news for you. Most of
the guys up in Sing Sing
weren't murderers until
they killed somebody.
You never know what a person will do
until you push him into a corner.
But it doesn't seem like you've
pushed him into a corner.
It doesn't, does it? Seems
more like he chose the corner.
You're right.
So, you through?
- I guess. Are you saying I'm dismissed?
- Yes, I am.
You got a card, in case
I need to call you?
Please don't take this
personally, but no.
I don't think you can afford me.
Well, don't take this personally,
Miss White. Kiss my black ass, okay?
Careful, Detective Frazier. My
bite's much worse than my bark.
- So, how old are you, Brian?
- Eight and three-quarters.
Eight and three-quarters.
Big boy.
- Were you scared in there?
- No.
- No? Not at all, huh?
- Nope. I'm from Brooklyn.
You're from Brooklyn, huh?
I understand.
- Guns don't scare me.
- They don't scare you?
- Brave, too, huh?
- Yeah.
So the guys that had the guns, do
you remember them saying anything?
- Yeah.
- What'd they say?
They asked me about my game.
- Who did?
- The guy that robbed the bank. Duh.
Son, be respectful.
Okay, Brooklyn. But it...
Was he the one in charge?
Uh-huh.
Okay.
And you don't remember
anything else?
He was kind of tall.
He had a mask.
Brian, you think you can recognize
him in any of these pictures?
Take your time.
Have a good look.
Let's keep that over there.
Just take a look.
- With the mask, they look all the same.
- It's true.
With the mask, they all look the same.
That's right, Brian.
Attempted robbery. Liquor store.
Well, this was a real step up for
a small-timer like you, huh?
I got to hand it to you, Pablo.
First of all, it's Paul.
Not Pablo, okay?
Excuse me.
- You want some gum?
- No.
And second, I didn't
do it, all right?
What? I made a few
mistakes when I was a kid.
I was out with some friends and
they held up a liquor store.
What was I supposed to do?
Where'd you grow up, you
Wassa Wassa, Park Avenue?
- What's that? Wassa what? What'd you say?
- Wassa Wassa.
You know, a person that don't
come to your neighborhood.
How do you say "Rikers
Island" in Spanish?
What about these two?
That ring a bell?
These two? No.
- Nothing?
- Nothing.
Don't they look
suspicious to you?
I mean, I would think that you
would want to know who they are.
No.
- Well, thank you very much.
- Thank you.
Hey, just out of curiosity do you
know anything about diamonds?
A bit. What do you need?
What do you think a guy like me
should pay for a diamond ring?
Depends. How many carats?
If you'd like, I could give
you my nephew's number.
- Okay.
- You'll get a very good deal.
What do you have on underneath?
- Excuse me?
- Underneath your painter's coat?
- What do you have on underneath?
- Clothing.
Could you show us, please?
You see, there's just
you and one other woman
that fit the physical description
of the female suspect.
What's that?
It's your height,
your age, and your...
Your cup size.
So, I violated
Section 34 double-D?
That's what you're telling me?
How dumb do these morons have to be
to think they're gonna get a plane?
This guy's no moron.
I don't just mean him.
Any hostage taker.
Those ragheads at the
Munich Olympics.
Who the fuck ever got a plane?
Shit, and these days? This
guy doesn't know that?
The area is flooded
with law enforcement right now.
Snipers are on rooftops...
What you doing there, Keith?
He wants a plane. I'm
gonna give him a plane.
- What happened to playing it by the book?
- That's what's bugging me.
It's like the other team read the book, too,
and they know exactly what we're gonna do.
This whole time, we're
trying to stall him, right?
Wrong. They're the ones
that are stalling.
Think about it. The bullshit
questions, the Albanian thing...
So, you're saying he what?
I'm saying that he wants to give
us more time. He makes demands.
He gives us deadlines. We stall.
Then he gives us more time.
I don't think he's in a rush.
- Why?
- That's what I'm gonna find out.
- Yeah.
- Your plane is ready.
Is that a faсt?
That's a fact, but I'm gonna
need something from you first.
I'm gonna need to come in there and
make sure the hostages are okay.
You'll see them when
they get on the bus.
I just need to make sure you're
not leaving any bodies behind.
Meet me at the front door.
- What the hell just happened?
- You got to be crazy to go in there.
Down the stairs.
- Gum?
- Excuse me?
- Would you like some gum?
- No, thank you.
Let me take the kid.
No.
Any more?
There are some who misbehaved.
Please help me!
Please help us!
Please help us! Please!
We're gonna get you
all out of here.
I promise you.
Tour is over.
- Can I ask you a question?
- There is nothing to talk about.
What were you planning on doing
if you actually got the
plane and the pilots, huh?
- Excuse me?
- You don't want a plane. You never did.
Who ever heard of bank robbers
escaping on a plane with 50 hostages?
You saw Dog Day Afternoon. You're stalling.
Why? I don't know.
What's the matter? You
can't get into the safe?
Perhaps.
There's two ways out of this.
The easy way, we walk out the front door
together, or the hard boys cut the power,
hit you with the tear gas, and
come in strong through the glass.
It's your choice. You don't want that.
I don't want that.
And, you know, they'd
like to do it tonight.
You got night vision?
- You got gas masks?
- Maybe.
- I'm this close to ordering it.
- Let's cut the crap.
First, you don't order an assault
when no hostages have been killed
and there's no immediate threat.
Second, if it ends that
way, whatever happens,
you don't get to be the hero.
You want to bullshit
me, try harder.
Let's go.
Okay.
I tell you what. My ass
is covered, sport.
But I would not get too comfortable
in here if I were you.
No? I got the cable guy
coming on Wednesday.
- Why don't you just walk out the door?
- I will.
I'm gonna walk out of that
door when I'm good and ready.
Can I get you to do that today?
I didn't think so.
Any other proposals?
Oh, please. Do not
say "proposals."
My girlfriend, she wants
a proposal from me.
- You think you're too young to get married?
- No, I'm not too young. Too broke.
Maybe I should rob a bank.
You love each other?
Yeah. Yeah, we do.
Then money shouldn't
really matter.
Thank you, bank robber.
I'm just saying money
can't buy love.
Thank you very much. I'm...
I'm learning so much
today, you know?
Look, why don't we go across the
street to the Killarney Rose, huh?
Forget about this dangerous
hostage situation.
- I'll buy you a beer. My treat.
- Thanks, Detective,
but I'm trying to stay away from
bars, if you know what I mean.
Well, if you change your mind there's
still a standing offer, all right?
Cellblock or the graveyard?
Prison whites or a toe tag?
- Make up your mind. Tick tock, tick tock.
- Hey! Hey!
We done?
You just crossed
the fucking line!
Buses, Kojak, parked outside.
You think I'm bluffing?
You roll the dice and
see what happens.
All right.
Now get the bunker up.
- So, what's up?
- Got him right where I want him.
Yeah? Where's that?
Right behind me with my pants
around my ankles, but it's a start.
Jesus Christ.
- What the fuck, man?
- How long?
- He got the drop on you!
- Two.
- How long?
- What if he saw your face?
- Two.
- What if I didn't have my gun?
Two, maybe three hours.
You know, you're letting this
cop get too fucking close.
What happened?
I gave him every excuse
to blow my brains out.
Yeah.
He doesn't bite. Why?
He ain't the type.
Let's just step back and think
about this for a second.
We know that they planned this whole thing.
The tape, the cameras, the costumes.
There was a game plan, but
it never included airplanes.
He's up to something
but it ain't violence.
- I'm listening.
- How's the reception?
- Excuse me?
- The camera on the truck.
Give me a close-up on the
second-floor window.
- Rourke?
- I'm on it, I'm on it.
No, no, no, no, no, no! Fuck!
Oh, shit.
Keith! Keith! Keith!
What are you doing? What
the fuck are you doing?
You mean beyond the obvious?
That's what I mean. Come on,
this ain't no bank robbery!
This is your fault. I told
you to get the buses.
Fuck you! I didn't kill anybody.
I got 50 more people in here.
You fuck with me again,
I'll give you two of the
longest days of your life.
All right, look, just tell me what it is
you really want and I'll get it for you.
- I promise.
- I've told you. Two buses, a plane.
Right, right. And box seats behind
home plate at Yankee Stadium.
Come on, don't bullshit
a bullshitter.
You planned every inch of this
thing right from the start.
You got everybody marching to your beat,
including me, and I'm through buying it.
You're too damn
smart to be a cop.
Now get the fuck out of here.
What? You going to shoot me?
Do it. Shit, you got
nothing to lose.
I damn sure ain't got nothing
to lose, so shoot me.
Do it.
- Shoot me.
- Fuck you.
Tell them to send
someone sane over here.
We got a big problem.
Hey, Detective, this
ain't your day.
How you doing, Captain?
Look, I know you put your
trust in me and I just...
Well, you're a good cop.
Frazier, I need more like you.
But if you're going down on
this one, I can't go with you.
You got to understand
this, though, sir...
No, no, no. Let me just tell
you what my problem is, okay?
I go to bed,
everything's hunky-dory.
I get a call at 3:15, and there's what?
A dead hostage.
- Right, right, right. But I can end this...
- Lt is ended.
See, you think I got options.
I got to answer to
the Chief of D's.
Darius is calling the shots on this.
That's it.
Hey, Sarge.
- What'd he say?
- That's it.
Shit.
- It's a tactical nightmare.
- I know.
Well, first, this
is the only way in.
Then we got to make it
up the stairs blind.
Once we get up there, we're
right out in the open.
They have the advantage of cover.
They can pick us off like sitting ducks.
Then if we make it across the
floor and down the stairs,
we still can't tell the homies from
the good guys until they shoot at us.
Even if it isn't rigged with explosives,
it's still a fucking nightmare.
Move! Move! Move!
Open the door!
- Keep moving.
- To the right.
Watch the hands,
watch the hands.
And let's not forget the possibility
of hostages being killed.
Right now! Put the gun down!
Back off or I shoot!
I said back off!
Well, our best hope is to
separate them from the hostages.
If we can get two or three
upstairs and take them out?
Kill them?
Gun! Gun! Gun!
What if there's more than four?
Yeah, well, that's what's so nuts about it.
Anybody in a painter's suit could be a perp.
Maybe we should dress our guys
up like a bunch of painters.
And we should use rubber bullets. Take
head shots. Put their lights out.
- Not a bad idea.
- Yeah.
Rubber bullets it is, baby.
If this goes down wrong,
they're going to dump this whole
mess in your lap, you know?
- I'm making First Grade.
- What?
I'm making Detective First Grade.
Things ain't all they appear to be.
- What the fuck does that mean?
- Deteсtive First Grade Keith Frazier.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- Yes.
Thank the Mayor and our
mystery guest for that.
You cut a deal with those guys?
Never make First Grade? Shit.
Worked too hard to
let that happen.
Everybody's getting theirs.
I'm gonna get mine.
I'll be outside.
What a day, what a day.
Detective, they're gonna storm that
bank without you? It's not right.
So, tell me about the kid who pointed
the gun at you, the 12-year-old.
- Now?
- Yeah.
Last year, up in the 33rd,
I was breaking up a fight about a
half a block from the high school.
This one little spic is getting
his clock cleaned by another one.
Do me a favor, Sergeant. Just
tone down the color commentary.
So I bust up the fight,
I turn around and this kid is
pointing a .22 at my chest.
- Is that right? Now, which kid was this?
- Another kid, an African-American.
- An African-American, right?
- Yeah.
Came out of nowhere.
I didn't see him.
So, what'd you do?
What did I do then? I'll
tell you what I did then.
I got shot in the fucking chest.
That's what I did then.
Yeah, so you'll pardon my
euphemisms, Detective,
but I would rather wind up an old
bigot than a handsome young corpse.
Now, no offense, Detective,
but I'm just trying to
keep them away from us.
Now, what do you say we just get
these people safely out of the bank?
I hear that.
And I'll try and watch
what I say in the future.
You never know who's listening.
What are you doing?
Jesus. Shit.
They bugged us.
Darius!
Darius, don't make a move!
- What?
- It's all fucked up!
Do not make a move!
Keep your men back!
What are you talking about?
They heard everything
we said in the M.C.C.
- What?
- Stand down! Stand down!
The drawer with the demands in it!
They heard everything we said!
They put a transmitter in it!
They bugged us!
No, no, no. I'm going in.
Shit.
Get everyone together.
Steve! Steve-O!
They're coming in.
- Everybody good?
- Yeah.
All right! Everybody out!
- Put your masks on!
- Everyone out! Out!
- Go now!
- Go!
Go! Go! Go!
- Now!
- Get the fuck out!
Move!
Everybody up the
fucking stairs! Move!
Move!
- Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
- Don't shoot!
- Get down! Get down on the ground!
Cease fire!
Cease fire! Cease fire!
Let's go, people.
Put your hands on your head!
Get down!
Put your hands on your head.
- Will somebody stop him?
- Get down!
Put your hands on your head.
- Put your hands on your head.
- Get them down!
- On the ground!
- Put your hands on your fucking heads!
Do not move!
- Get down, put your hands on your head!
- Put the cuffs on them! Let's go!
What's going on?
Don't take any chances!
It wasn't me! I'm
not a criminal!
Cuffs!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
- Don't move!
- I'm not moving!
- Do not move!
Check them. Make sure they ain't
got no weapons on them and shit.
- Hernandez!
- Right here.
E.S.U.
Team, line up!
Door to the left,
door to the left.
- Clear on the right.
- Clear!
- Left side clear.
- Clear.
- All clear!
- Check under the desk.
- Clear.
- Checking the office. All clear, Sarge.
Clear.
All clear, Sarge.
All clear. E.S.U.
On the stairs. Line it up!
Let's go, guys.
Team in, team in. Let's go.
Clear!
- Clear.
Clear.
- Clear, Sarge.
- Clear.
Give me a bunker up here.
I need a bunker up front.
Bringing the bunker up.
Clear, Sarge.
Clear.
- We're almost clear down here.
- Make sure you're sure.
- I'll keep looking.
- Stay on it.
Roger that.
Ready? Let's go.
This is the last door.
- Clear, Sarge!
- Come on down.
- Did you find a dead hostage?
- Negative.
If it ain't here, you
must've missed something.
Maybe, but I'm pretty sure we're the
only ones moving around down here.
Check this out. They
forgot to rob the joint.
- Holy shit.
- And you didn't find anybody?
We're still looking, but
there are no bad guys,
no booby traps, no
tunnels, no damage.
- And nothing missing.
- Great, great, great.
We'll put out a city-wide description for
David fucking Copperfield, then, huh?
Listen, I'm not trying to tell
you your jobs, Detectives,
but unless they swam out
through the toilets,
whoever did this is
upstairs sucking pavement.
All right, good job.
What's that?
Cell phones.
- Hey, guys! You need to see this.
- Okay.
Collins! Grab a uniform, make a quick
count of that money in there, all right?
- Yes, sir.
- And stand by, all right?
Don't let anybody get
tempted, including you!
Yes, sir!
Right here, Detective.
- What do you got?
- You're going to love this one. Toy guns.
Fake guns. You got
to be kidding me.
- Toys.
- As if it wasn't weird enough already.
Cap, come to the ladies' room.
On my way.
Check it out.
We can stop looking
for that body.
Fake guns.
Fake execution.
Nobody goes home till we
get everybody's story.
Cap, we got something
else in the storage room.
- Porcario?
- Yo.
- Where's the men's room?
- Down the hallway on the left.
Pick them up, pick them up.
Toss them.
I'm a hostage.
Stop pushing.
Female hostages to be
searched by female officers only!
All right, listen,
let's get these people up.
- I can't hear you. What?
- Valerie Keepsake.
Valerie Keepsake. Go,
go, get on the bus.
- Kenneth Damerjian.
- Yeah.
Person one.
- I'm Peter Hammond.
- Eric Dodge.
- Wait!
- Chaim. My name's Chaim.
Fucking cocksucker.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Just give me your name.
Say your name.
I work in the bank!
I'm the bank security guard!
Nobody's listening!
Okay, we'll straighten it out.
Everybody's saying listen!
Nobody's listening!
We'll straighten it out.
Come on.
- Listen, I'm not getting on the bus!
- Yes, you are.
- Move! Move! Move!
- I am not! I work at the bank!
Collins, you got this?
Listen, I work at the bank!
All right, just get him
on the bus. Get him on the bus.
- Nobody's listening!
- All right. Calm down. Get on the bus.
- Come on, guys, guys!
- Over this way. Over this way.
Officer, take her over to Sarge.
Come on.
Come on, let's get going with
these people off that line over there.
Come on.
Captain, I'm telling you,
this thing is a mess.
They thought this one
out, soup to nuts.
So, lay it out for me.
We photograph everybody
that came out of the bank.
We sit them down, we question
them, we show them the photos.
Most of them can't point to anybody
that's guilty of anything.
We ask them if they could recognize
anybody who was not one of the bad guys.
Even if we considered someone
as a possible suspect,
there's one or two or three other
people that would rule them out.
It's like the thing
never happened.
- What about prints?
- Everywhere. So what?
- All it shows is that these people were there.
- Alibis?
Just about everyone.
Even if their alibi was weak,
a hostage would identify them
as being one of the good guys.
There we are, back
to square one.
Priors?
We got one employee who had some
juvie stuff. One customer had...
Excuse me.
One customer had an out-of-state
warrant for child support.
Another one had a couple of priors, G.
L.A. mostly.
Again, same problem. Plus,
he was a fucking idiot.
- Bank cameras?
- Useless.
I'm telling you, they thought
of everything. Almost.
- Sounded like everything to me.
- But this.
We haven't found that .357 or
the perp that was holding it.
If you did, there'd be
no prints on it anyway.
- Bury it.
- Bury it?
What the fuck do you
expect me to say?
Captain, this thing stinks to high hell.
I mean, somebody did something here.
You said it yourself.
You got no robbery. No suspects.
Nobody's breathing down my
neck to come up with answers.
I'm not gonna breathe down yours.
Bury it.
I wasn't expecting this.
I promise you, I'll find you
guys more cases to solve.
Okay.
Oh, here's something that
you probably did expect.
- They found that missing Madrugada money.
- No shit.
Yes, you want to
know where it was?
- In my bank account?
- No.
- My summer house in Sag Harbor?
- My wallet?
- No.
Then, no. I don't want to know.
This is bullshit, man.
I mean, we're the only ones left
trying to catch the bad guys
and they're gonna come
after us like that?
I'll tell you what. Every
one of your accusers, man,
I say we go after them all,
Keith, Michael Corleone style.
"Michael Corleone, do
you renounce Satan?"
"Yes, I renounce him."
There's no 392.
- Huh?
- Safety deposit box number 392.
According to these
records, it doesn't exist.
Pinstriped, mayonnaise,
lying motherfucker.
- Didn't Coughlin say we should move on?
- Let's go.
Thank you, again, Your Honor.
I'll come pick it up tomorrow?
- Yes, you're welcome.
- Thank you.
What are you doing, Detective?
Now, what business do you
have with Judge Pasqua?
Police business.
- Weren't you told to bury this?
- I got a job to do, Miss White.
And since when is your job more
important than your career?
- Or did you forget our arrangement?
- We didn't have any arrangement.
Let me tell you how this works.
You...
No, let me tell you
how this works.
You press here to record and
you press here to play.
There's also the matter of the $140,000
that seems to have walked away
from the Madrugada
check-cashing bust.
I didn't have anything
to do with that, so...
We'd like to be
in your corner on that.
In exchange for what?
I mean, what, do you want me
to do something unethical?
I mean, no disrespect
to the both of youse
but I don't need you to be
in my corner, Mr. Mayor.
Look, I'm innocent.
Innocent or guilty,
you're still going down.
Give Miss White whatever she
needs, or your career is over.
Done.
Kaput.
So? You gave me what I wanted.
Your career is blossoming and
all is right with the world.
What was Case hiding?
You know, there's a famous saying
by the Baron de Rothschild.
"When there's blood on the
streets, buy property."
I think Mr. Case really took
that sentiment to heart.
But he is no different
than half the Fortune 500.
Let it go, Detective.
You're a good cop.
This city needs you.
- Lady! Lady, you're in the wrong place.
- I have an appointment.
Arthur.
- Good morning.
- Miss White.
Have a seat.
Thank you, Vincent. That's all for now.
Thank you.
Well. What did he say?
Well, Detective Frazier
turned out to be quite sharp.
But I just fast-tracked his career
a little and he's under control.
I hope so. Tell me
about the envelope.
Where is it now?
Well, the gang leader is
going to hang on to it,
as an insurance policy to keep
you from seeking revenge.
Clearly, he has a very
low opinion of you.
And what might that be?
Well, let's see. In a
nutshell, that you got rich,
doing business with the
Nazis during the Holocaust.
Yes.
It was 60 years ago. I
was young and ambitious.
I saw a short path to
success and I took it.
I sold my soul.
And I've been trying to
buy it back ever since.
But you and this mystery man,
you have an understanding?
I think so. And he managed to get
out of there with that envelope.
If someday he comes back
to blackmail you, well,
you'll pay him. And
you'll get it back.
- So, I guess that's it.
- I suppose so.
- Bullshit.
- I beg your pardon?
He didn't go through all that just to
stick your envelope under his mattress.
Look, they left money
untouched, Arthur.
So?
So, he had to have walked out
of there with something else.
The bank says that there
was nothing missing.
So, there had to have been
something in that box
that was worth more to
him than your envelope.
You don't have to tell me.
There's only one thing
it could be anyway.
Diamonds.
And then there's the ring.
Cartier ring.
It belonged to the wife
of a Parisian banker.
Wealthy family of French Jews.
And when the war came along, the
ring and everything else they owned
was confiscated and they were shipped off
to concentration camps. None survived.
We were friends.
I could have helped them.
But the Nazis paid too well.
Can I trust that you will
keep what you've learned
here today confidential?
Despite whatever you may think?
Yes, Arthur.
Well, I'd love to tell you
what a monster you are,
but I have to help bin Laden's
nephew buy a co-op on Park Avenue.
If that were true, you
wouldn't tell me.
We're listing you
as a reference.
My name is Dalton Russell.
Pay strict attention
to what I say
because I choose my words carefully
and I never repeat myself.
I've told you my name.
That's the "who."
The "where" could most readily
be described as a prison cell.
But there is a vast difference
between being stuck in a tiny
cell and being in prison.
The "what" is easy.
Recently I planned and set in motion events
to execute the perfect bank robbery.
That's also the "when."
As for the "why," beyond the
obvious financial motivation,
it's exceedingly simple.
Because I can.
Which leaves us only
with the "how."
And therein, as the
Bard would tell us,
lies the rub.
- He's gonna smell like shit.
- What do you expect after a week?
Yeah.
Why do you think I
rolled down the window?
Oh, shit.
That cop, Frazier, and his partner
are walking into the bank.
- Are they coming for me?
- Can't say. It's just the two of them.
Yeah, everything's
going great today. No.
Yeah, about 5:30. Okay.
Sounds like fun. Okay.
Talk to you later.
- Sorry.
- Excuse me.
Mr. Hammond?
Good morning, Detectives.
Just like he planned.
I got a court order here to
open a safe deposit box.
Number 392.
Oh, thank God.
Where is it?
I left it in there.
This way, Detectives.
Why did you do that?
You left the ring.
Trust me.
I left it in good hands.
I'm no martyr.
I did it for the money.
But it's not worth much if you
can't face yourself in the mirror.
Respect is the
ultimate currency.
I was stealing from a man who
traded his away for a few dollars.
And then he tried to
wash away his guilt.
Drown it in a lifetime of good
deeds and a sea of respectability.
- Let me get that.
- Let me.
It almost worked, too.
Okay.
But inevitably,
the further you run
from your sins,
the more exhausted you are
when they catch up to you.
And they do.
Son of a bitch.
Certain.
It will not fail.
What do you think that's worth?
If you got to ask,
man, you can't afford it.
Thank goodness my
girlfriend ain't here.
"Follow the ring"?
- Deteсtive Frazier.
- Mr. Case.
- How are you?
- I am great.
Nobody got killed at the bank.
Everybody's happy. My kind of day.
That's wonderful. Wonderful.
- Deteсtive Mitchell.
- Mr. Case.
- Be seated, gentlemen.
- Thank you.
- Can I offer you anything?
- No.
I must say
I was most impressed
by the way you handled
that business.
Thank you, Mr. Case.
Whenever I hear the term
"New York's Finest"
you're who I think of.
You keep the rest of us
safe and make it look easy.
- Pardon me.
- Well, what's so amusing?
When you say "the rest of us," Mr.
Case, I mean, you got to look around.
"The rest of us" is a category that you
haven't qualified for in a long time.
Touché, Detective. I won't deny it.
I've done well.
Yes, you have. But
I'm very confused.
You see, I got a case
where armed robbers laid
siege to your bank.
It is your bank, right?
Well, I'm Chairman of
the Board of Directors.
Then...
The robbers disappear. Poof.
And they don't take
a nickel, right?
- You're asking me?
- Yes, I'm asking you.
I mean, it's your bank. You own it.
I'm asking you.
It's a tiny part of
our organization.
No robbers. No real viсtims.
No loot missing.
It's got to be the first time
in law-enforcement history.
I never heard of it before.
So, you got to ask yourself, "What the
fuck happened?" Don't you, Mr. Case?
I'm not quite sure I
like your tone, Officer.
You don't like my tone? Then
give me a straight answer.
It's the founding bank of your empire.
You built it. It's your baby.
Give me a straight answer.
What do you think happened?
- I have no idea.
- Oh, come on, now. Come on.
I'll tell you what
I think happened.
I think you sent that woman
in there to patch things up.
Miss White. I think you paid her.
What was she doing in there?
Look, this is absurd.
Are you implying that I had
anything to do with it?
392.
Safe deposit box 392.
What's the story on that?
- I have no idea what you're...
- Don't lie to me, Mr. Case.
- I don't lie.
- I looked at all the records.
All the bank records for safe
deposit boxes at your bank.
At first glance,
everything looked fine,
but there was one safe deposit
box that had no records.
I mean, going all the
way back to 1948.
So I started thinking. Who would
have the answer to this riddle?
Probably the man who
forgot to mention
that he built the bank in
the first place in 1948.
It doesn't add up, Mr. Case.
It does not add up.
I'm afraid I can't be of any
further use to you, Detective.
It's something really
bad, isn't it?
Mr. Frazier, I have spent my
whole life serving humanity.
You can ask anyone who knows me.
They'll vouch for me, and for
the things that I've done.
You think they'll vouch for you after
I find out the truth about this ring?
I don't think so.
Oh, by the way, that thing you said
about us being New York's finest?
I want you to know, we
really appreciate that.
How gracious.
Let's go. We're gonna
follow that ring.
- Hey, Keith, let me see your shoe.
- What?
- Let me see your shoe.
- Why?
'Cause I have never seen anybody put
their foot that far up a guy's ass.
Yeah, I guess I did, didn't I?
Oh, man. You cut him an ass the
length of the Lincoln Tunnel.
We're gonna need a traffic
cop on that shit.
Good afternoon, sir.
- Do you have a reservation?
- Looking for the Mayor.
- May I have your hat, please?
- No, you cannot. Get your own.
They're looking to invest
$4 billion over the next four years.
And that's all in place.
Sorry to interrupt you, Mr. Mayor,
but there's an old American saying,
"When there's blood on the streets,
somebody's got to go to jail."
Edwin, could you please
excuse us for a minute?
What's this about, Detective?
I believe Deteсtive Frazier
is looking for some closure?
That's a good word. Closure.
Case closed, you
know what I mean?
This is the number
of the War Crimes Issues
office in Washington, D.C.
How'd you like to be on the front
page of the New York Times?
That'd be great.
Make sure they spell my name right, though.
That's Frazier with a "z".
You can keep the pen.
You made copies?
Please.
We got to keep the real criminals
off the streets, Your Honor.
All right, well,
thanks for lunch.
War crimes, huh?
What have you got
me into this time?
Mama?
- Did you bring Big Willie?
- And the twins.
Slow down, girl.
I'll get my gun off before
I get my gun off, okay?
Pow, pow.
- Sorry.
- Excuse me.
Why don't you
just walk out the door?
I will.
I'm gonna walk out of that
door when I'm good and ready.
Son of a bitch.
Come on, honey.
The handcuffs are getting cold.