- Hi!
- Ok, Francois?
And you?
Stephane... Francois...
- Still on the team?
- As ready as ever.
Hello.
- This one?
- At the back, please.
Hi, I'm Herve.
A sports teacher here for 3 years.
Welcome to all our new colleagues.
The students can be tough...
but they're good kids.
Hi, I'm Olivier.
I teach physical science...
and I've been here for 4 years.
I'm Patrick,
and I teach multiplication tables,
and sometimes mathematics!
I've been at this school
for a number of years.
Hello, I'm Anne.
I used to work in the Lyon suburbs.
I teach English.
I'm looking for my new colleagues.
Hi, I'm Isabelle
Nice to meet you.
I'm Christiane.
I'm Frederic,
I teach history and geography.
and I used to work
out in suburbs of Paris.
I'm happy to be in the city now.
I'm Julie, the year supervisor.
I'd like to welcome you all
and wish you a good year.
I'm Aline and I'm the cook
I'd like to welcome you all.
Thank you, Aline!
Hello. I'm Gilles,
I've been teaching mathematics
for many years
I'm retiring at the end of this year
I'd like to wish the new arrivals
plenty of courage.
I'm Francois
I teach French.
And I'm starting
my fourth year here
Welcome everybody.
We'll meet up at midday...
in the canteen for a drink
to mark the new year.
You get Wednesday like you wanted!
We could swap our classes
Nice, nice...
Not nice, not nice at all.
He's nice.
Not nice, watch him.
Not nice at all.
Nice, not nice.
She's not nice at all.
Arthur, your cap.
Good morning.
That's my place.
Get lost!
Calm down now!
Stop stirring things up
Remove your hood, please
You two back there,
there's place here.
- One up front.
- There's room here too!
Let's get one thing clear...
We waste 5 minutes
lining outside,
5 coming up, 5 setting down:
15 minutes out of hour
Do you realize
what 15 lost minutes means?
With 25 hours a week
and 30 weeks in the year,
we lose thousands of minutes.
In other schools,
they do a full work.
Imagine how far ahead they get
in a year
Figure it out!
We never do an hour.
Hand up to speak.
We never do an hour
You always say that!
Teachers say we do an hours class
but we never do.
8.30 to 9.25 doesn't make an hour.
All right it's 55 minutes.
That’s an important point
Stop saying other schools do an hour
They don't!
All I'm saying is that
we waste time. Like now.
To start with,
take out a sheet of paper,
fold it in two so that it can stand
on the edge of your desk clearly
and using block capitals,
write your full name.
Why write our names?
To know who you are
- But you know us!
- We had you last year.
Esmeralda,
half of the kids here are new.
Be happy. That way
people will know your name
I'm not doing it
I won't if you don't
You're right
For those of you who don’t know me,
I'm Mr. Marin
- A marine?
- Very funny
Corny!
He wiped you out, sir
Come on, it shouldn’t take so long
Five minutes to write a name
It's ridiculous
A biscuit for the firs day?
I'm OK, thanks
Rachel, a biscuit will buck you up
All right. "Witty"
That's word
we'll try to explain later.
Are there any other words
that you don't understand?
The word "condescension"
Yes, that's a complicated word.
Do you have any idea
what that might mean?
A vague idea but I'm not sure
You're not sure?
We'll talk about that later then
- Yes, Damien
- "Argentine".
Argentine. What does that mean?
It's people who live in Argentina.
Right, the inhabitants of Argentina
Of course not
Damien, who lives in Argentina?
The Argentines
In a soccer match
Argentina's players
are called...
Footballers
Let's move on
Any other difficult words
in the text?
Henriette
Is there anything
that you didn't understand?
"Henceforth".
"Henceforth"
Thanks for the prompt, Samantha.
I think that will do,
Let's take a look at these words.
All right. Austrian
Wey was the one
who picked the word Austrian
Yes, Esmeralda.
We all know what "Austrian" is.
- People from Austria.
- Wey doesn't know and...
Maybe, but everyone else knows!
We get the message. You didn't
know "misleading"
...so you're not really
in any position to talk.
But everyone knows
what "Austrian" means.
Nobody's perfect.
- "Austrian" is not a very,
important word, Wey.
It refers to someone
from the land of Austria,
which is pretty tiny country.
We can live without the word.
Can anyone name a famous Austrian?
Mozart.
- Who?
- Wol Fang Amadeus Mozart.
- "Wol Fung" maybe if he
were English, not Austrian.
Any other famous Austrians?
Austria could vanish
no one would notice.
Seriously, it's south of Germany.
So check a map, Wey,
You'll see where it is.
Souleymane,
...can you note the words too?
I forgot my things.
No one can land you some paper...
I'll do it at home.
You'll do it at home. Sure you will.
That's your approach
Only work at home.
I'm serious!
If I could be sure of that...
Don't worry. It'll be ok
Let's move on to "succulent".
"Succulent" is a word that we'll try
to guess the meaning of.
What's is "succulent"?
Suck
Suck off.
Very funny, Boubacar.
Very witty indeed,
Here's a sentence...
...with "succulent".
"Bill enjoys a succulent...
...cheeseburger. "
Cheeseburgers stink!
- Who said that?
- Me.
Why "cheeseburger"?
Well, since you say that, you
think cheeseburgers aren't succulent.
Maybe, but they're crap.
OK, but what I just said
should have made the penny drop.
- What does that mean?
- Mean what?
The penny thing...
To make the penny drop,
No one knows the expression?
If the penny drops,
it means you understand.
When I say,
if cheeseburger stink
they're not succulent,
that should help you see
what "succulent" means.
- What's with the Bills?
- What bills?
The name Bill.
You always use weird names.
Weird? A recent US President
was called Bill.
Why don't you use Aissata
or Rachid or Ahmed...
You always use whitey names.
What names?
- Honky names.
- What's honky?
Honkies, Frenchies, frogs.
You're not French?
No, I'm not French.
I didn't know.
I am, but not proud of it.
Fine, I'm not either
Why use these names?
Khoumba, if I start choosing names
to suit all your origins, it'll
never end.
Just change a little!
What do you suggest?
Aissata! Fatou, no!
- No, Aissata.
- Aissata, Aissata!
Excuse me. You have class 4/3
in French?
I'm class supervisor too.
Know what book you'll be reading?
No, I haven't decided.
In history I'll start with
Ancien Regime
If you want to link into that,
what kind of books are there?
The Enlightenment will
be tough for them.
How about Voltaire? Is he tough?
He's not easy.
Candide, is simple...
Not in their year
Zadig...
Yes, but it'd be tough
You have 20 seconds.
No, we've not finished yet!
We've not finished yet!
We can't spend 2 hours on the
imperfect.
Dalla, I can give you the time.
Sir, my pen keeps leaking!
- It's crap
- Who has a handkerchief?
Me!
Rabah!
Ask before you stand.
- May I?
- Yes.
- Gently, Ok...
- The perv!
He touched her tits!
Just give him the handkerchief.
Spare us your comments.
God dam pedophile!
- Quiet!
- Sir?
Why the imperfect indicative?
Cut it out!
- Why not just imperfect?
- Quiet, Souleymane.
All right, Esmeralda,
why the indicative?
If I knew, I wouldn't ask.
I can imagine. Anyone know why we
specify the imperfect indicative?
Why not just the imperfect?
Nassim?
May I wash my hands?
Go on, wash them and get it over with.
Make it quick.
He'll take a week!
- I'll go with him.
- Enough
The imperfect indicative is
different than another imperfect
Which imperfect is that?
Agam?
- The imperfect subjunctive.
Exactly.
The Imperfect subjunctive.
Can anyone give me an example?
I don't believe it, Khoumba,
but go on.
I may be wrong...
I think so too.
- I were
- I were.
From the verb "to werr"
- I don't know...
- I wuz.
I were, we were, you were
All right. Not bad but you use it
wrongly.
You vaguely recall
the imperfect subjunctive.
Imagine I say:
"He insist...
"that I be... "
Let's say "in shape".
"He insists that I be in shape"
What is "be" in that example?
The present subjunctive.
Very good. For the imperfect
subjunctive,
we follow the sequence of tenses
and use a past:
"He insisted... "
- "He insisted that I... "
Khoumba?
- Were.
- Were. Yes.
You really think I'll tell my mom:
"He insisted that I were'd been in shape?
Not I were'd been.
Learn to use it first
"That I were in shape"
- The sequence of tenses.
- No one says that.
I was right!
"I were".
Will you let me answer the question?
If you care.
- You may.
- Before mastering something,
the imperfect subjunctive,
you're telling me it's no use.
Start by mastering it,
then you can call its use into question.
Sir, why are you criticizing us?
They're right, that's the way
people talked in the old days.
Even my gran didn't say that.
Or your great granddad
It's from the Middle Ages!
No it isn't.
It is!
It's bourgeois...
Tell me, when was the last time
you heard someone talk like that?
Yesterday, with friends,
we used the imperfect subjunctive.
No, someone normal!
All right, all right.
The people on the streets...
Can I reply?
Yep.
I'll talk this over, but calmly.
All right, not everyone talks that way.
In fact, people who do are pretty rare.
I'd even say only snobs...
...use the imperfect subjunctive.
What's a snob?
Snobs are slightly affected,
slightly precious people
who tend to put on airs.
Homosexuals?
No, not homosexuals...
You can be affected and refined
without being homosexual.
In any case,
this register may seem
formal and a bit affected,
and even bourgeois.
But these different registers exist
...as I keep telling you,
...you need to be able to use them
...Familiar, current, formal,
oral and written.
Move between them
and use them all. Yes, Lucie?
How do we know what's written
and what's for oral?
Why is a word more one for one register?
Normally, that's something
that you pick up as you go along
You need to use intuition.
What's this?
Intuition is when you can't use thinking
When you can't really...
It's not knowing
but more like sensing something.
When you sense things
What if you don't sense?
If you don't sense them, well…
You gain intuition
by using the language.
That's when you learn to distinguish...
almost automatically
between oral and written styles.
- Souleymane wants to say something.
- Shut it.
What does he want to say?
Go on!
Calm down
Cut it out. No fighting
- I'll whop you
- Don't act tough!
What's wrong? Boubacar, turn around.
- What is it?
- Nothing
- Apparently not.
- Don't send him to the principal.
If I tell you,
I'm good for Guantanamo.
Guantanamo! Guantanamo!
I'll be tased!
You won't be tased.
- You have a question?
- Yep
So ask it
- It's too wicked
- It's not
It's the pits for you
- Just ask it
- I have your word?
- Hurry up
This is what I heard, ok?
I didn't say it but I heard...
People say you like men.
I didn't say it!
- Who says that?
- Just people
They say Mr. Marin likes men"
Others say that, not you?
- You not interested?
- No way
- So why do you ask?
- For the others.
I'm spokesman
- But you don't care?
- If you like men, fine
- So is it true?
- You are asking me.
Homosexual isn’t an insult, sir.
You say it isn't but it seems
to be a problem for you.
You find it odd, men liking men.
Maybe it is, I don't know
It is true or not?
No, it's not. Feel better now?
Yeah? Sure.
Sorry to disappoint you.
All right, if Souleymane doesn't mind
now he's settle his hang-ups,
let's get back
to the imperfect indicative.
Yeah, like that! Not bad
- What are you doing?
- Stop.
- What's up?
- Get lost
Who asked you? Look at your mug
- It's fucking ok!
Take these jerks,
then we'll see
Go on, show me your backs
- These guys suck.
- Another one.
- Classy display
- You bet
- Got one for me?
- Can't afford it
- How much?
- Too much!
Stop thinking I'm broke like you!
She screwed up there
She thinks it's regular verb
No the verb's swim. Swimmed.
Justine! "Swimmed"!
Justine, work it out yourself
Swummed. That's better,
it mixes the two.
Swammed!
She put swemmed
- Ok, thank you
- Try swommed
You can sit down
Let's see.
Let's see
She can’t write
She can’t write? Can you, Rabah?
- You bet
- Go on then
Conjugate it properly
- Swummed
- No
Continue.
Swammed
Wrong again
Just kidding
- It’s not like that
- So what is it?
Without an I
Right, no I
Why make fun of Justine,
when you can’t do better?
Justine wasn’t so wrong
That’s enough
You cant focus for more
than 20 seconds
like 3 year olds
People aged 14 or 15
like you’re supposed to be
If I ask a question
they should know
Your kidding around goes too far!
Not at all
- Everyone thinks so
- Dead right
Everyone thinks so
or only you think so?
No, everyone!
I think you push it.
If I cut you some slack,
you'll never get anywhere
You go too far!
And you know why
I’m sick of these clowns!
Sick of them!
I can’t take any more
They’re nothing,
they know nothing...
they look right through you
when you try to teach them
They cat stay in their shit
I’m not going to help them
They’re so basic, so insincere
...always looking for trouble
Go ahead, guys
...Stay in your crap neighborhood
You’ll be here all yours lives
and it serves you right
Ill see the principal and tell him
I’m not working with 3/2 again.
No more technology
for the rest of the year. Too bad
It’s been three months now and
they haven’t done a single thing
Have you seen them in the yard?
It’s like they’re in heat
They’re all over each other,
like animals
It’s crazy. It’s the same in class
Kevin spent a whole hour doing
I’ve never seen the like
of it in 5 years!
Enough, no more!
We’re not animals!
Sorry I’m…
It’s dumb.
Come on. Let's get some air
One extract isn’t a lot to read
No one did it?
We’re wasting time here
Let’s read it again then
Who wants to read?
Great! Excellent work
atmosphere today.
Khoumba, go on.
No way.
You won’t read?
I don’t want to
The class revolves
around your desires?
- I don’t want to read
- Don’t care
What did Khoumba just do?
- Wey?
- Sneer
I meant her attitude,
What did she show?
Insolence.
That’s right, you’re an expert
You’re all angrulo with me
What is this?
- That’s not true
Try saying it in French. What am I?
Angrulo
Say it in everyday French
- You’ve got it in for me
- That’s normal French
I just want you to read
I have the right to ask you
to read, don’t I?
Don’t you think so?
- No.
No one has read it
and you’re picking on me.
I’m not. I want to work
and I’ve chosen you
as I have the rights to.
Drop it.
Shut up and start reading
I won’t read
You tell me to shut up,
then to read. What is this?
What’s what?
Make your mind up,
Think it through
Well talk it over after class
It won’t be fun
- Sure
You won’t say that later
Esmeralda, are you on strike too
or can you read for us?
It’s her life
In that case, will you read for us?
I'd be delighted to
All right, were listening
"Dear Kitty
I’m known as a bundle
of contradictions.
"As I’ve told you several times...
..."my soul is split in two
"my mocking approach to
everything, my joy in life,
..."On one side
my exuberant cheerfulness
..."and my ability
to take things lightly
"By that I mean not seeing
any wrong in flirting...
..."giving a kiss, embracing someone,
..."or telling a tasteless joke
"That side lies in wait
pushing back the other side...
..." which is more beautiful,
purer and deeper.
"The truth is that no one knows,
..."Anne's better side...
..."and that's why most people...
..."can't stand me.
"I can be an amusing clown
for an afternoon
..."but then everyone
"has had enough of me,
..."So the nice Anne has never once,
..."been seen in company
"But, in her loneliness,
she always triumphs.
"My best to you. Anne Franck.
Anne's diary ends here
It ends here. Why?
Because the police turned up
at the rooms
...where they were hiding
and deported them.
She died shortly after
...That's what I asked earlier
We talked about it.
I learn about Anne Frank
because she talks about herself
and so I get to know her.
When I ask you to write
your own self-portraits,
...I'll expect the same.
...In other words, to learn things
through your feelings,
...You can talk about facts...
...that will allow
me to know you better.
Yes, Lucie?
What we write
won't be as gripping as...
as what Anne Franck wrote
Our lives aren't as gripping.
- All right
Juliette?
Someone aged 70
could talk about their life,
...but we have nothing to tell at 13,
At 14, 15 or even 13
you've had experiences
- Less then someone aged 70
They’ve live a lot more.
- OK
- They’ve seen life.
It’s funny. You don’t think
your lives are interesting.
We just come to school, go home,
eat and sleep.
You come to school, eat, sleep, fine
The bare facts of your life are dull
But what you feel is interesting
- That’s my business
Maybe, but I’m interested
That’s different
Why is it different?
Because you're a teacher.
It’s not the teacher talking.
- It’s the human being
- It’s your job
I think you’re only saying that
to get us to talk and stuff
...but its not true.
It isn’t? What isn’t true?
The fact that you’re interested
in knowing all that
So I’m not interested at all
...and I’m pushing at this
...to convince you its interesting?
Not as much as you say
Maybe I am exaggerating a little.
It’s only natural since
you don’t agree with me
But, deep down, I’m totally sincere
Why it is such a problem for you
...to talk about your lives?
Boubacar.
Well there stuff...
There’s private stuff.
Of course
What could be hard to say
about your private lives?
Burak.
- We may be ashamed
to say certain things
Yes, it has to do with shame.
Things you find it hard to say
and even harder to write.
On your life, when were you ashamed?
You can be ashamed of pal's mom...
Why? Because you find her ugly?
No. For instance, Rabah's mom,
She offered me lunch but I refused
because I was ashamed
Ashamed to eat with her?
Because it’s beneath you?
- No.
I don’t understand, Tell me why.
I’m ashamed to eat with her
because I respect her.
You never eat with people who
you respect?
I mean, she’s not my girlfriend!
You can only eat with
a girlfriend...
Tell me why. I’m interested
I can’t explain it.
In any case, I’m ashamed
I always hang out with Rabah
so I respect his mom
I don’t eat in front of her
So if Boubacar eats in front of us
he doesn’t respects us
No, it’s not that!
- You can’t understand.
- I’m not smart enough?
You just can’t understand.
Rabah?
I was at a party with Camemberters
Camemberters?
Yeah, like you
What's a Camemberter?
Someone who stinks of cheese
So the people at the party
stank of cheese?
They were all in suits and ties.
I was in my baggies and
got these weird looks
You were ashamed?
Because of the looks
They were embarrassed because of you
...and you felt the same
They weren’t embarrassed
They looked at me
like I was an E.T.
You are an E.T.!
"Why’s that Arab here?"
Ok, so it was a race thing
I don’t know
But the snacks were bacon-flavored
So I... abstained
Right. Bacon, ham... Ok, I get it
Wey...
Young people now have no shame.
Young people now? Like you?
Yeah
- Drop your briefs!
- They have no shame
It’s normal. Always normal
Are you like them?
- No.
- Are you ashamed?
Yes, ashamed of them.
I’ll waste your ugly mug!
Anyone can speak, but
you stay polite, OK.
So why are you ashamed for them?
They have no shame
They yell, they hit each other.
They make jokes,
bother others. No shame
Wey, aren’t you confusing
shame and discipline?
You find the others...
rowdy and impolite.
It can be shameful too
Louise?
You can be ashamed of your appearance
Absolutely
Tell me Louise
what are you ashamed of?
My ears
Your ears?
Can we see? You’re ashamed of your ears?
What’s wrong with them?
They stick out
- You think they stick out
- Mine too
I think that covers it all.
You have all you need
to figure it out
Take out your exercise books.
Note the following exercise
for next Thursday
It’s very simple:
Write your self portrait.
A self-portrait
isn’t an autobiography.
I don’t want your life story
Describe yourself and your personality.
We’ll read them in class
...and see how we can use them
Khoumba.
You know I want to see you
Give me your report book
Why?
You know why.
No, give it to me. Politely.
That’s enough now
Put your photo on it
Is it normal to refuse to read
when teacher asks you to?
Is that normal?
There’s others in the class.
I can’t turn a blind eye to this.
Can I?
OK.
What happened this summer?
What happened during the vacation?
- I didn’t see you
- I know.
I’m intrigued.
At the end of the year in June
...we’d gotten on pretty well together
You participated in class.
Since September,
since the start of this year,
You’re not cooperative,
...You keep sulking,
You refuse to read... What happened?
I don’t like reading now.
Can you hurry, please?
No, I won’t hurry!
Explain.
Why have things changed
all of a sudden?
I can’t stay a kid forever
So it’s a kid thing to cooperate?
That's it
- There's others in the class.
Of course, when you work, it's
I haven’t finished.
My moms waiting for me
I want an apology first
An apology for what you did
"I apologize for
being insolent, sir"
Sorry. Ok?
No, not sorry.
"I apologize for being insolent"
Go ahead
"I apologize, sir"
- "No, I apologize
for being insolent"
Be sincere. I want a real apology
Can you hurry up, please?
- My moms waiting
- For your apology
Let’s deal with this
I want a sincere apology
...that’ll stand for the rest of the year
We won’t go on like this
I apologize for being insolent.
More conviction!
I’m not saying it 50 times
- You two,
What are you up to?
We’re waiting
Hurry, I’m listening
I apologize for being insolent.
May I go now, please?
I didn’t mean it
Two weeks ago, at the last meeting
the teachers suggested
introducing a penalty point system
for the students
...based on the driving license system
If student broke a rule
...they would lose points
As its teachers idea,
I’ll let them to speak
Since last September...
...we’ve noticed an increase
in problems within the school.
Punishment has no effect
on the students
So we had the idea
...of a penalty system
The students would have
for example six points each
and depending on the misdeed
they’d lose one or two points.
And when they run out of points?
They go before the disciplinary committee.
As a parents representative...
...this is typical
of the schools bad habits…
You always condemn the students...
...but never praise them
They earn praise on their own
They do it with their grades,
by moving up a class
and we do it in staff meetings...
...by encouraging them to work.
There’s the honor roll,
the congratulations.
that all counts.
In your system
...you take away points for misdeeds
but why not further
...and give points to those
who do good things?
Like gold stars.
I’m all for praising the students.
but if student collect points
and end up with 34 points, say,
...That leaves room
for all kinds of trouble,
...we can’t control
Without going as far...
as these imaginary 34 points
...six points to start with,
means they can cause trouble
without punishment.
Losing a point or two
isn’t a real punishment.
It can create
a dangerous sense of impunity.
For me, the ideas
totally wrong-headed.
In that case,
...we could find a punishment
...where the students
lose all their points in one go...
But why bother with the points
in that case?
It’s tricky
- What you call a sense of impunity
gives us a room to maneuver,
...When you’re dealing
with punishments.
that are cut and dried,
you can’t adapt them to each case
I don’t agree
The rules apply in the same way
...to all the students
They break them, they’re punished
If not, why bother with rules?
Dealing with extremely strict rules
...creates the greatest tension...
Take cell phones
We agreed on a rule...
...that cell phones
were not allowed in class
Sorry, but I break that rule
...because it wasn’t problem for me
There’s room to be tolerant.
The reign of the arbitrary.
No, the law
and the spirit of the law.
We could talk all night
but its not possible
We have other topics to tackle.
In particular, one vital issue,
a very sensitive one,
concerning the staff coffee machine.
It’s a sensitive issue, all right
There’s a real problem this year...
...The price of a coffee has gone up
from 40 centimes
to 50 centimes
That may seem petty...
...but with several coffees a day,
...at 8, 10 or 4
in the afternoon...
it works out a lot
...So we've clubbed together
to buy a coffee maker.
- That way we can drink
as much coffee as we want...
...without having to count.
- Mr. Pierre will be delighted
to reply.
- First of all, this machine
was installed in 2001...
to replace a machine
...that needed the intervention of...
...an outside company for restocking
...repairs etc.
It was very expensive
And not at all profitable
We switched to the new machine,
which isn’t profitable yet
I’m sorry to hear that!
And so we increased
...the price of coffee by ten centimes.
The thing has to be
economically viable
- Nobody’s shocked?
- It’s clear and logical for me.
- Good evening. Don’t move
- We have to go
We haven’t finished
" Respect
" Adolescents
learn to respect their teachers...
..." because of threats...
..." or the fear of having problems
" For starters, I respect you...
..." and respect must be mutual
For instance,
I didn’t say you’re hysterical
..." so why do you say I am?
" I’ve always respected you
..." so I don’t understand
why I have to write this.
" I know you have it in for me
but don’t know why.
" I shall sit at the back...
..." to avoid any other conflicts.
" unless you come looking for them.
" I admit I can be insolent...
..." but only if provoked.
" I wont look at you again,.
" so you cant say
my look is insolent.
" In theory, in French class,
..." you talk about French,
not your grandma or sister
..." or girls periods.
" And so, from now on,
..." I wont spell to you again.. "
Signed Khoumba.
- What is it?
- Secret.
- A secret?
- A secret.
It won’t stay a secret for long.
Esmeralda,
Why have you changed places?
No reason.
I felt like it.
- A problem?
- No, not at all.
No problem.
I wanted a change of scene.
Ok, that’s enough.
Let’s get to work.
No, sir, please!
Please, sir!
You’re just copying
what you did at home
You’ve had plenty of time
Esmeralda.
I have to?
Yes, absolutely.
My name is Esmeralda Ouertani.
I'm 14...
...I live on Allee du Pere Dhuit...
...Paris 20,
...with my two parents and
my three brothers and sisters.
Later,
...I’d like to be a policewoman...
...because people say
all policeman are bad,
...and so we need good ones.
If not, I’d like to be a rapper...
...and I’m fan of Bakar, Medine,
...Younes, Marvin and Mafiak1 Fry.
Otherwise,
I like eating, sleeping
and hanging out in the hood.
Or rather?
- The neighborhood.
- You can say it right.
When you write,
you use the standard style...
Don’t make me correct you.
Wey, go on.
My names Wey, I’m Chinese.
I’m 15, I have two sisters,
I’m the youngest.
My hobby is playing video games
at least 4 hours a day.
I find it hard
using French correctly.
It’s so hard expressing myself...
...that others don’t understand me.
That’s why I don’t communicate much.
I hardly ever go out.
Nothing much interests me outside...
The environment doesn’t suit me here
since I’m allergic
...but i don’t know what.
Allergic to yourself, that’s what.
That’s good, Wey.
I feel I know you better...
...after hearing your self portrait.
That’s the goal. To tell us things.
He’s just happens to be good,
not ours
No, not at all.
I can congratulate Wey
and I'd gladly congratulate you,
if you manage to do it well.
Rabah, read us...
…your self portrait
- No.
How can I congratulate you
if you don’t?
I don’t need that.
Make your mind up
We’re listening.
My name's Rabah. I’m 14.
I listen to rap.
I love my village in Kabylia
and go there every year.
I like music, rap and slam.
I have two brothers
but I don’t like school.
I don’t like tramps.
I like Zidane.
I like to talk and I like
Psy 4 de la Rime's videos,
...Go Marseille!
We can manage without Marseille.
Go Paris!
We don’t need it in a self-portrait
- That’s all.
- He skipped two lines.
Cut it out.
Go, dude.
Boubacar!
- I like to make love
I like to look good for the women
and I like summer,
...to see girls cleavage.
Why not, Rabah?
I never wrote that.
It looks like your writing.
No way!
There’s no shame in liking cleavage.
It's not a sin.
Souleymane stop rocking
and read your self-portrait.
- I’m very curious
- Huh?
No, not huh.
I wrote nothing.
- I saw your writing earlier
- No, I wrote nothing
You did
- Nothing
- We're listening.
I'm Souleymane.
I have nothing to say about me
because no one knows me but me
- Bravo!
- All right
That’s good. A bit long maybe
You can’t make the effort
that the others did?
I don’t talk about myself.
How come the others do?
That’s their problem
I don’t talk about my life
He just can’t write, that's all!
What's up, you cop?
You talking to me, cop?
I can live with it
- Enough!
- Arrest guys...
...instead of talking to me.
Got your cuffs?
Your breath stinks!
- Chill.
- Heard of Aquafresh?
Souleymane…
there's no need
to be offensive.
Need a toothbrush?
Souleymane,
...You’re a lot better
at oral insults than writing
He can’t even write his name.
Zip it! What does this say?
Spare us your Koran.
Shut it. What’s wrong
with the Koran.
I’ll spare you when you calm dawn
It’s the Koran.
Bullshit!
What’s that tattoo, Souleymane?
Why are you showing it?
He claims it's Koran
What is it? Why are you showing us?
It means shut your mouth.
It doesn’t mean that
So give us the real translation
Go on, tell us
I don’t want to
You show it in my class so tell us.
It says here, right here:
"If your words are less important
than silence, keep quiet. "
What I said
It’s not what you said.
Why isn’t it the same?
It’s different.
I think it sounds better
Yes it’s better put.
If only you could write such
interesting things on paper,
that would be great
I think so too.
That proves you can do it.
After these fires few
self-portraits, Id like you,
to rewrite them and polish them...
...making sure you answer
the questions that we listed:
what I like and don’t like...
my qualities and flaws
who I’d like to be?
Come in.
Stand up please. Good morning.
That goes for those at the back too
Come on, stand up.
Cherif, you heard me?
Everyone has to stand.
It’s a way of greeting an adult
It doesn’t mean
submission or humiliation.
Good. Sit back down
I’ve come to introduce
a new student.
Carl.
Try to make him welcome...
...until the end of the year.
Thank you
Carl, go sit in the third row,
in that free place
Khoumba, move your things
Take a sheet of paper and a pen
and try to catch up with the others
...We’ll talk after
Don’t forget the homework
for Monday without fail.
Let’s finish with this
Carl, stay here a minute or two
Welcome
I don’t know if you know
but I'm Mr. Marin,
your class supervisor.
If there’s a problem, tell me.
I know who you are...
why you’re here
The principal told me
but that doesn’t matter for me
We'll start from scratch here
It will all go well.
You’ve seen that we...
Were on self-portraits to be
handed in next Monday.
- Maybe you could do one too
- OK.
Know when the next class is?
Monday, 9.30
Good.
You like French?
Like everyone, I guess.
That doesn’t mean much.
Ok, off you go.
Good bye
You know what a self-portrait is?
- Yes.
- You’re sure?
Yes.
Have a good day.
Pleased to meet you
Sit down, please.
Thank you for coming
I know it isn’t easy
We're very pleased with Wey
Very pleased. All the teachers
at the staff meeting said so.
He's kind, he's pleasant...
It's good to have him in class.
And it’s showing in his grades.
we have...
the usual good grades in mathematics.
He's doing well there
13/20.
In French,
we have a 9 here
Not a lot
He doesn’t speak French very well
yet but that’s only normal
He speaks a lot.
He tells me about a lot of things.
He talks about his computer
He’s into that
Always too late
He works too late?
Yes, too late, not sleep good.
After, school not good.
...Eyes get sick after
He may spend a lot of time
on the computer
but things are fine at school
for now
He works well
and he doesn’t seem tired
Nassim... I’d like him to do...
He can go far. He has all he needs
At his age, I wasn’t that lucky
I’m behind him
Anything he needs, I get him
But he has to do right
Things are good at home with him
but I’d like him
to keep on studying
Me and his mother,
we’d like to be proud of him
That’s what we ask of him
I think we all agree
on what we need to do.
It’s crazy how alike you are
We're lookers in family
You’re right.
An adolescent who talks
with his family,
...who has good grades,
...who has friends,
even if he’s a bit of a loner,
...he’s an outcast?
He’s a boy who talks with adults,
who exchanges with them
Maybe he doesn’t with you
but that means
...he’s just a teenager
trying to define himself.
I was useless at school for years,
...I rejected the idea
of marking us fit in with the system.
Do his black clothes bother you?
The way he looks?
I don’t get it.
I’d like him to go to the best,
to Henri IV.
Why?
Standards again...
Because they have
very high standards.
A mother wants the best for her son
She’s scared I’ll feel lost
in high school because of others
...went to fancy private schools.
and Dolto Hogh isn’t like that
It’s a pity that the teachers...
I don't want to accuse anyone
Go on, accuse us. It’s a pleasure
Why don’t you try
...to push the better students
...a little harder, say?
They get bogged down
by other students...
...who aren’t as good
My mom makes stuff up.
Dolto High isn’t useless.
- I didn’t say useless,
I said average
I didn’t call it useless
- We talked about Souleymane
a great deal...
...at the staff meeting
Many teachers have complained
about his attitude
...that is very negative.
What?
Many complain...
...that he comes without his things,
...When he comes, as he’s often absent
- I think you know that
- No we didn’t know
Souleymane tells us he works hard
She doesn’t think so.
- There have been notes
in his report book...
...since September, 3 month now
Notes about the problems
he was having.
- She signs them without knowing
because she cant read.
You read the notes too?
Yes, but I'm just his brother. You see?
But you knew there was a problem?
- No, I didn’t know.
He says things are fine when I ask
Does he work at home?
He stays in his room
She doesn’t understand the notes
I realize that
You know the situation now
I'm telling you officially:
there's a problem
- Talk to him.
- I'll talk to him about it
Just having an idea.
Maybe conversation with his father
could help.
I'll talk to my father
and see what we can do
We're not settling scores.
We want to improve things
- Your mom?
- You bet.
- Ugly old crow!
- She hates photos
Me and my bro pissed her off
Sir! Souleymane has a photos
...for his self-portrait
Cut it out, my photos are crap.
- That’s a good idea.
- Get your down
Painters do self-portraits
- I'm no painter
- Yes, I know that.
Let's go
Caps, please
I spend all my free time
playing the guitar.
If you’re typing, hurry and finish
to let the others...
...type up their self-portraits
Souleymane,
Dont blow the place up!
- You know what you’re doing?
- Yeah
As a computer genius
you’ll put it all back after.
Don’t worry.
I’m counting on you.
- Ok, Carl?
- Yes, sir
- I can’t see it?
- No, not yet.
Sir?
How do you spell Lafayette?
- How do you mean?
- Like Galeries Lafayette.
Why mention that?
I go there often
so I want to add it
Wow! That’s four metro stops
A huge leap from your neighborhood
We're not Hicks
We're city kids
Really? You go into
the center of Paris?
I go everywhere. The 1st, the 5th,
the 20th, the 12th, the 19th
Why do you go to the 5th?
In the 5th, I go to see pals
...in high school
Near Luxembourg.
The Luxembourg gardens?
Not the gardens, Luxembourg.
The country?
No, the Luxembourg metro station!
So you do get out and about
I see you two have made up
- It's our business
- And not yours
So, how do you spell Lafayette?
Lafayette is L-A-F-A-Y-E-T-T-E.
With a capital
Much better now!
Much better
Yes, that is a good photo
- You could add a legend.
- A legend?
Like a story or tale.
A caption under the photo
like in papers.
You mean, like in Le Parisien?
Yes, like in Le Parisien
What could you put? Who is she?
- My old woman.
- Meaning?
- My mother
- You could say she's your mother.
Then you could explain
...why she's making this gesture
to the photographer
They'd pissed her off
I'm not gonna write that!
- So why is she doing that?
- She hates photos
So write that
"My mother hate having
..."her photo taken".
That's a legend.
- Understand?
- Yeah
Do that with all the photos
and you're set
- Printed everything?
- Yeah, I’m good
Excellent
What are you doing now, sir?
As you can see,
I’m putting the photos up
...to get a global view
The others read out,
their self-portraits
...so you’re going to put yours...
...on show.
You know my photos suck
Not at all, they’re very good
Sure
When a student does good work,
...I let the whole class see it
You’re just winding me up
No, I wind you up if I feel
...you can do better. This is good.
That's bullshit
If you've finished,
come and take a look
...at Souleymane's masterpiece
Slowly
I'll straighten them
Look at the tattoo!
You're hideous!
I like playing soccer
I like playing computer games
I like playing with pretty girls
I like vacations in the Carribean
I like fries, zouk and dancehall music
I like watching MTV Base
and I like my parents and my brother.
I like my pals and staying up all night
I like the series on the slave trade
I like my hood
I like the series Homeland Security
I like eating in restaurants
and going wild.
I hate people crying for no reason
I hate techno and tectonic
I hate guys and girls who show off
I hate visiting my brother in jail
I hate talent contest shows on TV
I hate politicians,
the war in Iraq,
Goths and skaters
I hate teachers who are too strict
I hate mathematics, racists
and I hate Materazzi
I hates the Paul Eluard school
and I like being here
I have something to say
Could you listen to me, please?
The mother of Wey
...a student in 4/3
has been arrested
She was in France illegally.
She has been picked up
and may be tried next week
She may be deported to China.
I thought you should know
as its important
She's been here 3 years now!
I know but that's how it goes,
wrong place, wrong time
Not the father?
He doesn’t have papers either
but they don’t bother him
To start with
as lawyers cost a lot
we could do a collection
and maybe even go to court
to try have some influence
on the verdict
Will Wey have to leave?
Not for now but you never know.
Well,
I feel kind of pathetic after that
I had something to tell you,
...but this isn’t a good time
You’ve said too much now
I'm pregnant
That calls for a celebration!
How far gone?
Two months. I'll only have a drop
Just a drop
Bravo, Vincent!
I didn’t do it on purpose!
Who shook it?
Any names yet? If it’s a boy, say?
...You already know?
If it’s a boy, I like Enguerran.
Seriously?
What a handicap!
That won't be easy
I hope not. Thanks a lot!
You all have a glass?
Hold on a second
I have two wishes
My first wish
is that Wey's mom stays in France
And my second wish
...is that my child will be
as intelligent as Wey
"Jackie Chan"!
C'mon, play
I didn’t do nothing
He just fell!
Play, Souleymane
- What do you say, Mali man?
- What’s up, you Caribbean shit?
Malian bastard!
Motherfucker
C’mon lets play!
- Caribbean fag!
- I’ll waste the fucker
Shut up
Blow Thierry Henri, faggot
Stand there. Talk loud enough
for them to hear
and try to convince them.
Go ahead
The African Cup of Nations
will be starting soon
I'm glad Morocco's playing
It's the best team in the world
in my opinion.
The sick thing is
that my pals,
the Malians aren't playing.
It's tough for them.
They weren't good enough to qualify.
Morocco would have let them play
on a friendly basis...
but 4-0 is really hurts
- 4-0 how?
- Last time
...Mali played Morocco,
they wasted 4-0
But the weird thing is
...when Mali doesn't play
...it's like all the Africans here,
...aren't African
With each cup, they all go crazy
but when Mali doesn’t play,
they keep a low profile.
Weird.
So, whether Mali plays in the
African Cup of Nations or not,
...the Africans in this class
feel more or less African. Ok.
Thank you, Nassim.
I get the feeling
your words are directed
...at your neighbor, Souleymane
Morocco jerk's
...not even on my radar,
Arthur is next
I see you have your notes
just like a politician
- Exactly
- That's good
Speak up Arthur.
Esmeralda, let him speak first
I want to defend my look
...A lot of people say it sucks
I don’t dish your clothes,
so you don’t dish mine.
Clothes are freedom of speech
I dress how I want
you dress how you want, ok
I dress like this to be different
...and not follow the others
like sheep.
You're the sheep here!
I feel better being myself
and not being like others
I also think
if there were 22 goths here,
...and one guy like you
you'd keep quiet then
There's a contradiction
in what you say
You want to be you.
Are those clothes you?
Those clothes are worn
by a huge number of people
Most people who wear them
are gloomy inside
...so we're all kind of alike
- You're all alike, you're all gloomy,
so that’s not you.
By being different
You're different and the same.
Thank you for taking a stand
...and being brave enough to do so
Boubacar, go on
Boubacar, my pal
Listen to him
I’ve come up to reply to Nassim
He says that since Mali
isn’t in the Africa Cup of Nations
black Africans have no team to support
But he's forgetting Ivory Coast!
With an ace player Didier Drogba
He beats any Moroccan
He plays for Chelsea
What Moroccan plays in England?
They're not up to it
I'm through.
Thanks, Boubacar
I think that rectification
was indeed...
...indispensable
Who wants to speak now?
Carl, go on
Actually, I'd like to say
they're starting to piss us off...
...with the Africa Cup
At recess you're there
pissing us off with your cup
It hasn't even started yet...
Carl, I'll be polite with you
Sorry to interrupt, but tell me,
what's your national team?
France
Why do you say you're Caribbean...
...rather than French?
We're French. It's a French region
Why don't you ever say
you're French?
- It's the same
- I don't think so
Look at the players.
Thierry Henri, Wiltord…
...Abidal, Thuram...
Where does Diarra play?
He won't play in Mali, bro,
he's not crazy enough.
Shut your mouth, pal,
I'm not your bro!
An ape like this jerk
No need to loose your cool.
We can talk calmly!
That isn’t a slanging match.
It’s a debate.
Souleymane,
watch your language
He's fuming!
Clam up. Go get fucked!
No vulgarity
- I ain’t talking to you, man
- I’m talking to you
Is that any way
to talk to a teacher?
That's enough now
You're coming with me
- I'm talking to you
- Don't start yelling at me, ok
I'll get you, faggot
You just can’t talk normally?
Shut up, ape
Nobody else moves
Hurry it up
- Move it
- Hands off!
Aren’t you sick
of assing around?
Sorry to bother you
I have a troublemaker who's
been disrespectful in class.
I didn’t ask you to sit down,
Souleymane.
My class is waiting
Sit down now.
I'm listening
Will you tell me what happened?
A teacher should have to leave
his class to bring you here?
"Results
..."too uneven
"Too much talking in class
Now let's move on to Louise,
present here today
A total disaster.
What can we do with you?
No, good work
Always good, I'd say
It's a joy having a student
like her. We need to say it.
Shall we offer this young lady
a commendation?
I'm sorry, but I don't
...totally agree with you.
She's relatively well-placed
in the class
from a numerical angle
But a commendation?
There's room for progress,
huge room for progress
and I don’t think
her general attitude
...really merits a commendation
That's the problem
with commendations
...Are they purely numerical
and mathematical
or are they also to do
...with her attitude and behavior
as top of the class?
That means, to get commendation,
...you have to be an excellent student
...and, at the same time,
be a class leader?
So a commendation this term
Louise is intelligent
...and will realize she can do better
to satisfy you
Now, Cherif
...Our friend Cherif
I have a problem with Cherif
...He's a kid with abilities
he could do well
could easily give him 17/20
...but he spends so much time talking
...and disturbing the class,
...his average grade is poor
And that's a pity
His behavior's irregular.
He can be a disaster
and you cant do a thing with him
or he can be really good
- What does Cherif get?
A warning about his work
or his behavior?
For me, behavior,
...not work
- In my class, it's more his work
- That’s a problem.
It's more like a work problem
looking at his grades.
Mathematics: 6
French: 8
History and geography: 9
English: 9,5
Excuse me!
Science 12. Music 11
His grades are pretty low but…
...it seems to be a behavior problem
Why don't we put that for now
and say he can work harder?
So I'll put Cherif
..." can succeed as long as
..." his attitude changes
..." in relation to his work. "
Let's move on to Souleymane
Someone else can start.
What do we say?
Nothing good.
- What else?
- We already discussed him
in the first term. We said it all
He has huge weakness,
notably in written French
I don’t think there’s anything
particularly new
this term
Feeling better, Esmeralda?
I didn’t know being class rep
was such fun
We were talking about Souleymane
In relation
to what Francois just said,
he forgot his things
most of the time this term
...and didn’t do much
It’s not just that,
It’s way beyond that
Sir!
He’s more and more unruly
He prevents the others from working.
Can I say something?
If you put the biscuit away.
Remember, you aren’t allowed
to eat in classroom
Well, his overall grade
has gone from 6,75 to 7,25.
We're not discussing his grades
...but his behavior for now
I have the impression
...we need to consider
disciplinary action
His attitude's wrong
It's simple. Every other class
I throw him out
I don’t even throw
him out anymore,
...He’s only too happy when I do.
I don’t think disciplinary action
will help...
...because things will get
...really bad then
They’re already really bad
It’s gone too far.
It’s like he’s mad at the others
for being normal
I'll remind you Mr. Marin
...you brought him to me yesterday.
Yes, but it was this year's
first incident.
He was disrespectful, I set a limit
I did what I did but I don’t think
it will go any further than that
I don’t have any real complaints,
...apart from yesterday
Our job isn't to make sure
students sit quietly at the back
and don’t cause any trouble.
We have to bring them out!
I won’t do that
with threats or punishment,
...I'd rather stress his good work.
Some things interest him.
He can come out
with some pretty good stuff
Simply because he does
...something positive now and then,
...we let him sink
and wallow in his hole...
...and we do nothing. You
just want to buy social harmony.
That said,
what do we say? What do we do?
A warning?
I don’t think a warnings
what he needs.
Maybe we should say
he has reached his limit,
...because he’s
limited scholastically.
That’s all well and good
but I’m dim and have a line to fill.
What do we put?
It’s not right
...saying that
Three rhymes per verse.
What do you call that?
- Verses of three lines... Wey?
- A tercet
Very good
And four rhymes would be?
A quatrain
From quatre, four
Tercet, three rhymes.
Quatrain, four
How many syllabes per line?
Can you tell me that?
Khoumba.
I know here are 10
You know that?
- Want me to show you?
- Yes.
"Noir-dans-la-nei-ge...
..."et-dans-la-bru-me. "
Thats 10
You say that and...
...You have two
...extra syllables
by counting the mute Es.
Don’t count them, they’re mute
That makes 8
...We can underline each syllable
I'll come back to that one
Two octosyllables
and one four-syllable line
- What is it?
- A problem,
11.47 that makes
11,5.
Is 11.47 the number of syllables here?
No, my grade. It's down!
They lowered my grade!
What's that to do with poetry?
11.47 is 11.5
Who gave you your grade?
You shouldn't have it yet
Esmeralda told me
So the class reps
...did do something after all
I took a load of notes!
I got the impression you weren't
...really following the meeting
- I noted all!
Louise, I'm delighted
you've done
a good job passing on information...
Let's get back to this poem
The rule is to count
in front of a consonant...
A question
What?
I heard you really wiped me out
...at the meeting yesterday
Another remark about poetry, I see.
No, it isn’t
Yes, I know it isn’t about poetry
What do you mean?
I dunno. You wiped me out
Some teachers, not me,
...said if you carry on like this
you'll be in trouble,
...not wiped out.
That's revenge. I don't get it
Why do for revenge?
How come it's revenge?
If you say stuff about me
getting in trouble, that's revenge
It's not revenge at all
We're not on the streets
It's a warning
Our goal here isn't revenge,
...it's discipline
- Get the difference?
- I don't get it.
When a judge sends someone to jail,
...he doesn't do it to get revenge
...It helps society run smoothly
You just want revenge.
You're riffed with me.
All I care about is revenge?
I wake up and say
I'll get Souleymane today?
You insulted him yesterday anyhow.
He really laid into you!
I did not.
What did he say, Louise?
That you we’re limited.
...I underlined it, I was so shocked
Me? Limited?
Brilliant...
Esmeralda, Louise,
...What's your role as class reps?
You represent the students
to help this class work
or you stir up trouble for me?
We just do our job.
Wicked!
We report on the meeting.
Of course.
I didn't realize
When I saw you snigger
...at the meeting, I felt bad for you
It wasn't the place or time
It didn't look very serious
Nobody minded in any case
- They did!
- Only you
No, it bothered me and I think
it bothered the others too
No. It only bothered you
Sorry, but laughing like that
made you look like two skanks.
What?
Have you just lost it?
That's a bad thing!
You can't dump on us
The word is insult.
You're crazy insulting on us.
You say "dump on" or "insult"
It's either one or the other, ok.
Yeah keep on talking!
In fact I never said
you we’re skanks,
...I said that at one point
...in the meeting
...you acted like skanks.
Understand?
Don't try to con us,
you said skanks
I'm just explaining the difference.
Sir, you don't talk to girls like that!
Look who's talking!
...You always insult everybody!
He wants revenge on the girls
No way. The noble knight
riding to rescue act,
...won’t wash!
You don’t talk to me, man!
Show some respect!
I will if I want!
You're heading for trouble!
Think you're tough?
It's a question of discipline!
I'll take you anytime!
Stop playing the big short
- Calm down
- Stay outta this
Cut it out!
Don't touch me!
Don’t touch me.
You're crazy!
Cut it out
What are you doing?
I'm outta here
You can't just walk out of my class.
Are you nuts?
- Calm down
- Let go of me
Stop it
- Let me go
- Ah!
- Where are you going?
- Let go, fucker
Pathetic
Fuck
What do we do?
I think we need to convene
the disciplinary committee
This is starting to add up
it begins
with disrespect, then the fight,
...with a student injured,
...and finally he leaves the class
without permission.
There was only one incident
and it all spread out from there.
One thing led to another,
...a chain reaction.
Well
...what I can do is take
a protective measure
...since this is so serious
...by suspending Souleymane
for 48 hours.
That'll give us a little time
...to reach a decision
OK.
Shall we do that?
However, I need to see you tomorrow.
Could you come to my office?
- Good bye.
- Good bye
Francois!
I need a word with you
There's a rumor going around...
A rumor?
Some students came to see me
and told me...
...you insulted them
Who? Louise and Esmeralda?
They told me
...you called them skanks
...and that led to the incident
...with Souleymane
And you believe them?
That's why I needed to see you.
You didn't mention it
in your incident report...
I didn't mention it.
What can I say?
- Did you do it or not?
- What?
- Did you...
- Hi!
Hi.
Did you call them skanks?
But Souleymane's another matter!
I know it had nothing to do with him
But word's getting around.
People are talking.
I wanted
...to let you know
- Thanks for letting me know.
Hey, you two
You complained about me.
- Thanks a lot!
- You’re welcome
You could have talked to me
Teachers can complain about us
and vice versa, right?
No, it doesn't work both ways.
What are you after?
To see you punished
- Punished?
- Yes!
- You, punish me?
- You insulted us, you get punished.
Where will that get you?
I'll have spoken out.
Great, that's a lot of use.
Do you know what 'skank' means?
I never called you skanks!
Yes, you did. For me
skank means prostitute.
It's not that at all
For me, it doesn't mean that.
It's nothing important at all,
just a girl laughing stupidly
Hey, skank means prostitute, right?
You bet!
- Will Souleymane get expelled?
- No.
- A disciplinary hearing?
- We don't know yet.
It's a possibility
Stop yelling
before anything is decided
It's all settled anyway
- Why say that?
- Because it's always the same!
You're in no position to talk.
You're the one who got hurt
He didn't mean it
There was a metal thing in his bag
In any case he blew a fuse
and that's bad
Sir,
...anyone can blow a fuse
And then calm down after
That's not sure
- You did
- No!
You're calmer now
I'm not. You don’t know me!
All the teachers say
your attitude is perfect now...
You think you've tamed me?
No, being sent here helped
...you understand things, see?
Teachers helped you
and we'll do the same
for Souleymane.
I say teachers who
expel students are fuckers
Right on.
You want to repeat that?
- Yeah, fuckers
- Everyone goes wild
...over some word I said. You
say fucker and I shouldn't react?
They're fuckers!
Cut it out!
You say skanks, we say fucker.
It's the same thing
They're nothing alike
A teacher can say certain things
that students can't say.
Try to understand that!
We have no right to speak?
You keep talking all the time!
You never stop speaking
Whenever we talk, you yell.
What is this?
Enough...
Sir!
- Sir?
- What?
Will Souleymane get a hearing?
Give it a rest
You sound like you want
him to. It fires you up.
You know what'll happen
if he's expelled?
He'll change schools.
No, he won’t change schools.
It's automatic. It's obligatory.
That goes for Souleymane too.
Do you know his father?
I've seen him once or twice.
No, you don’t know him!
If he's expelled, his dad'll
send him back to their village
Don't get overdramatic
He'll go back to Mali
I think we all need
to keep our heads.
Don’t worry
You can’t smoke here sir
I know, but since I was alone
Ok, you went too far
with those girls.
We all screw up.
Souleymane overreacted.
He's right.
I saw Khoumba.
Her face was all bloody
What he did is unacceptable.
That's for sure.
I know that.
His bag hit her by accident.
A split eybrow bleeds a lot.
That's all.
You can't ignore it.
Don't take it to heart.
Seen how they talk to us?
How's that relevant?
Souleymane is going to get expelled
...That’s it!
- No.
- That's kind of logical.
How many hearings last year?
12 at least.
Not that many.
He could be right.
I know, I'm on the committee
so I saw them all
An average of two per month,
12 in all with an expulsion each time
The hearing is where
we talk things over
Ok, 12 students were expelled
but maybe there was no other solution.
12 out of 12
...talk about debate!
But 12 out of 12 just means
...when a student has a hearing,
it's too late.
Or it was justified.
Ok, things happen
that lead to a hearing
But then what happens?
What do we expect from a hearing?
There are prior stages:
Pre-disciplinary committees,
...we inform the parents,
the students are warned...
- Not in this case.
- We've no time.
It's pretty rare.
It's rare because we have
this final punishment
...that allows us to ignore
the prior steps.
And even if we did use them,
...the simple fact
of expelling a student...
...is a disavowal
of everything we have tried.
Ok, but it's Souleymane's chance
to justify himself
At a hearing, you don't speak.
You're scared. You're paralyzed.
Exactly.
Let me sum up.
He'll get a disciplinary hearing,
he'll be expelled
and maybe even sent back to Mali
You're being overdramatic.
No, I'm not
Students who know him better
than any of us here,
...who know his father,
say that he is likely Mali...
to send him back to Mali after this
Some are threatened
...with boarding school
but in never happens
It can happen.
A lot of parents spend their time
...threatening their kids with that.
You can't take it into account
- Even if there was just a slight risk
that a hearing could lead
to him being sent back,
I don't think I can take that risk.
It's like when you hesitate
...over punishing a kid
because when he goes home,
once that door closes,
...he'll get a beating
from his parents
We've all seen that
...But we still have to punish
them when they go too far
Whatever the consequences
which don't
...concern you!
So I ignore that?
I know punishment
can have such a consequence,
...but I turn a blind eye, is that it?
You can't take it into account
in every case
The violence…
him being sent back...
- No more Christmas presents...
- True, you have to consider it
but after a while...
It's a question of principle
...We each have a role to play
We can't substitute
ourselves for the parents
Sorry, but if I rewind the movie,
...it's a weird chain of events.
It starts with reprimands,
...when Souleymane forget
his things, talks back.
We punish him. Again and again,
until a disciplinary hearing
leading to who knows what
Everything gets out of hand
Sure, looking at it that way
it's really shocking
But the school won't
expelling Souleymane
He's been gone for a while
Francois, I didn't
expect you so soon.
Have you reached a decision?
I don't think I have much choice.
By the way, Julie told me…
you had a heated exchange
...with two girls in your class.
Yes, the two class reps
but it happened first so
You apparently
called them "skanks"
Let's say that, yes
That complicates things,
but the problem remains.
I'd like you to mention it
in your report
I don't want it used against us
at the disciplinary hearing.
Don't bother hiding it,
just write it down.
I understand.
I'll let you reread this
before we launch the procedure.
So I… I just need to add...
Yes, without going into detail.
Does that suit you?
OK.
Can you take the minute.
- Hello
- Hello.
Hello, sir.
- Please sit down.
- Thanks.
"Carl tried to reason with him,
but Souleyman broke free,
"winging his bag that hit Khoumba
in the face.
"He left, insulting everyone
and slamming the door.
"I didn't go after him
because I needed...
"to help Khoumba
whose eybrow was bleeding. "
Those are the facts
that led to today's hearing
Madame, it doesn't mean
Souleyman is a bad boy.
That's not we're saying
But, sometimes,
a student in a class
through voluntary or
involuntary behavior,
can create an atmosphere that...
...prevents the class from working.
Do you understand
what we're saying?
If I may say something, it's true
there had been number of signs
that should have warned us.
We could have reacted sooner
But how we have to deal
with an incident
that is fairy violent
and that's simply unacceptable.
I'd like to know
if you realize that, Souleymane?
We're not saying you're
deliberately violent.
The problem is you can't control
what you say,
...and what you do
You're here to express
your point of view.
Go ahead
I don't give a damn.
I've got nothing to say
Do whatever you want to do
Excuse me...
Can you translate?
She says I'm a good boy
I do my homework.
I help my brothers and sisters
with their work when I can
I always wash the dishes
and help her when I can
We don't doubt he's a good son.
That's not the problem.
Let's consider
...his school record
Excuse me, but could we focus
on the facts here?
Firstly, I'd like to say
...that we're surprised to see
the teacher involved in the incident
...on this committee
We find it highly irregular
It's true. It's odd
to be both judge and litigant.
First of all,
...Mr. Marin was elected
to the administrative board.
as the teachers' representative
Moreover, I think
that the incident...
...that occurred in
Mr. Marin's class
...doesn't involve the teacher
directly.
I'm sorry, you mention
...some harsh words
...spoken by the teacher...
Apparently, you used
the word "skanks"
...to describe the class reps.
And that's a problem
I did say that
...but it wasn’t something
that concerned Souleymane.
I think he used the excuse
of a rather heated exchange
...to express the bad mood
that he was in that day.
He tried to defend them
So I feel that it's relevant
Sorry, but absolutely
nothing justifies
...being disrespectful to a teacher,
...insulting everyone and leaving
a class without permission.
Souleymane, do you
have anything to say?
I don't know. What can I say?
Souleymane?
- What did she say?
- The same thing again
Souleymane?
She apologizes on my behalf.
You can come back in now.
Madame, the committee
has conferred
and has decided to expel Souleymane
from the school for good.
You will receive the ruling
by registered mail
...and have eight days to appeal,
We shall do our best to find
Souleymane another school
Goodbye, Messieurs, Mesdames
Souleymane, come to see me
before the end of the week, please.
Mathematical proportionality.
This year, you learned
mathematical proportionality?
- I liked science
- What you learned, not liked.
If you liked it, you learned.
So what did you learn?
All about volcanoes, earthquakes,
...plates...
Convergence and divergence,
...movement of the Earth's plates,
- It was fascinating.
- It interested you?
- Yeah.
- Good.
Well, in mathematics,
.. trigonometry Pythagoras
theorem, Thales theorem.
I'll stop you there.
You can't sit there and brag...
...you learned Pythagoras theorem.
Recite it for us
If, in a triangle
...two sides are equal to
...If the square rot
If the square of two sides
is equal to the square
...the square of the hypotenuse
then the triangle's a rectangle.
More or less, yes
It's spot on
All right. I believe you.
In history, I learned
about triangular trade.
The fact that ships left Europe...
...with manufactured goods that
they took to Africa to trade for men,
...who’d became slaves
that they took to America to work.
Then they took the money
they made back to Europe.
That's triangular trade
Chemistry
What in chemistry?
Combustion
What's that?
Blending Fehling's solution
and glucose.
What do you get?
Heat up test-tube,
...and it changes color.
- What's the interest?
- The interest?
I dunno. Why teach it to us
if there's no interest?
Reproduction
What did you learn
about human reproduction?
Human reproduction...
Well, the sperm
...gets into the ovum
then you wait 9 months,
then you do a sonogram
and then it comes out
The sperm does?
No, the baby
The human being that's inside.
- Khoumba?
- Me?
Yes. That is your name?
Yes.
In music, I learned to play
the alto recorder...
and in Spanish
The recorder in Spanish?
No, in music, I learned
to play the alto recorder.
- Right
- And other stuff in Spanish
- Good.
Can you say something
to us in Spanish?
- And that means?
- "It's the vacation soon".
I didn't learn anything
You cant spend 9 months at
school and not learn anything.
I'm the living proof
You got something
from the books we read.
- Your books are shite.
- They're what?
They're useless.
What about a book
you read by yourself?
The books I read?
Well, there's The Republic
Platon’s "Republic"?
You read that?
How come?
My big sister had it
- She does philosophy?
- No, law
So what's it about?
Well, there's this guy...
His name's Socrates
Yeah, Socrates.
He stops people in the street
and asks them:
"Are you sure of thinking
what you think?"
"Are you sure of doing
what you do? and so on?"
After that, people
start getting confused.
They ask questions.
The guy's too much
What does he ask people about?
Everything.
Love, religion, God
people, everything
- It's good you read it
- I know
It's not a skank's book!
Wait a second. Before you leave,
here are your self-portraits
One by one. When you have
yours, you can go.
What is it?
These are the self-portraits
that you wrote
...and that we made up
with the class photo and so on
You too, Eva.
You don't have one?
- You look good in it
- Cut it out
You're like a leader
Very good.
- Good bye, Sir.
- Good bye.
- Have a good vacation.
- You too
- Sir?
- Yes…
What is it?
I didn't learn anything
What? That doesn't mean anything
Earlier, all the others...
...said they'd learned something
Compared to them, I learned nothing
You learned as much as them
They had to think hard too.
It's not easy
to remember what you learned...
But I don't understand
What do you mean?
I don't understand what we do.
In French?
In school
You can’t say you don’t
understand everything.
That’s not true...
I don’t want to go
to vocational school.
There’s no question of that yet
You’re moving on to the next year.
You’ll have plenty of time
to think about your future
Vocational school isn’t
an absolute certainty
It all depends on how you do next year
But I don’t want to.
Subtitled by Ian Burnley
Resynced by Runkulis