LOS ANGELES 1979
Come on!
- Yeah... yeah!
- Come on!
Let's try and do this nice and easy,
without any blood.
Like a cobra, huh?
And if we can't?
I said we can try, Andreas.
Here in America, there's always
some smartass who tries to be a hero.
We'll soon be out of America.
We'll have money to build my new plant.
We've got a great future together.
Don't blow it.
Hey, Sean. When's your dad coming on?
One more fight
and they'll start the main event.
Where's Sean?
I don't know. This kid's never around
when you want him.
Come on!
Yo, work this shoulder.
Now breathe.
Go, go! Go!
- Hey, Sean! Sean, where you going?
- I'll be right back.
- Wait! I'll come with you.
- No. I'll be back before the next.
Go.
Use the crowd noise to cover our move.
- Get up! Get up against the wall!
- If they move, kill them.
- Come here, boy.
- Sean!
- Stand back!
- Don't shoot my son!
No!
- Sean, look out!
- Dad!
Dad...
Help him, Izumo. Help him!
I'm bleeding. The little brat bit me!
- Izumo? Is he...?
- I'm afraid he is.
Sean, in the last months you have
proven yourself a worthy student.
Thank you, Master.
Now it is time to continue your training
in the art of mikkyo, the secret doctrine.
First position.
Second position.
Third position.
Fourth position.
Fifth position.
Very good, Sean. First position.
First strike. Second position.
Third position.
Angle the sword down.
Fourth position.
Fifth position. Well done, Sean.
That's OK.
Four, five.
One, two.
- One, two...
- Ow!
Your body is merely
the vehicle of your soul.
Ultimate physical power can be achieved
only by way of spiritual power.
Your mind and soul over your body.
Remember that, Sean.
Mind and soul over your body.
Sean?
Do you remember the first technique?
It's been a long time.
Hai!
We have overcome your tragedy
and turned it into opportunity.
My doubts and fears of bringing you here
are at rest.
Your ability shows that
a greater destiny awaits you.
Now you must seek out this destiny alone.
Your training is at last complete, Sean.
Now you are a ninja.
PORT SAN LUCO, TRIANA
PRESENT DAY
Gentlemen, may I have your attention?
Thank you for coming. Please be seated.
Today is really a great day.
This project has been
over ten years in research.
But I'm glad that I can tell you that there
will be no more inefficient hijackings.
No more bungled kidnappings
or mistimed bombings.
Now terrorism can be scientifically
focused to be totally effective.
It all sounds quite impressive, Doctor.
But untiI you prove its ability
to defeat any human -
or should I say even the strongest
human? - they're not buying.
Very good, GeneraI Andreas.
That's a good challenge. I'll accept it, too.
We'll find a superhuman and show you
the power of our new experiment.
We'd be ready to strike within a month,
if not sooner.
Things seem to be going nicely.
Except for GeneraI Andreas. I don't know
how you tolerate his incessant demands.
His dissatisfaction
can work to our advantage.
UntiI he's outlived his usefulness, let him
think he runs the island. It doesn't matter.
Air Triana announces
the departure of its flight...
Excuse me. You're Sean Davidson, right?
Yeah.
- Curtis. Curtis Jackson!
- That's right.
- Good to see you again, man.
- Good to see you.
- Fighting lightweight?
- I'm just gonna do the sword competition.
Excuse me. Sorry. You made the cover
of Inside Karate this month.
- Dex.
- Hi, Dex. Sean Davidson.
Good to meet you, man.
It's a pleasure. It really is.
- Hey, this is Curtis Jackson.
- Dex.
- Of course. The sword man.
- That's right.
Boy. The English look, uh...
very pale, wouldn't you say?
That's Joe Simpson there. He's tough.
I see Tom Wright from Australia's
here also.
I ain't worried. I mean, uh...
we're Americans, right?
- This your first time?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
- ... please board immediately.
Triana Island Air
is pleased to announce
the flight from the mainland
has now arrived at Gate 3.
Oh.
- Well, they've all arrived.
- Great. Please, sit down.
- Would you like a drink?
- No, thanks.
Arranging that tournament was actually
a fabulous idea. Really fabulous.
Well, only if the right one is here.
Remember, GeneraI Andreas
asked for a superhuman.
Yes. That is the question.
I saw the American team at the airport.
I think the guy we're after is one of them.
Really?
Very good. Watch the tournament.
If you think he's the one, let me know.
- Absolutely. I will.
- Thank you.
Welcome to the opening
of the 1989 Island Games
InternationaI Karate Championship.
East Bay Labs is proud
to sponsor these games.
As their representative,
I would now like to introduce
the honorary host of this marvellous event,
the distinguished leader of Triana,
GeneraI Andreas.
Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
over the next few days you will see
the battles of modern-day warriors,
courageous men
who will prove their strength and skills
in the spirit of internationaI competition.
Let the games begin.
And now, from America,
Sean Davidson,
three times black belt karate champion.
And his opponent, from Great Britain,
the European karate champion,
Joe Simpson.
Sean Davidson is on the white line
and Joe Simpson is on the red line.
Gentlemen, here. Bow.
To each other, bow. Fighting stance.
Sean Davidson appears to be taunting
Joe Simpson by remaining still.
Good blocks and quick reactions from
Davidson has averted any contact hits.
Continue.
A nice combination by Davidson
gives him a first point.
Ready?
A solid hit by Simpson ties the match.
Whoever gets the next point
will be the winner.
No point.
Despite Davidson's contact hit, it was
a no point. Simpson was out of bounds.
Continue.
Strike point. Winner.
Sean Davidson wasn't going
to leave anything to chance.
He defeated Simpson
with a fast kick to win the match.
Wow, would you look at those two!
I'm gonna get us a table with them, OK?
If he introduces me again
as the karate champion...
- May we join you, my friends and I?
- Yeah.
Guys, come on over for a beer.
Let me introduce you. My buddy Sean.
- Hi.
- Karate champion.
Hi, I'm Susanna.
And this is Powerhouse Jackson.
Oh, Powerhouse!
- Nice to meet you.
- Powerhouse.
I'm Dex.
Kind of the... heartthrob of the group.
- Your best one yet!
- Can we have three beers, please?
- No. Make mine a Coke, if you will.
- Make that two.
- Are you with the tournament?
- We represent the United States.
- Who do you represent?
- Myself.
Yourself? I'm very glad.
Perhaps there is a God.
Thank you. You're very charming.
Hey, Sean, what's up?
Can you keep up with him? OK.
Go.
Hey. An orientaI man, older guy,
and a couple of other guys. What room?
What room?
Upstairs on the right.
Izumo.
Sean.
It's you.
Izumo, what's going on?
What are you doing here?
Who are those people?
Sean! Help me!
Sean!
Help, Sean!
This way, Sean!
Izumo!
What the hell?
This comb has history. Yeah, it's...
Jackson! Jackson.
- I've got to talk to you.
- Sure. Excuse me.
- Come here, man.
- Yeah. How you doin'?
- Later, girls!
- What happened to you?
I'm not sure.
You're a mess.
Look...
I have a master, Izumo.
He raised me since my father's killing
in the way of ninja.
- You're a ninja?
- Yes.
So that explains a few things.
I saw Izumo here.
He was being kidnapped by the ninja.
The ninja. Not again.
I thought ninja only hung out in Japan.
No, they were here.
Look... I don't want you guys
to get involved.
I'm in, buddy.
OK, but what about the tournament?
To me, Izumo is much more important.
- Dr Saxon, sorry for barging in.
- How are we doing, my dear?
He fell for the Izumo disguise.
But he's so good he got away from us.
Perhaps we should use
more direct methods.
No, no, no.
Chan Lee is right in her pursuaI.
If she hasn't ensnared him yet
it's because he's doubly powerfuI,
in body and mind.
I have every confidence in you, Chan Lee.
Bring him back, OK?
Thank you.
- You guys hungry?
- I don't think I want any of this here.
Let's go grab some of that Caribbean food.
Maybe a glass or two of wine, huh?
We could get some dates.
What do you say, guys, huh?
Sounds good, huh, guy?
Wait.
- What is it?
- I don't know.
A feeling.
Who the hell are these guys?
You gotta be kidding.
Well, got no choice.
- OK. Let's spread out.
- Hm.
Right. OK.
Can't believe I'm looking for ninjas.
I thought I stopped doing this
when I left Joe back in the army.
What a damn day.
Where's Izumo? Tell me!
- Sean.
- Jackson. You all right?
- Yeah.
- Hey, guys. I got one. Guess what?
- What are you doing up there?
- I saw where some went. There.
OK, come on down. Let's go.
Right this way.
They're doing something in there
they want nobody to know about.
- We're being watched.
- Yep.
Like they've been waiting for us.
It's all too convenient.
Would someone mind telling me
what's going on?
- It's saiminjutsu.
- Huh?
Way of the mind game.
- Which is?
- We're being manipulated.
I'm here to see the minister's secretary.
- Right through there, please.
- There?
Sir. May I help you?
Yes. Hi, uh... I'm Sean Davidson.
I called your office about Mr Izumo.
- Yes, they told me. Please take a seat.
- Thank you.
I've done some checking for you,
but there's been nothing
on anyone named Izumo
or any Japanese gentleman
entering the country.
No, but I saw him here.
I have reason to believe that he's being
held at East Bay Laboratories.
Please understand. East Bay is a scientific
research centre. It's low-profile.
Dr Saxon is doing
some very valuable work there.
- What kind of work?
- They develop and manufacture drugs.
- Drugs?
- Yes.
The kind that cure people. The kind
that can't be made in the United States.
- Is there a problem?
- No, sir. No problem, everything's fine.
Would you bring me the file
on East Bay Labs, please?
- Excuse me...
- Oh, I'm sorry. I really am very busy.
I have to attend to the minister's business.
- Could you just tell me...
- I am busy. I hope I've been of some help.
Fine. Thank you.
You know, I keep getting the feeling
they're all around us.
Who?
What's up?
I got nowhere
with the minister's secretary today.
Hm. Tell me something new.
Sean, how about if we spoke
to the locaI police?
No, we're gonna need
a more aggressive approach.
Hm. I'll give it a crack anyway.
Who knows?
Maybe they speak my language.
- Thanks. Appreciate it.
- OK.
- Excuse me.
- Address?
Excuse me.
- Excuse me.
- What?
Who can I see about a missing person?
Captain.
Inside.
So none of you guys
have ever seen this man?
Perhaps he doesn't want to be found.
People come here to get away,
from other people,
from financiaI problems, to get married.
Yeah, yeah. Captain,
I think you're starting to jerk me around.
What makes him so speciaI?
Number one,
my friend saw him kidnapped.
And number two, we think
he's being held in East Bay Labs.
East Bay Labs is one of this community's
strongest supporters.
Their business is making drugs,
not trouble.
Well, Captain, baby,
that's kind of a contradiction.
If they're not looking for trouble,
why all the high security over there, hm?
To protect their work from thieves
and prying eyes.
- And...
- I resemble that remark.
Look, Lancelot, here's some money.
Now go see a movie. Cheer up!
- Look, my man...
- I'm not your man.
Now, look. The less straight answers I get,
the more curious I'm gonna be.
I wouldn't follow that route if I were you.
- Are you threatening me?
- Not yet.
Remember, you and your friends
were invited as guests to this island.
- Don't abuse your privilege.
- Or what?
Good day, sir.
You're breathing my air.
Give me back my money.
Invading bacteriaI phages,
penetrating and destroying cells.
Mutating viruses change form so quickly.
Before a vaccine can be invented, they've
changed form and become immune.
This is the basis for the most potentially
dangerous warfare known to mankind.
Germ warfare.
When will you show us your experiment
and stop lecturing?
Excuse me, GeneraI Andreas.
This is not a military sideshow.
This is a precise scientific exercise.
AII I'm asking of you
is just three more days.
Then I'll show you the most
fantastic scientific advancement
ever known to mankind.
Three more days.
That's not too much to ask.
The other guests seem content
to wait for your demonstration.
But I have never been a patient man.
Listen, my impatient man. I've given you
your power and I can take it away.
These nice people seem content to wait.
So you be content.
Relax. Have a nice day.
All right.
Drive.
Chan Lee. How are we doing?
I have never failed you.
He's not like the others. He's ninja.
Why have you chosen him?
He's gonna show people
who live off the miseries of others
that they're vulnerable like anybody else.
I can't see why anyone would want
to stop a cure for disease.
I've seen men do a lot worse things
than that. All right? Just believe me.
We must find out
what they've done with Izumo.
There's a lot of clues. We need
to put it together, make sense out of it.
It's time to pay a visit to East Bay Labs.
- How do we get in?
- Nobody's afraid of flying, are they?
- OK. Do your thing.
- Piece of cake. I'll take care of it.
Come on, Dexter.
Let's go, Junior.
You're mine.
- Can he really do this?
- I hope so.
Junior, come on.
- I'll tell you one thing.
- What?
- It has nothing to do with what you hear.
- OK, come on, do it.
- It's about time.
- Good.
Here we go.
- Wow.
- Boy, there they are.
Two of us have got a ride.
- I'm gonna try and get this truck started.
- OK. We'll get this.
Curtis will wait
and get us out with the truck, all right?
- You still with me, Dex?
- Right behind you, Ace.
Ever flown one of these before, Dexter?
Lots of times.
Whoa... Aah! Whoa...!
When we hit the lab, I'll find Izumo.
You get Curtis inside with the truck.
- Any sign of Curtis?
- Yeah. There he is. And he's cooking.
Sean, is it OK if I go down
and give Mr Jackson a little hello?
I think we'd better keep our minds
on the mission, Dex.
No problem, Sean. It's all under control.
- Sean, I've got a problem!
- Don't panic. Try the gas pump.
The line's burst. I'm going down!
Pull the engine cord.
- It's not catching.
- Keep trying, Dexter.
Come on, baby. Don't do this to me.
OK, you got it.
Sean, I'm losing control.
Push up on the bar and level off.
Now try the engine again.
- Sean, I'm gonna hit!
- Don't quit, Dex. Start that engine.
You did it, Dex.
The engine will never make it.
I've got to try to land on that road.
That road's too rough.
You'll smash that thing apart.
I've got to do something right now.
You're gonna land
on the back of the truck.
- No way! I'll never make it.
- It's your only chance. You've got to try.
- But, Sean...
- Do it, Dexter.
Just relax, Dex. Let the controls flow.
All right. Here I go.
- I don't like this, Sean.
- Careful, Dex. You're going too fast.
- That was too close.
- This is crazy. I can't do it.
Try again, Dex. This time I'll talk you
through it. Circle around.
Last chance, Sean.
The engine's gonna go any second.
Keep your front wheel up.
Steady. Now cut your speed.
Steady. Steady.
Now take her in.
Yeah!
Way to go, Dex.
Thanks, Sean.
Wouldn't have made it without you.
I gotta get to Izumo.
Wait for me outside the lab.
You guys be careful.
- Some landing! Was I good or what?
- Yeah, great.
Sky King, let's dump that baby. We've got
to meet Sean and Izumo outside the lab.
Close the door quietly.
Let's go.
He must have got in OK by now.
Maybe. Let's just hope he found Izumo.
So, shall we go?
Mm-mm. No.
Aaah!
So, you came here as I planned.
Who are you?
- Why'd your men attack me?
- To get you here.
To tickle my fancy.
Curiosity is a reaI dangerous drug,
you know.
So the tournament
was a scam to lure me here.
No. To lure the best one here.
That just turned out to be you.
A ninja.
Is that why you have my master Izumo?
- Yes, I guess you might say that.
- So he's here?
Let's just say
that really doesn't count right now.
What's important is your usefulness to me,
proving the power
and the effectiveness of my new disease.
Boys.
Well, no news is good news.
- OK, Curtis. What now?
- We wait, Junior.
Who are you?
I need some answers.
I know you are ninja.
- So?
- Listen, your life is in terrible danger.
Who else knows about Izumo?
- Why should I tell you?
- I'm here to help.
Please.
My two friends know,
the police and the minister's secretary.
- Now everyone's involved.
- What is going on here?
I'm not sure yet.
- But I'm gonna find out.
- Wait.
Dr Saxon, the minister's secretary is here.
Nice of you to see me at short notice.
We like to help people of the community.
Dr Holger, could you see to it
that our mouse is fed?
It's breakfast time in the lab, you know.
What can I do for you this fine morning?
Doctor, you probably don't realise,
but the minister has concerns about you
and your operation.
He doubts your sincerity.
My sincerity? My dear girI, my whole life's
work is tied up in this project.
Yes, but the question is,
what exactly is that work?
Well, if you don't understand
the nature of my experiment,
one of my scientists could explain it.
No, that's not the point.
We've done some checking.
Er... A certain GeneraI Andreas
was known to InterpoI as a notorious
terrorist, missing for severaI years.
I don't think we could be
talking about the same man.
These deadly virus strains
you've been working with...
With minor modifications, could they not
be usefuI to a man in his line of work?
What is it exactly that you want?
Well, my position has some prestige to it,
but the burdens are enormous
and the salary unfortunately is less so.
Ah. I see.
It's funny you mention it.
Dr Holger and I were discussing
the need for an assistant
to help us further our operations.
Could I put my name up for consideration?
Absolutely. I can't think of anyone
who'd be more qualified.
I'll just, uh... send you over
a retainer cheque tomorrow.
- That'd be fine.
- Great.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Give my regards to the minister, will you?
And thank you so much for coming.
You're a great woman
and I appreciate your advice.
Thank you.
Bye.
She knows.
I warned you. She's excessively ambitious.
My dear boy, we'll just have to do
what we have to do.
Relieve her of that unfortunate ailment.
I'll see to it myself.
It's the minister's secretary.
What has she been doing here?
- Let's get back to the truck.
- OK.
Everything in order. Thank you.
Calm down.
That'll do for now.
Go. Relax.
Electronarcosis. A little something
we developed in the lab. Works well.
- What do you want from me?
- Nothing personaI, my dear boy.
You're just a victim for this experiment.
By the time this gun's effect wears off,
- you will have outlived your usefulness.
- We'll see.
Ah, impatient one, how are you? I trust
this subject meets with your approvaI.
Yes.
Perfect.
Very good. Come, relax.
I'll show you the ultimate test
in designer death.
I'm really worried about Sean.
Me too, but let's give him more time.
Time? Man, he's had enough.
We've got to do something.
I'm beginning to like your attitude.
No more wine, women and song?
That was before.
Time is running out.
We can't afford to waste any more.
And who are you?
- The only one who can help you.
- All right, start explaining.
Your friend has been caught
by the head of East Bay Labs.
He's known as the Cobra and he plans
to kill your friend. He must be stopped.
Unfortunately, my ninja are no longer
loyaI to me. I need your help.
Now we got ninjettes.
Let's talk, sweetheart.
Not so strong, huh, ninja?
Take our soon-to-be-dead friend
to the ship.
If Cobra kills Sean with his virus,
he will prove to Andreas
how powerfuI they can be.
Let me get this straight.
He's selling out to a terrorist?
Exactly.
That's wholesale slaughter.
That sounds like reaI bad news to me.
Hey, don't underestimate that man.
He's not called the Cobra for nothing.
It's your call, Curtis.
OK, darling.
Let's go kick some ass.
We need to head for the docks.
The Cobra
will have injected Sean with the virus.
He'll be taking him to his ship.
Good. He's only just arrived.
But look at the state he's in.
He can hardly walk.
Where are they gonna take him?
Out of here,
so no one will know what Cobra's up to.
- Time to do it.
- Wait.
I go first. No slip-ups.
Cobra's not the forgiving type.
You just get there, ninjette baby.
We'll do the rest.
Curtis!
Get out of my way.
Jerk.
Well done, ninjette baby.
This way.
- Junior!
- Thanks.
- Wait...
- No time to explain.
On the contrary.
There's plenty of time to explain.
- Who's this?
- Cobra's partner.
Shut your mouth. Get away from him.
He's the only one of value.
I said move!
- So it's me you want.
- Uh-huh.
- And no sudden moves.
- You got it.
All right.
- No!
- Sean!
- We don't have much time.
- For what?
To get you the antidote.
No. That electronarcosis stuff
has about worn off.
He zapped you with a virus.
- We've got to get Izumo.
- Sean...
You are a kunoichi?
Yes.
- Hensojutsu?
- I am a master.
Now I see.
- Izumo...
- Izumo was you.
Yes.
I thought I was doing the right thing.
I did not know that they were eviI.
It's time for action. Let's go.
OK.
The minister's secretary
is here to see Dr Saxon.
How can she make herself
into different people so perfectly?
Disguise and illusion. Hensojutsu.
- Hensojutsu?
- It's the ancient art of impersonation.
The kunoichi, the female ninja,
they're masters at it.
Where'd she go?
Machine-gun work?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
- I'm OK.
- Good.
Look, if we don't get that vaccine in time,
you've got to kill me.
- What?
- If it doesn't work...
- It will.
- If it doesn't, and I lose it,
you gotta kill me.
You or Jackson.
Do you understand?
You know what we're up against here.
I have your word?
Yeah. You got it.
OK.
Let's go.
What's going on? Sirens are blazing.
The minister's unhappy.
It's all going crazy.
The Americans escaped...
and GeneraI Andreas is dead.
Andreas is dead.
This could ruin us, you know.
Get me Chan Lee.
The ninjas say
that she helped them get away.
Stupid incompetent idiot!
Well... they're turning against me.
It's happened before,
and I must say to no avaiI.
Alert the ninja.
I think we'll be having company.
And don't screw it up this time!
Shut off those sirens.
Good evening.
- I, er... I thought I might meet you here.
- Ah.
Well, it appears that you're after
much more than just a meeting.
Not at all, Doctor.
Come on.
Your disguise is quite apparent, Chan Lee.
You said your cause
was for the good of mankind.
- My cause is a good one.
- For those possessed by eviI.
I was taking the antidote to the American.
Oh, really? Do what you have to do.
But I'm telling you, you are deluded.
I'm not going to listen to you any more.
You are the snake.
Die!
Take these. I'll meet you at the car.
- Is there...?
- No, just get the hell out of here!
Is everything all right?
All right, Cobra.
Your turn to die.
- One answer. Where's the lab?
- Why?
Just be carefuI of this stuff, will you?
It's dangerous. It's glass.
What is it?
- Uh... It's a urine sample.
- Jesus, don't piss me off!
What is it?
It's viraI antidote. Be carefuI, will you?
Very good, Stretch. Now, again - the lab?
Up those stairs. Up there.
All right.
Oh, shit.
Right here, Stretch.
Oh, no.
Oh, Chan...
Oh, God...
Another illusion you believed in
shattered?
- There's no cure for your disease.
- Give me the damn antidote.
- Sure. I've got all the formulas.
- You won't get away with it.
Really?
But I am getting away with it.
Like I said,
you've outlived your usefulness.
Your mind and soul
over your body.
Remember that, Sean.
Mind and soul over your body.
Cobra.
Hey, Sean. Here's the antidote, man.
I don't need it any more.
- Hey, you OK?
- Yeah.
You know what I went through
to get this for you?
Let's go home.
Hai... ya!
I think you're finished. Let's go, paI.
Look, if we're gonna remain friends,
can't we fight other bad guys,
like robbers, thieves and muggers?
Does it have to be ninjas? You know
how long I've been fighting ninjas?
# There's a shadow
Falling over you and me
# And there's a serpent
Crawling but we cannot see
# You can feel it in the air
Hear it in the night
# There's something out there
Shrinking from the light
# He who hesitates
Will be the first to feel the bite
# In the blinking of an eye
# The cobra strikes
# Strike out against the foe
# Strike out even though you know
# The price you pay
May be your life
# You've got to strike out
While you still can
# Strike out
There'll be no second chance
# Even as we love
# The cobra strikes
# Go to the mirror
Take a look into your eyes
# Can you see it
The fear that keeps you paralysed
# You're afraid to make a move
But you feel it in your soul
# That something out there
Has taken your control
# The longer you delay
The stronger is its might
# And while you turn away
# The cobra strikes
# Strike out against the foe
# Strike out even though you know
# The price you pay may be your life
# You've got to strike out
While you still can
# Strike out
There'll be no second chance
# Even as we love
# The cobra strikes... #