Hotel Sudamerica.
So how have you been?
Do you stiII, uh...
Shh! My wife would kill me.
l switched to birds.
- Birds?
- Birds.
Exotic-- import-export.
- l got my own plane.
- Mmm?
How about you?
StiII writing?
Si. l'm down here
doing a story on the rainforest.
Huh. Poor Santos,
he was in the middle of that shit.
They would stop at nothing.
They had the government
in their pocket.
All they wanted was land--
our land, our rainforest.
But Santos,
he could not stand for it.
He organized the people.
Oh no. Not again.
For the last time, Santos,
get the hell out.
RafaeI Santos--
leader of the rubber tappers,
staged a passive
resistance in Padre
against the cattle ranch company.
Santos-- a symbol today
for environmentaIists
and ecology groups
all over the world--
has been the target
of death threats.
Santos vehemently states,
"We will not allow this deliberate
destruction to continue."
Buenas noches.
Papi!
Papi!  Papi!
Mami, mami!
Papi!
Papi,  que te pasa?
Papi. Ma--  mami!
Mami!
-  Mami!  Mami!
-  Rafael!
To kill a man
in front of his daughter--
that is the work of a coward.
But it is an old story
lndians against rubber tappers,
tappers against lndians
for a piece of land,
cattle ranchers against both,
and buying everything
with big money.
- Yeah, l remember that.
Do you know where
l can pick up a cheap car?
You can take mine.
I don't use it.
- You're gonna give me your car?
- Yes.
Santos vive!
(Santos lives!)
La lucha continua!
(The struggle continues!)
Santos vive!
La lucha continua!
But Rafael Santos never stopped
believing in non-violence.
Although threatened many times...
he and his followers held fast
to the principIes of passive resistance,
teaching us
that to stop the bloodshed
and wanton rape of the land,
we must think not
of the differences that separate us,
but the common interests
that bind us together--
our love of the rainforest
and all the living things in it,
and our need to improve
the impoverished state
of men and women
of this country.
Rubber tappers, lndians,
farmers and environmentalists
must all work together
to help each other
so that our dear
departed friend-- ahem--
Rafael Santos,
leader of the Rubber Tappers' Union,
good father, husband
and friend to the rainforest,
you may rest in peace.
How are you doing?
Fine.
Holding up okay?
- l guess.
Do you want me
to do anything?
lt's okay.
You have done a lot already.
WeII then,
you must've been very close.
Did you see a man?
No, just a policeman.
Policeman?
What policeman?
Just a policeman.
Gloria, have you eaten
anything yet?
Alyssa's been looking for you.
She's in the kitchen. Go.
- Ahem. Hello.
- Hello.
l'm very sorry about your husband.
- You have my condolences, ma'am.
- Thank you.
Do you feel that you know
who killed your husband?
l feel that anybody
who didn't stop it did it.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, l am okay.
Do you want something to eat?
Are you hungry?
Yes.
Yes?
Hello.
l don't think we have met.
l don't think we have.
l'm R.J. O'Brien.
- Alyssa Rothman.
- Pleased to meet you.
So are you here for a visit?
Yeah.
What about you?
- l work here.
- Yeah?
l'm with the Rainforest
Preservation Society.
Oh yeah. What do you--
what do they do?
We're a privately-endowed foundation
that supports Santos's work.
Oh, so you're the good guys
in this whoIe
rainforest enchilada, huh?
lt's just a little bit more than
an enchilada to me, Mr. O'Brien.
Oh.
WeII, see,
as far as l'm concerned,
that's the probIem--
everybody takes this thing too seriously.
I mean, in America
you got the politicians,
you got the singers
and the Hollywood actors
all jumping on the bandwagon
doing speeches
about the poor birds and the bees
in the Amazon.
You know what l mean? lt's just like--
it's like the fucking fashion, you know?
Well, l'm not in Hollywood,
as you can see here.
lt's been a long time
since l've known
that this cause is a lot more
than just the birds and the bees, okay?
- Mm.
- There're people out there with rights,
the right to live the way--
the way that they want.
And Santos and l have been
working to protect that right.
So yes, it is very serious, Mr. O'Brien,
and it's not an enchilada,
which by the way is a Mexican dish,
not a BoIivian.
Well, as l predicted, l offered Nacia
the check and she refused it.
- As you predicted.
- Yeah.
You're much too pure
for the rest of us, Alyssa.
- Oh yes.
- Lucavida wanted to help
and she had the right to say
yes or no.
- l know. You know l didn't mean to--
- l know,
- and that's why l keep you around.
- Yes.
Oh, we're going to be late
for the meeting.
- Do you need a ride?
- Um, no. No, l have my car.
- Okay. Don't be late.
- I won't. Bye.
Gentlemen, l wish to thank you
for your presence here today.
And of course l would like
to thank Mr. Lucavida,
who's been kind enough
to lend us his lovely house
in order that we may discuss
the unfortunate circumstances
surrounding the death
of our dear friend.
A house built with the money
he stole from the rubber tappers.
We're not to blame for the old rivalries
between you-- the tappers--
and the lndian tribes.
The big ranchers--
you destroy everything.
Please.
Our situation is
only going to get worse
unless we learn to coexist within
the economic realities of this country.
Gentlemen, this is our test.
lf we fail, we all lose.
No, l don't accept
as an economic reality
a group of cattIe ranchers
destroying all our rubber trees
so they can export
their meat to the gringos.
We want to know
who killed Rafael Santos first.
Se metio, senor.
Buenos dias.
And who are you?
Well, l'm R.J. O'Brien. l, uh--
l knocked on your door, but there was
nobody there to answer. And, uh--
well, l'm down here doing an article
for an American magazine and--
Shall l call the police?
- l'm sure Mr. O'Brien...
- Yes.
...didn't realize it was my home
into which he was intruding.
Now wait a minute.
You're not Mr. Lucavida?
- Please.
- lt's a pleasure to meet you.
This is not a good time
for an interview.
- No.
- Perhaps l can call you.
Santos vive!
La lucha continua!
-  La lucha continua!
-  Santos vive!
Rafael Santos.
Presente.
lt seems like he was
against progress for your country.
I mean,
he fought against bank loans
for the building of roads,
for the buiIding of dams.
- lt's no wonder he pissed people off.
- He was not against progress.
He was against
the destruction of the rainforest,
against development that
only benefits the big companies
and the powerful
who expIoit us.
He probably pissed off
some landowners, right?
Rafael made a lot of enemies
in his Iifetime.
He's not the first to die
over the rainforest.
He won't be the last.
Que pasa, Aringo.  Que tienes? (What happened?)
Que tienes, Aringo?  Que pasa? (Do you have it?)
Hey hey,  que pasa?
Dios.
No pictures!
- Give me the camera!
Un momento.
l'll give you the film.
Lo siento.
(Sorry)
Aqui aqui aqui.
(Right here.)
Muchas gracias.
The guy's got a bad temper.
The whoIe goddamned roII
of film-- can you believe that?
- We have to go now.
- Oh no, amigos--
no no no, no no no.
Amigos!
The interview is not over yet!
That's probabIy how
you stuck by Santos!
Excuse me, do you know
where Senor Pedrosa is?
lf l could ask you a few questions.
Who do you think kiIIed Santos?
I mean, given the fact
that he was asking for it.
You want to be more carefuI
choosing your words, Mr. O'Brien.
Well, let's face it.
The guy was a pain in the ass.
- He was giving everybody trouble.
- Mmm, not unlike yourself.
He got the wrong people angry.
What wrong peopIe
are you talking about?
Well, that's hard to tell--
cattle ranchers, authorities,
lndians.
Who knows?
And what about
the timber industry?
You guys weren't very happy
with him either, were you?
The timber industry is older
than the rubber business.
Yeah, but you cut down the forest,
you destroyed the trees.
Ah, no more than you destroy
your hair when you cut it.
Yes, but what are you gonna do
when your resources are depleted?
Ah, that will only happen
if we become greedy.
- Quieto. Quieto. (Be calm.)
-  No!
- Nobody's gonna hurt you.
- Step back!
Put down your weapons.
- Nobody's gonna hurt you.
l'll kill him.
Okay. Let's go.
Let's go.
No pictures.
Hey, stop it.
Alto!
You're gonna kill him!
Take them.
What about
the fucking phone call?!
Do you wanna tell me
what that was all about?
Exc-- can you hear--
excuse me, can you fucking hear me?!
Huh?
You speak English?
Habla espanol?
Como estas?
Ah, bien. Bien.
Fuck me.
What?
What the fuck?
What the fuck is this?
Mr. O'Brien.
What do you know
about your friend in your cell?
My friend?
Mm-hmm.
Well, he's my long-lost lndian brother.
What do you think?
He attempted
to escape with you.
No.
No, he took me--
he fucking took me hostage.
What was your business, my friend,
with Senor Pedrosa?
- Hmm?
Look, do you have any charges
to bring against me
or are you just jerking my chain
to justify a day's pay?
Don't talk to me like that, all right,
Mr. Ponytail?
Don't talk to me like that!
The man who was arrested
with you yesterday, my friend,
is the murderer
of Rafael Santos.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
No, l'm not kidding you.
l'm just as interested
in his capture as you are.
Mr.--
Mr. O'Brien, that's unlikely.
You're not cooperating too much.
- What the fuck do you want me to say?
- You know, you're gonna be my guest.
Guard, take him
back to his cell. Now!
You can't fucking do this, man.
l am an American reporter working here.
CaII AIyssa Rothman
with the Rainforest Society.
She's a very good friend of mine.
Djamori?
Somebody call
the American ambassador!
l am an innocent American
being heId against my wiII.
Someone caII
the goddamn ambassador!
Hello?!
That's him.
Somebody call the ambassador!
Look, you might as weII
let him go. He's harmless.
Yeah.
- HeIIo!
- Sanchez.
- Si, Mayor.
- Take him out.
Alyssa!
Reo.
Take a seat.
Asientos, senores.
Did the suspect
know Santos personally?
l cannot comment
on that question.
Which tribe is he from
and did he have any accomplices?
That wiII come out
of our legal investigation.
Then, what-- what kind of questions
are we supposed to ask?
Do you think
you know why he did it?
His reasons will be brought
to Iight at his triaI,
but in the meantime we have
his fuII signed confession.
Bullshit.
And solid evidence,
including witnesses,
and everything--
everything to convict him.
What if he was framed?
That's all.
Go.
- Yeah.
Do it! Whoo! Yeah!
Yeah.
Si! Oh, si.
Whoo!
Ay, mi amor!
Thank you.
Djamori gets
arrested for questioning
and two days later he's dead?
l don't believe this.
lt's true.
But you know exactly
what's gonna happen if--
lf they don't have a trial for this,
They're just gonna conveniently
Iet everything just bIow over.
You're probably right, Alyssa,
but the police seem convinced.
- Oh, the police?
- Mmm.
Since when did you start placing
so much faith in the authorities?
Since l have
a great deal of work to do.
Now why don't you run along
and go find another righteously
indignant souI to rant to?
Well, because l'm not done ranting
to this righteously indignant soul.
- All right.
Sometimes we have to--
we must work together.
We have to compromise in the interest
of getting something done.
RafaeI Santos
did not die in vain.
Ahem.
So are you here to see someone?
Uh, yeah.
Actually, l'm here to see you.
l wanna thank you
and, um, as you can see,
l'm unarmed and l'm not dangerous.
And I just thought maybe
we could talk like good boys and girls.
Okay then.
Let me ask you this.
Why did you follow me
to Lucavida's house?
- l followed you?
- Yes, you did.
And l didn't like it. Father Benacio
caIIed together that meeting
and he did it to bring together
the people at odds over Santos's death
and the people concerned
about the rainforest.
l'm all in favor of proper relations.
Mr. O'Brien,
you have absolutely nothing to say
that holds any interest to me.
Well, l think l do.
I think the guy who's in jaiI
for killing Santos is innocent.
What makes you think that?
Well, it's a gut feeling,
but, uh...
l have some ideas.
Sandra, hi. This is R.J. O'Brien.
You remember meeting him--
l remember him
from Mr. Lucavida's house.
So what brings you here,
Mr. O'Brien?
- Well, actually l was--
- Well, actually-- l'm sorry.
Um, Mr. O'Brien was
in jail with Djamori
and he aIso beIieves
Djamori was framed.
And why do you say that?
Did the lndian say something to you?
WeII no.
He didn't say anything,
but l thought that perhaps
with your connections
that we could get
an interview through the police,
- maybe talk out of his own safety.
- I'm afraid that is not possibIe.
- Why?
- The lndian is dead.
He's dead?
He hanged himself last night
in his cell.
Unbelievable.
What did they do,
slip him a pre-knotted noose?
l agree with him 100%.
l mean, this whole thing
is just way too convenient.
That may very well be,
but who's gonna challenge the police?
l'll challenge the police,
but l've gotta have more information.
l don't know the first thing
about this guy.
Well, what l know is that
he's from the Zingari tribe
and their territory's way up
in the highlands.
WeII, then I guess
an excursion is in order.
l hate to burst your bubble,
Mr. O'Brien,
but you're gonna
be like a flea on a gorilla.
The rainforest is
no place for a gringo.
Well, thanks for the advice.
l guess Santos is gonna become
a worId martyr for this one.
He was a bit of a publicity hound,
wasn't he?
No, not really.
l mean, he just realized
that there was a connection
between the rubber tappers' struggle
to save their way of Iife
and the world's concern
for the ecoIogy.
So the pubIicity
that he generated
was basicaIIy just
to pull the two together.
Mmm, pure at heart.
- No!
- What?
No, they're not supposed
to be burning out here.
Alto!  Alto!
-  Alto!
- Watch out, watch out, watch out!
Ayudame!
- What's going on?
- Somebody set her house on fire
and her son's still inside.
Wait. Wait!
Shit.
-  Como se llama?
- Antonio.
Antonio.
Come on, Antonio. Come on, baby.
Come on, come on! Come on!
Come on, Antonio. Breathe! Come on!
- Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on.
Come on, breathe. Come on.
Come on! Come on, breathe!
Do you hear me?! Come on.
- Come on, please! Oh God.
Come on, come on,
come on, please.
Please please please.
lt's all right.
lt's okay.
There he is right there. See?
Let's wait for the police to leave.
Adelante.
Ataninde,
un momento por favor.
My name is Alyssa Rothman.
We met at Lucavida's.
l'm with the Rainforest Society,
and we wouId very much Iike
- to speak to you about Djamori.
- I was the one
who was arrested with Djamori.
I don't think he kiIIed Santos.
Ahem. Um,
can l ask you a few questions?
Uh, excuse me.
l'm trying to help!
No--  no escuchas?
l'm trying to help.
Scratch that idea.
- Come on.
- What are you doing?
Come on,
we're following him.
We're-- no, we're not.
- This is no time to give up.
- l'm not giving up.
I just don't think it's right
that you go follow him-- hey!
- Sorry.
- Asshole.
Where in the hell is it?
l have no idea.
Santos said he was there once,
but the only thing he said was
that it was a Iong trip.
Nos estan siguiendo?
Si. Ahi estan.
lt looks like we're up the creek
in more ways than one.
Son of a bitch!
- Shh. Shh-shh!
- What?
- Quiet. Be quiet.
l just heard something.
Shh. Shh.
What the hell.
Ow.
- God.
You're lucky it didn't go
through the bone.
l am really scared.
Look,
those lndians
didn't have any guns.
Whoever shot us
came from back there.
l'm sorry.
l'm sorry, l'm sorry, l'm sorry.
The Zingari territorial boundaries.
See?
Come on.
Shh.
Right.
l think we lost them.
All right, you wait here.
- l'm gonna see if l can find the river.
- No. No, l don't--
Just wait here one second!
God.
- Why are you following me?
Hmm?
This is my territory.
You could've saved me a trip if you'd
answered my questions about Djamori.
Djamori was killed
by a white man and l can kill you
whenever l fucking want to.
Camina!
Hold on.
Please, his shoulder
has been hurt.
Is there anything
that you can give him for it?
Si.
You know Djamori.
Do you think he killed Santos?
Yeah, he could have done it, maybe not.
But either way, he's dead.
Yeah, but if we don't
find out the truth,
more people are just gonna
keep getting kiIIed.
l don't believe
the white man's truth anymore.
Toma.
l can't believe
l've lost my fucking camera!
You didn't.
lt's right here.
You are quite the Girl Scout,
aren't you?
Brownie.
Bring the prisoner.
Two blows to the head,
covered up with false hair.
But what killed him was the blow
to the back.
He burst his kidneys.
White man's truth.
l'm sorry.
I'd Iike to take some pictures.
l'd like to prove he didn't kill himself.
Did you know Rafael?
l spent five years working
outside the reservation
for the government,
for the Zingari tribe.
That's when l met Santos.
You were his partner, right?
He knew how to use the law
to protect the lndians
and the rubber tappers.
l know how to protect
the movement from outside threats.
And?
And he failed.
He died.
He failed before he died,
when he decided to fight
the exploiters with empathy--
passive resistance bullshit.
Well, it seemed to work
aII right for Gandhi.
You don't happen to know who
might've put this hole in me, do you?
There's a lot of fools
Iooking for goId.
You stole the blankets!
lt's the middle of the night.
Come back to bed.
We are so different.
You're here for a story
and l'm here because l care.
l bet if all the logging
and all the burning stopped tomorrow,
you'd find another cause.
And l guess you don't hold
anything sacred, huh?
l guess you've just seen
so much in this worId
that you've deveIoped
this profound philosophy
that there's nothing worth
caring about. Is that it?
No.
- l don't care about a lot.
- Mmm?
l care about you.
You don't know me.
No, but l want to.
Good morning.
Thank you for the ride back.
We probably wouldn't have found
our way by ourseIves.
- Morning.
- Come on.
Hey, you wanna have a little drink
before we part company?
l don't think so.
Ataninde, please, do you have
any idea who killed them?
Santos had many enemies.
lt could have been anyone.
Yeah. Well, the arrow indicates
that it was an Indian.
Appearances can be deceiving,
Mr. Magazine Writer.
You shouId know that.
You write the truth every day.
Where-- do you know
where we can get this film developed?
Yeah, we have a makeshift
Iab at the office
that we use for our newsletter.
Oh, God, you're so beautiful
when you say that.
Do women in New York
actually fall for these lines?
All the time.
Funny.
lt sounds pretty cliche to me.
Can l come in?
l've been trying to get ahold of Sandra,
but I can't find her anywhere.
So how is it going?
Really good.
These are beautiful!
Are you gonna use
all of these in your article?
You can bet
your sweet ass l am.
You are so charming.
That's great.
- l meant it affectionately.
Oh.
Alyssa: We have work to do.
- Perdon.
Oh-oh-oh, shoot shoot,
I have to caII Sandra.
- Now?
- Yes, now. Just real fast.
- Shall l get horizontal or--
- Yes, you shouId.
- 213.
l cannot see
Why do you want me?
Yeah.
l cannot see
Why you look so...
Mmm.
Want me?
Don't move.
You should have left
after the funeral
like your friends.
This is none of your business.
Tie him up.
Listen, we can--
we can make a deal here.
Uh, you can have the pictures
as far as l'm concerned.
l'll get out of this fucking country
anyway. Your food sucks!
- HeIIo?
Hi. lt's me Alyssa.
We just got back and R.J. managed
to get ahoId of some information
that proves that Djamori
didn't kiII himseIf.
You know,
I was getting ready
to arrest you myself,
but apparentIy some fucking
drug dealer got you before l did.
l don't like you.
Listen, this isn't that important to me.
- l wanna get the fuck--
- l don't like you!
l never liked you.
l don't like this fucking ponytail!
l don't like it!
Fuck you.
Don't ever talk to me
like that, gringo maricon.
- Don't forget! Never.
Alyssa, where are you?
l'm calling from his hotel.
His hotel.
AIyssa, do me a favor
and come to the office.
You get to the office right away, okay?
I'II meet you there.
- l wanna hear more about this.
- But this is good news, isn't it?
lt's great news. l just don't wanna
discuss it on the phone.
Now go to the office.
Okay, l'll be right there.
Bye.
Shoot.
Good luck.
- R.J., come on, open up.
What are you doing?
Come on, open the door.
R.J., are you all right?
- Come on.
- Jesus.
Oh my God.
- Move!
- l'm trying.
l'm trying.
Let me get this.
Come on!
Who would do--
who did this?
Valdez and a bunch
of fucking cops!
Valdez?
And now what the fuck
are we gonna do?
All right. Let's go back to my office.
Sandra will know what to do.
Yeah? Well, we need somebody
who is not afraid of the cops.
Well, believe me, Sandra is not.
Fuck! Unbe-fucking-lievable!
- Oh my God, wait. Wait wait wait.
- What?
- Oh Jesus.
Sandra knew about the bomb
in your room.
- How do you know?
- I don't know.
lt's just the way that she was reacting
when l was talking to her on the phone.
Are you sure you're not reading
something into this
because this is our last chance?
l don't know.
You were right.
Lucavida is paying everybody,
incIuding your boss Sandra.
- Ataninde, please listen to me.
- Enough.
No! Ataninde, no.
l will not shut up, okay?
Listen to me. Listen to me, okay?
There's no place else that we can turn.
- And we need your help, all right?
- AII right, Iisten.
They're aII in this together. Lucavida
is financing the whole forest operation.
What does that gotta do with me?
So you're saying that Santos'
death's got nothing to do with you
and that Djamori's death
got nothing to do with you?
Look, you white people
mind your own business,
and I'II take care
of my people, okay?
Don't you realize
we're on the same freaking side?
Can you hear me?
You know, you're a fucking hypocrite,
you know that?
-  Concha su fucking madre!
- Stop it, okay?
- Just take it easy.
- Shit!
Calm down.
Calm down, all right?
You guys are going too far.
You are both
responsible for this.
lt has cost us a lot of money.
I think I know
where they might be.
- l'll get the bastard.
- No more vioIence.
Senor VaIdez, wouId you mind
waiting outside for me, please?
Why not?
And you listen to me.
l've done my best for you,
but I cannot--
lt's your job.
Just do it, hmm?
Tell him to bring more if he can.
Yes, as soon as possible. Okay.
Some of them already left.
A lot of good it's gonna do us.
- At Ieast they wiII protect you.
- What we need right now is a plane,
not a protest movement.
Holy fuck!
- Damn it!
- What?
I had Chato's number
the whole goddamned time.
- He's got a plane.
- Who's this Chato?
- Yeah. Hello.
- Chato?
- Chato, it's R.J.
- Oh, how are you, my friend?
- Where you been?
- Listen, man, straighten up.
This is some serious shit,
all right?
I need to get a pIane
out of here right now.
No no, l can't--
l can't do it, man.
Man, there are people
trying to kill me.
l'm tied up at this moment.
Chato, Iisten to me,
this is no fucking joke!
All right? And my life is
on the line here. l need your help.
Okay okay. l meet you
at the embarcadero in Bella Vista.
Remember, Bella Vista.
Don't move!
Don't fucking move.
- You two, sit! You two, sit!
- Alyssa: Get off of me.
She doesn't know a fucking thing.
lt's you who we want.
- The embassy knows every fucking thing.
- Shut up!
God damn you, pig!
Do you like that?
- Good.
- The fucking embassy.
Take him away.
The embassy!
Don't try anything.
l'll blow his brains out.
The American embassy knows everything.
You guys are in deep shit.
AII right, aII right,
this is a police matter!
And anyone-- anyone--
who tries to interfere
will be arrested.
Now move!
You don't hear me? Get out!
Bring Nacia.
And you stay there.
Camina!  Camina!  Camina!
Come on!
Now move!
- Or she comes with me.
- Don't move!
Shut up! Move!
Move!
Muevase, carajo!
Sueltala!
Come here. Get up!
Get away from him!
This is the last time!
Get out!
lmbeciles!
- Go!
Get out! Move!
Get out.
l'm gonna kill all of you.
Now move!
Move!
Get away from them.
Now! Get out!
We are not moving.
Get away from there!
Don't you understand?
Alyssa, get out of the line.
What are you looking for?
Get out.
- Get out.
- AIyssa!
Out! Get out!
We are not moving!
Do you wanna die, bitch?
Is that what you want?
- You wanna die, bitch?
- Alyssa!
Die!
- No!
- You fuck!
Quieto, mierda!
You son of a bitch!
Move!
Fuck you!
Stupid girl.
l'm gonna fucking kill you!
Bring him!
Mierda.
- Ataninde: Valdez?
Stop!
All right.
Tell them to drop the weapons.
Let them go.
- Relax.
- Drop your weapons.
Drop the weapons.
- Now relax.
- You reIax.
- You relax, motherfucker.
Let's go!
lt's all right. Shhh.
All right, we're gonna make it.
Come on, come on,
give her to me.
Hurry!
Where are you going?
If you go back there,
they're gonna kill you.
Crazy fucking lndian.
Come on, hurry up!
Forget about him. He's dead.
Okay, buddy,
anyplace you want.
We're going home.
We're going home now.
Everything's gonna be all right.
- Mm.
WouId you-- wouId you
promise me something?
Hmm?
What?
Write about what you feel,
not about what you've seen.
Okay?
Alyssa?
l'm sorry, my friend.
Come take my hand
Show me the way
With you, l understand
What words cannot explain
Just the touch of your love
And l know it all
l can stand on the edge
l'm not afraid to fall
Take me to the place
Where we collide as one
Where no one knows
The look on my face
OnIy you see
the woman l've become
Take me to the star
Where children can be free
Where l found you
And you found me
ln a secret sanctuary
Come be my knight
l'll be your sword
Come be my slave
l'll be your lord
Come be my devil
And l'll be yours
l'll be your...