The empire of Izmer
has long been a divided land.
Ruled by the Mages,
an elite group of magic users.
The lowly commoners, those without
magic, are little more than slaves.
Izmer's young empress, Savina,
wishes quality and prosperity for all.
But, the evil Mage, Profion,
has other intentions.
We're are not.
Yes!
At last.
Come Damodar.
Release him.
You are mine now.
Come to me.
Yes. I told you it could be done.
You have the power of the immortals.
You can control dragons.
- With the dragon army at my command,
I can crush the Empress and control
what is rightfully mine!
You don't like it, do you? Good.
I can use every ounce
of your rage. Come on. Follow me.
Follow me!
I said follow me!
What now, my lord, Profion?
- We shall have to modify our plans.
Summon the high council of Mages
immediately.
They are about to learn something
Of our young Empress,
that may give them pause for thought.
- It will be done.
I'm telling you this' gotta be some
twisted magic experiment gone wrong.
Why is it every time something bad
happens, you gotta blame the Mages.
Well, when was the last time you saw
a river catch on fire? You think they
care if anyone got hurt? I'd just
love to find a way to give those
Mages some payback.
- Oh yeah. Ridley the Savior.
That'll be the day. Look, Ridley.
Things are the way they are and
there's nothing you can do to change
it. Ok? You got your haves and your
I'm telling you this' gotta be some
twisted magic experiment gone wrong.
Right about now we gotta get paid.
The magic school.
- The what? The magic school?
Are you crazy?
- We'll break into. There's anything.
'Cause the fire, it won't be guarded.
- No.
Think of the challenge Snails.
Think of what we could find in there.
If we pull this off, we'd be the envy
of every thief in Sumdall.
Trust me.
And why would the Empress try to
disband this counsel? It's a concept
I find difficult to believe.
- Now Azmath, your loyalty
is commendable. But we've all watched
the Empress' growing up. We have all
heard her views on what she considers
to be the injustices of this land.
But she is just a young woman.
Young people speak from the heart.
Not he mind. In time, with our
counsel, she will come to understand
why things cannot be changed.
- Maybe so. But, is that a risk you are
willing to take? Her revolutionary
ideas have already taken root among
the people.
In time her influence will grow.
As the months go by, she will learn to
master the powers of her scepter.
And when she does, I have no doubt
that she will use it to enforce
her changes upon us.
- Then, what do you propose, Profion?
I humbly ask that we vote
to remove the scepter
from the Empress' control.
So that government in Izmer
Will remain secure.
Remove the scepter, which looms above
our heads and destroy
the threat of revolution forever!
And if she does not agree?
- Then...
then her true intentions
will become clear.
And the we will be forced to do
whatever we must to protect
the strength and the unity of Izmer.
What say you?
How could he get the council persuade?
- He plays on the fears of the others.
Their fears of change.
- Yes, I know, Vildan. But, the changes
I propose are for the good of the
people. All people deserve
to be free and equal,
whether commoner or mage.
I know this within the depths
of my soul. And if necessary,
I would die to make that the way
Izmer is run.
What can I do to stop Profion?
- You must outsmart him.
Over the past years, I have been
searching for an ancient
artifact called the Rod of Savrille.
It holds the same powers
as your scepter. With one difference.
It controls Red Dragons.
If you could obtain it,
you could relinquish your scepter and
still have protection against Profion.
I must have that Rod of Savrille!
With one wave of it
I will topple her and bring down
That useless council of idiots
with her.
- What is your wish, My Lord?
Pay a visit to the Magic School.
And see our friend Vildan.
Persuade him to give you the scroll
of which he speaks.
And bring it here to me.
And Damodar? Make sure that he's
No longer around to give
our young Empress anymore good advice.
Come my friend.
Ridley, why's it gotta be so high?
- Snails, let go of me.
Can't we just rob the first floor next
time? Why don't we just rob God?
Come on.
- You said this was going to be easy?
No. I said it wasn't impossible.
- That's the same thing you said when
we robbed that house. Who'd he catch?
Who'd he beat from the waist down? Me.
Are you gonna jump?
- Gonna catch me?
Yeah!
- Promise?
I promise. Now jump.
- All right.
Sorry. I thought I heard something.
You did. Me hitting the ground.
That is a big dragon.
Now we're talking.
All right. Let's get to work.
I already told you, Marina.
The Empress can't use her scepter for
dragon control or Profion will paint
her as a tyrant to the council.
Profion must be made to expose himself
to them. Dammit, I know it's here.
Where is it?
- It should be right here.
You're sure you put it in its place?
- I'm sure.
Sure, are you? Why is it filed here
among these volumes on alchemy?
It belongs in dracology. Now then,
where is it? I know I've got it
somewhere. Ah yes. This was it.
Mariana. You must stop doodling. The
Empress only has 3 days the council
forces her to relinquish her scepter.
- I'm sorry.
But you must be more serious.
- I know. But, I feel I should be doing
more than shelving books.
- I understand, Marina. But, you must
learn to be patient to maintain focus.
That is the best help you can
provide right now.
- I suppose you're right.
I never saw a scroll so hard
to decode. It’s protected by very
ancient magic. Marina,
fetch me some Manticore wing.
What's that?
- Dragon tooth.
Put it back. Put it back.
- Ok. What about a gold dragon tooth?
It’s too big. Put it back.
Hey, Snails. Snails.
Here.
- What'd you do that for?
Pick it up. Come on.
- Ain't got enough of these at home?
Look at this.
We're gonna be rich.
Ridley? You know how much we could
get for one of these?
Snails! Don't touch that!
One of the lab creatures must have not
loose again. Go and check on it.
All right.
Snails, relax.
It’s an illusion.
- Ok. I knew that.
Now, don't touch anything else.
- All right.
What are you doing?
- The cleaning crew.
Dirty.
- Cleanup crew is more like it.
You're thieves trying to rob us.
She must have put some kind of holding
spell on us with that bracelet!
It’s the only way she can get guys.
- I’d have to put a feeble-minded spell
on myself to want to take you home.
- That was funny.
You're going to the city dungeons.
- That wasn't.
Thank you when they cut my head off.
- You should.
It'd be an improvement.
There's that superior intelligence
you mages are so famous for.
Speaking of intelligence. What kind of
genius would break into magic school?
He'd have to be really stupid. Or...
- Or what?
Well... Lester!
If you don't tell me which scroll
it is...
I'll have to kill you painfully.
- Never!
The Chief of the Crimson Brigade!
To the street of Sumdall!
Follow them, you fools!
Where are we going? Hey! Nice trick.
- Hey, no! The other way!
Watch out!
Lady, please stop to listen.
Escapes are our bread and butter.
...oughta-
Nice lid.
- You shouldn't have done that.
Shut that door!
Stop him!
- In that fifth? That's disgusting!
Post brigades
at every sewer entrance and exit.
I want them found.
Now.
Marina of Pretensa, student mage...
I don't believe that.
- Better believe it.
They hang on it to us.
- No, on you, thieves.
Me not. As aristocrate, mage...
- An insignificant mage, totally
dispensable, practical worthless.
- That's ridiculous!
I clear it up. I can't clear it up.
To whom I should explain?
Right! They put you into prison and
torture you, until you confess.
Let us hold together, you heard it,
we're companions.
Ok! Come on!
You allow a slip of a girl to escape
you with the scroll. And now, Norda,
the Empress' finest tracker,
is in pursuit.
And you tell me not to concern myself?
It was a mistake.
It will not happen again.
Now there, you are right.
And here's why.
Just a friend I'm sending along
For the ride.
A gentle reminder
not to make any more mistakes.
The moment you deliver me the rod,
I'll ensure that he...
It vacate the premises.
Now. May I suggest that once you two
have become fully acquainted,
you follow the Empress' tracker,
Norda. She happens to be good
at her job. She will lead you
to our missing friends
and the scroll.
- And this time, Damodar,
don't fail me.
So, if we find the rod,
the Empress heaps us with gold. Huh?
Why don't you try and rise above
being a dwarf? This isn't about gold.
It’s about saving our empire.
- Empire?
Who cares about the empire? You mages
are the only ones who benefit from it.
Oh really? That's an interesting
sentiment from a guy who steals
things for a living.
- Have you ever heard of honor amongst
thieves? We might live outside the
law, but we respect each other.
Unlike a bunch of back-stabbing mages.
- That is just the sort of
half-baked illiterate drivel that
proves commoners really are common.
That's it. We'll go into hiding for
a while. She'll find the rod herself.
Fine.
I thought you were leaving.
- You mind if we eat first?
No. Be my guest.
You know, those red marks there look
like the locks my father used to put
on plans for his carriages.
- This is an ancient scroll,
not a blueprint for a buggy.
- You don't know what you're doing, so
you might as well let me have a look.
- Give that back!
Let's see. He used to put his fingers
like this. And he would say something
like Alinor sala. What was that word?
- Bidet.
Bidet? Bedarra! Bedarra.
Alinor salla bedarra!
You can't blame me for trying.
At least l...
See that there?
I knew that boy had talent.
Alinor salla bedarra.
Do not let them escape or you will
suffer a fate far worse
than that inflicted upon me.
I lie on the floor. On the back.
Hands and feet bound like a pig.
This Orc appears to stab me
with a stick. Huh!
Hopeless situation. I said to myself:
Do I have anything to lose?
So, I take my spear
and throw him towards my enemy.
Really lovely.
An elf? You are kidding?
You know, the hook on an elf is,
they are too skinny.
No, my dear,
a fifty pound dwarf, that will do.
With hair on her chin
that you can hang on to.
- No, thanks.
Excuse me, little man.
Hi. Are you looking for somebody
in particular?
Or, are you just looking
for somebody?
Actually, I'm looking for someone
just like you.
What a coincidence. 'Cause I was
looking for someone just like you.
We gotta celebrate. Bartender?
Give me a bottle of your best wine.
Make that your cheapest.
Wait.
I need the girl.
Bring me that girl!
- No time for a romance.
What?
- Come on!
Wait! I'm falling in love.
- With an elf? They almost think,
humans are a kind of funny stuff!
Ok. Let's get Ridley out of here.
That wraith must have been defective.
- He seemed pretty reliable to me.
Ridley?
It’s Damodar, man. He's onto us.
- Yeah, with what we walked into,
everyone's going to be onto us.
- What do you mean, everybody?
Tell him what you got us into.
- Me? But you...
Yeah. Tell me what you got us into.
According to the wraith inside the
scroll, the rod we're looking for
caused the Great War.
- Oh. Is that all?
Have you lost your damn mind? Huh?
What does this rod do?
- Maybe to control Red Dragons.
This sounds like a bad idea to me.
- It gets better. This map leads to a
Dragon Temple. In order to get in,
we need the Eye of the Dragon from the
Guildmaster of the Thieves Guild
in Antius City.
Zilus? Get! No way!
- I know she's crazy, but she keeps
going on about Profion and the Empress.
- Profion?
They can take care of themselves.
I suggest we lay low, let the whole
thing blow over, come back, rob
everybody. That's our plan. Let's go.
There's one more small problem.
Problem? What's the problem, Ridley?
I kind of committed us to find it.
Ridley?
How could you do something like that?
I can't believe this. I can't...
This is our big chance, huh?
Let's rob the magic school.
That's what you said to me, right?
This is dumb! Dumb! Dumb! Dumb! Dumb!
You know what?
I got a new name for dumb! Ridley!
This is the Ridleyest thing...
Snails? I'll understand if you
don't wanna go.
What do you mean I can't go?
Really, Ridley?
All I'm saying is that, don't you
think that's just a little bit out of
our league? Just a little bit?
- Snails, listen.
This Dragon-Eye we're supposed to get?
It’s a ruby the size of your fist.
I don't.
A ruby the size of my fist?
- Yeah. So we'll use her to help us
get it. And we'll take off.
We'll make a fortune.
Trust me.
I hate when you say that!
Oh Ridley, I'm going to regret this.
- Ha! I knew you'd come through for me!
Don't touch me. Ok, just a little bit.
We're in. How about you?
I don't see what choice I have.
Just tell me one thing!
If I help, who is going to pay me?
We'll worry about that later.
That's a terrible way to do business.
Ridley? Check it out.
Let's go.
Snails.
Ok.
Listen. We're looking for esteemed
Guildmaster Zilus. We thought
perhaps you'd know him.
- The only thing I know is, you oughta
take your business out of town before
you end up with the words
"Outsiders Not Appreciated" branded
right where your nose used to be.
Get it?
Thanks for your time!
If I ain't drinking,
you sure ain't shopping. Come on!
There you are! Where have you been?
- Don't look at us.
Who's been shopping? Is that
three-eyed hyper bastard watching us?
All right. If we follow him, he'll
probably lead us right into the guild.
There he goes.
Come on!
Elwood, we'll go in.
You keep a look out.
Nice.
Isn't that Tony?
- The guy that kidnapped.
All right. Let's go find Zilus.
- That won't be necessary. Like I said,
outsiders not appreciated.
- You're talking to us? We're confused.
Your third eye was looking
at somebody completely different.
Take him away!
Where do you think they took Snails?
- He'll be fine. Just let me talk.
So, this is it, huh?
Everything a thief strives for?
Yeah.
You must be Zilus. Ridley Freeborn.
Practitioner of the larcenist crafts.
Member in good standing with the
Sumdall guild. It’s a pleasure
to meet you.
- A fellow thief.
Well, the pleasure is all mine.
- See?
Sumdall, eh? How is old Sumdall?
That's a pretty tough town, isn't it?
All those mages.
- We get by.
Yes, I guess you must be very
accomplished to have such a precious
morsel travelling with you.
So what might I do for you?
- The unity of our kingdom...
We understand you have the Dragon-Eye.
- We desperately need it.
Yes well, I'm always happy
to help a fellow thief.
Have you ever heard of
the Antius Guild Maze?
Of course. Every thief heard of it.
- Wonderful.
You'll know that the Eye of the Dragon
is the prize at the center of my
guild maze, won't you? You finish
the maze, you win the prize.
Has anyone ever finished it before?
- Uh, no.
They all died trying.
But look on the bright side.
At least the prize is still there.
Good health. And jolly good luck.
This is a good one, Ridley.
40 seconds.
- 1 minute.
They bet on whether or not he lives?
- Au contraire, precious morsel.
They're betting on
how long before he dies.
Be careful, Ridley!
Oh my.
Very clever. But is it clever enough?
The game ain't over yet.
Uh!
Very light on his feet, isn't he?
What kind of vault is that?
I think she wants to visit her friend.
Nice.
Yes, yes, yes! Very clever. Well done.
You were absolutely amazing.
- Thank you.
No, no. Thank you. You know, I’ve
waited 1 5 years for somebody to come
along and pick that lock. I knew that
the man that could get through that
maze alive would be able to get into
that vault. And now, here he is.
Then man. You. So, why don't you give
me what's rightfully mine?
What about honor amongst thieves?
Oh, what a romantic notion.
Do you honestly believe I could have
amassed the wealth I have if I worried
about honor? Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
So, pretty boy. If you don't want Hugo
here to come rearrange
your features for you,
I suggest you just give it up.
Who the hell is he?
Who the hell are you?
Listen. I don't know who you are,
but be prepared for a lesson in pain.
You must be joking.
- I never joke...
when mages trespass in my guild!
This is the map you're after.
Clear a path and I'll put it out.
Do it.
Ridley!
Marina!
You ok?
- We gotta save Marina.
Wait! What about the dwarf?
- You get the dwarf, I'll get the girl.
Wait! How come I always gotta get
the dwarf? Damn!
Marina!
- Ridley. We have the Dragon's Eye.
Let's just sell it in Sumdall.
- We're not leaving without Marina.
You're gonna risk all for a mage?
- Listen, Snails...
What?
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
Hey. It’s you. Hi.
- You know her?
We're acquainted.
- That elf you were drooling over?
Well, I wouldn't put it that way.
But, yeah. That's her. Pretty, huh?
They all look alike to me.
- Silence!
Where's the girl?
- None of your business.
Human.
It is my business to arrest you and
Marina of Pretensa. And to take you
and the scroll you stole back
to the Empress of Izmer.
Oh. You're the law, are you?
I should have known.
One of your fellow lawmen, the Chief
of the Crimson brigade beat you to the
punch. He just took off with Marina.
- Damodar.
Yeah, that's him.
- Only he's not working for the law
anymore. He's working for Profion.
He's the one you want. Not us.
Your Majesty.
Yes, Norda? Have you found the scroll?
- No, your highness.
It seems Profion
also seeks the rod.
- But how could he know?
I do not know, my lady. Damodar has
captured Marina of Pretensa
and the scroll. But, I have her
companions in my custody.
What is your command?
Seek Damodar out.
We need that rod.
The counsel demands my response
imminently.
Norda, please hurry.
Our time is running out.
As you wish.
Gather the horses.
We will track Damodar.
They will travel with us.
Should they try to escape,
kill them.
Tell me.
Why were you at the Thieves Guild?
It isn't exactly a sightseeing spot,
is it?
We needed money. For supplies.
You'll have to do better than that.
I'm curious. You're a mage.
Yet, you're disgracing your family
by consorting with thieves.
- You're a disgrace to Izmer,
conspiring against the Empress.
I have no dispute with that.
You know me.
I have served her family loyally
for many a years.
It is Profion's desire
to dethrone her.
Not mine.
Then why do you help him?
Look at me.
If I do not obtain the rod,
I will die.
Please.
Help me.
I'm sorry, but I cannot help you.
Foolish girl.
I can suck any information I want
right out of you.
Your friends have procured
the Eye of the Dragon from the
Thieves' Guild.
A key of some sort.
Can't I just walk?
Don't you people know dwarves are
terrified of horses?
Get over it.
- A lot of dwarves are afraid
to show their feelings. I'm not, ok?
They've followed the valley.
I know these lands.
There's a shortcut up ahead through
the forest and over those hills.
It means leaving the trail,
but if Damodar sets up camp
and we ride all night, we stand a good
chance of cutting him off.
All right. Let's go.
You know, I love the way you track.
You wouldn't happen to be single,
are you? What?
No harm in asking, is there? You know,
it just so happens, I'm single.
Can you believe it?
- How old are you?
23. Yeah, I know I'm a little young
for you. What if I get my hands
on aging potion?
I'll sacrifice a couple years for you.
I'm 234.
- Damn.
I didn't mean that much of a change.
Ridley, look. We're hopeless.
- Relax. We'll just sneak around.
Now what?
- We need a diversionary.
All right, Snails. Stay close.
All clear.
Ok. I'll get Marina. You get the map.
Ok. Wait, wait. How do you get a girl
and I get a map?
We gotta work on some new plans.
- Would you go?
Hey, Snails?
- What?
Be careful.
All right. Hey, Ridley.
You too.
Let's go in.
We were not meant to enter this place.
This task they must complete alone.
I'm Damodar.
A little black magic.
All right, Damodar.
Nice!
Piece of cake.
Oh no! I knew this was too easy!
Need a hand?
Marina?
Hey.
Hey. It’s ok.
Let's get you out of here. Come on.
Just like you thieves.
Always taking things
that don't belong to you.
- That's enough. So!
Now I'm mad.
Oh. You want to play, do you?
- Yeah. Let's play.
Ok, you win. Game over.
So much for getting out of here
without a fight.
Thanks.
- Any time.
Marina! Get him!
Snails!
Let's go.
Oh, no!
Come on.
You cannot be serious.
- I’ve never been so serious.
Oh please.
If you'll give me the Dragon's Eye,
I might decide to let
you die quickly.
- Go to hell.
Damodar!
Not your usual punctual self.
Where's my Dragon's Eye?
I have it.
- Really?
Show it to me.
Let him go first. And it's yours.
Snails, don't!
No!
Make it easy on yourself.
Give me what is mine.
Never!
- You're as stubborn as your friend.
Very well. You've made your choice.
Come on, Ridley.
Wherever Norda is!
Come on, Ridley. Come on.
The council has voted. You must
oblige us. Do you understand the
consequences of your decision?
- Do not patronize me, Azmath.
For I understand all too well.
Yes, I violate the law in defying
the council.
But, if I were to give you this
scepter, my crime
would be graver yet. I would be
defying my conscience
and our people.
Have you all forgotten?
This council was created
to protect the people of Izmer. But,
ask yourselves. Is this what you
are doing? I say not.
Your concern is only for yourselves.
Not the people.
And your Majesty is forcing the empire
to the verge of civil war
in the best interest of the people?
- The man who convinced you to take the
scepter from me so that he would
leave the state defenseless.
Be careful, my friends.
For once he's done with me,
this council may be next.
War benefits no one, Profion.
And I oppose it.
But, if it is necessary to obtain
the freedom of our people?
Then no cost could be too great
to achieve that goal.
Do you hear her words?
She violates our highest law.
And then threatens to force us into
submission with the threat of war!
- Each citizen of Izmer,
whether a commoner or a mage,
deserves an equal right
for prosperity. And as Empress,
this is how I decree Izmer shall be
run from this day forward.
- Such pretty words.
My friends, I warn you.
That this headstrong child
will defy you. And destroy you.
Her youth denies her the wisdom
to understand
why some things cannot be changed.
That idealism
is for children. And a child is not
fit to govern an empire.
I ask you one last time!
Will you submit to the ruling
of this council
and relinquish your scepter?
- I was praying
that you would find the wisdom to see
that the path I propose for Izmer
is the right one.
I do not wish to fight you.
But I will not leave
the empire at the mercy of
an unscrupulous charlatan.
So, decide as you must.
But, know one thing.
I am not afraid.
A wonderful performance. My friends,
ask yourselves.
Are we prepared to see our empire
destroyed by a child?
- No!
Then is now not the time
we should act?
Yeah!
- Then, down with the tyrant!
Wow.
What is he doing?
Isn’t he going to use any spells?
- Wait.
Hello, Ridley.
How did you do that?
- The elven peoples do not require
spells to work with magic.
You use magic.
We are part of it.
You're part of the magic?
- As are all living creatures
including dragons. Sadly, humans see
only their destructive powers.
Sshh!
- I had a dream. I saw...
You saw a dragon being born.
- It was amazing.
Life was exploding all around it.
- So it should. You see,
when dragons are born,
they bring new magic with them.
Magic is the life force of our world.
It keep nature
and everything around us in balance.
And if many dragons should die?
- Oh, life would wither as it must.
And the balance would be destroyed.
The rod.
You and your countrymen are very
close to irreparably destroying
the fabric of magic with this rod
you seek.
The rod is man-made.
Unnatural. It must not be disturbed.
Sshh. You must rest.
I'm sorry about Snails.
Yeah.
I'm sure you are.
Ridley, he died for a good cause.
- A good cause?
What cause is that? Hmm?
The Empress against Profion?
Politics.
I'm through with all that.
I'm not going to die over some power
struggle between a couple of mages.
No. No, you're wrong.
- No! You're wrong! Mage!
You never had to live on the other
side. You know what? Snails was right.
We can nothing do to change it. If I
had listened to him, he'd be alive.
Just because some mages are evil does
not mean they all are! I'm not!
I'm not!
Let me let you in on a little secret.
The Empress that Snails died for
stands to lose everything because
she is fighting to change things.
As if she has anything to worry about.
You are so naive.
She risks everything because she does
not believe the system is fair.
Profion seeks to dethrone her because
she believes that mages and commoners
should be treated as equals.
She is fighting to change
what you hate so much!
That, Ridley, is what Snails died for.
You now, when Vildan told me what was
happening with the Empress
I wanted to do all I could
to help her.
But, even then I did not understand
why she would want
commoners to be equal with us.
But now. After being with you for
only a few days
and seeing how you, you always manage
to find your way,
I understand why the Empress is right.
Please, Ridley.
Help show that we are not
like they are.
You know, for a mage
you're pretty smart.
It will protect you.
Thank you.
All right. This is it.
This is the entrance to the dungeon.
What happened? What is it?
It’s a wall of force of some kind.
I’ve never seen this kind of magic.
Only you were meant to pass.
I guess I go alone then.
Ridley?
Be careful.
- Don't worry. I'll be fine.
Great.
Now what?
Sorry, Snails.
Finally.
A mage who got what he deserved.
Why do you disturb the
Rod of Savrille?
To save the empire of Izmer.
Who? What are you?
- I am Savrille.
Creator of the rod. Cursed for the
crime of trying to control
the Red Dragons.
And sentenced to this purgatory
until someone worthy of its power
takes it. You are such a man?
I don't know if anybody is such a man.
But, I'm gonna find out.
Be warned.
Anyone who wields the power of the rod
shall suffer a horrible fate.
For the evil it creates cannot
be undone.
Unless it's spell is broken.
How do I break the spell?
- That, you must discover.
The Empress has called
all her dragons upon us.
Don't just stand there admiring them!
Destroy them before they reach us!
Hurry! Hurry!
Prepare to fire!
- Fire!
Is that the best you can do?
Get up!
Prepare to fire again!
Aim for their wings, you fools!
Fire, you fools! Fire!
What have I done?
Yeah!
Come to me.
I found the rod!
Thanks for saving me the trouble.
Feels good, doesn't it? Ah! Remember
your stupidity and persistence
got your thief friend killed.
Don't let it be responsible for
finishing off the rest of your
social circle.
Oh. Look. I’ve cut her.
What a shame.
- Don't hurt her!
Then give me the rod!
- And you'll release them?
Don't do it, Ridley.
You have my word.
Finally.
- You said you'd let them go!
I lied. Kill them.
Slowly.
Ridley! No! No!
Give that to me.
You said you'd set me free.
Yes!
Now what about my head?
Here they come!
Come, Damodar! To the roof of Sumdall!
Fire!
My destiny.
Come to me.
Damodar!
Look. I’ve cut you. What a shame.
You can run your ladyship.
But you'll never run far enough!
Let their blood rain from the sky!
You'll pay for that, boy.
Did you really think you could steal
my destiny?
I’ve got a new destiny
especially for you.
Full of pain. New kinds of pain.
And new senses to feel it with.
- Not if I kill you first.
Now, this will be a real pleasure.
Not so talented, Mr. Ridley?
I’ve enjoyed our little chat.
But, now is your time to die.
My little tracker.
Hey mage!
Why don't you pick on someone your
own size?
Oh, do you really think that you
could use that,
you little burglar?
That's impossible?
- Bring them down on him Ridley!
Destroy him!
No.
I won't become you!
What have you done?
Profion!
Your majesty?
It’s over, Profion.
- The battle may be,
your Majesty. Maybe.
But not the war!
Thank you.
Norda?
People of Izmer. At long last,
I do declare
that you are now all equal.
Let the celebration begin!
Hear that, buddy?
That's for you.
Nothing's gonna be the same
without you.
But, I guess I'll have to get
used to that. I just hope
wherever you are,
you know that you did make
a difference.
You helped things change.
You finally got it.
Your big score.
Well, I guess I better get going. Or,
I'll miss my own knighting ceremony.
Ridley the savior.
Can you believe it?
I'm gonna miss you, pal.
No not question your gift.
Your friend awaits you.
Subtitles: VICOMEDIA 08/2001