- Three photographers, $250 each.
- I thought it was $400 each.
Kid, are you in or out?
I'm in.
Okay, here to the bridge. Winner take all.
If the cops get you, you're on your own.
Hey, right here, man.
Beautiful.
Hey, kid.
Smile.
Hey, give me room, will you?
Shit!
You almost got me killed, asshole!
You son of a bitch!
Grab hold!
Oh, shit!
Marcus Ridley, how the hell are you doing?
How long have you been back?
Three weeks. Spent it with my kids.
I miss them when I'm over there.
I'll bet. Why don't you bring them back?
You could afford it. Look at these baubles.
So, what happened, man?
What's going on?
- Still trying to kill yourself?
- Something like that.
What happened to playing pro?
I thought you got picked
for the minors last fall.
Yeah. Well, that didn't quite work out.
You know, coach wanted me to play "D."
- What did you do? Hit him?
- I should've.
Wasting your life.
I just haven't gotten the break I need.
NHL tryouts are in three months.
Jon, the break you need is right here.
They'll cover your travel,
give you $5,000 just to show up...
...and if you make the team...
Come on. That's a circus, not a sport.
- Pretty sunset, though.
- It's the mines.
- What is?
- Dust from the mines.
It makes the sunset red.
Come on. We both know cash is king.
I last two more years, I have enough
to retire, support my family for life.
They love Americans, especially
baby-faced, boy-next-door types like you.
It'll be just like high school.
You run, I block.
Besides, it's where even a doofus-ass
white boy like you can get laid.
- Is that right?
- That's right.
I appreciate the offer,
but I should stick around.
This is my year to make pro.
I tried. Good luck with that.
My flight leaves at 9:00 p.m. tonight,
in case you change your mind.
Thanks for saving my ass today.
Anytime.
- You better walk.
- What? What's the matter?
It's Sunday. The mines are out.
Oh, shit.
I don't understand a word
you're saying to me.
But maybe if you say it louder,
I won't understand you even better.
I get it. Your nipples get hard
at the very sight of me, right?
A new bio on the kid.
Now he's a rodeo champion.
Jon-a-ton! Jon-a-ton! Jon-a-ton!
Jonathan.
They're waiting.
Hailing from the wide-open plains of Texas,
a former rodeo champion...
...and first-round draft pick by
the prestigious National Hockey League...
...back in the States.
Considered the next Wayne Gretzky...
...he refused a king's ransom from the NHL
to play here in a real man's league.
The Red Horsemen's sure bet
for Rookie of the Year...
...who kills his stubble each morning
with a Wilkinson Sword Tri-flex.
Here he is, your very own...
...Jonathan Cross.
Please, my friends, sit down. Have a seat.
You are his boy. Looks like Alexi's
got himself some hot investors.
Vodka!
You got your armadillo on?
Jesus, you're an idiot.
You want to be a paraplegic?
Do you know what those guys
can do to your spine?
Gotta catch me first, Rid.
- Right. It's your face.
- Yes, Mother.
At least do it up.
- Okay, Mom.
- Stubborn bastard.
Toba!
Okay, Toba! Big roar now!
Let's hear it! Let's go!
Great roar, Toba! Now, you hang tight
up there tonight, okay?
You, too, Jonathan.
All right.
Listen up, thugs.
Got our butts kicked last game,
but we're not going down again.
Are you?
- I didn't hear an answer! Are you?
- No!
Give them something to think about
for the playoff.
That means teamwork,
so no more cowboy hot-dog dogshit.
Can't we all just get along?
No, Aurora's right.
No more of the cowboy hot-dog dogshit.
When the Red Horsemen went
to the Golden Horde last month...
...they came back with their tails
between their legs.
Now the Horde comes to Horsemen town.
The word is "rematch."
And the Horsemen hope
it's spelled "payback."
A team must go around the track twice...
...maintaining possession of the rollerball
before they can score.
It's really that simple.
As simple as using a Lifestyle
female condom before sex.
The ball must be held at all times.
Player gear may be only used
to dislodge the ball...
...or prevent a score.
A team gaining possession
must first do the rabbit hole.
That's that killer tunnel above each bench.
Then make one circuit
through enemy territory...
...and then they're eligible to score.
All you really have to know is,
there's only one way to score...
...and that's when a player
takes one of the balls...
...wings it at one of the goals
hard enough to set off the pyro.
As for the rest of the rules...
Well, the rest of the rules are Russian
and complicated.
What's it going to be, U-Chow?
Us or them?
Patience, outlander.
The gods not yet ready.
Big goons over there.
Watch your backsides.
Ten seconds to the first ball.
First ball wagers close in ten seconds.
Five...
...four...
...three...
It's us!
Go, go! Denekin, move!
Ball's away.
It's rollerball!
First play of the rollerball game
is underway.
Through the rabbit hole.
I need a ride, Rid.
On the way.
It's a 12-foot jump.
And Jonathan Cross is in enemy turf.
He crosses back around.
This game,
I cannot believe it, is starting this early.
Yes!
Cross leaps!
Cross is in the air.
He scores!
Cross has scored in record time!
Only 12 seconds after the first ball...
...and he soars over the heads
of the Horde!
Cross has led a 1-to-0 lead!
She say you must do again.
- What?
- Drink again.
Label out.
Put the label out.
We're the hottest sports-entertainment
start-up in the world, bar none.
We have to pay a couple of headliners...
...but the rest get bollocks.
They'll fight for peanuts.
It's about to get interesting!
Good move for Denekin!
The local boy who made good used to work
right here in the coal mines!
All the glitz is put on
in the media trailer out back.
We even had a computer to build
the city around it. You know?
And it becomes Vegas!
We've got a fight down there!
There is a fight going on right there!
She just swung at a referee!
Well, that's a tutu in the penalty box!
What was she thinking?
We got a fox in the box! A fox in the box!
They put that fox in the box!
She's called in the catcher.
He's a 400-pound monster on his way in!
I will not allow this game
to become corrupted...
...like so many things
in this part of the world.
The integrity of the game
must be maintained.
For the people, to keep their heroes alive.
And to keep them gambling, of course.
Go!
Are you crazy? Are you insane?
- Why are you mixing it up with that guy?
- So he's doped up. Big deal.
It could be PCP, for all you know.
That dude doesn't feel anything.
Stay the hell away from him.
Payback?
How many of you will last the season
with management out there watching...
...this sissy performance?
- That woman.
- Come on!
- Go out and score.
Stay focused. We have a lead.
We have to keep up the pressure.
Tell cowboy to pass the ball
once in a while.
- They're keying on him.
- She's right.
If she'd get in the air,
somebody would pass her the ball.
Enough! We have a game to play!
On three. One, two, three! Get some!
- She's wide-open...
- Come on! Throw it!
He bogarts it!
Cross keeps the ball!
- Come on, Jon!
- I'm on it! Go! Move!
You don't listen, do you, cowboy?
Here you go, princess.
Toba, get down! Move!
Toba! Somebody get a medic!
You're okay.
Guys, wait! Hold on. Here you go, buddy.
Toba, you're fine!
Hang in there.
And don't screw up.
What the hell is wrong with the officials?
I mean, the band can smell it.
The audience can feel it coming.
Cross is going over the top.
And if the officials would quit
playing games down there...
...maybe we'll get this thing going!
"From the mountain, to the prairies
"From sea to shining sea"
He asks if it's true your mother
is a crack whore.
You actually translated that?
My mother's a pediatrician.
The plane leaves at 8:00 a.m. sharp.
That's 8:00 a.m. tomorrow morning.
Be there. Be on it, or be history.
We will see you in the morning.
My friends, they call me rabbit.
Really?
What was that?
I think it's something about her
only batting for the home team.
Management told me
you got to wear the hat.
- Like hell I will.
- No, I'm serious.
Management's going to tell us
what to do, Rid?
- You got me.
- You wear the hat!
I told you this was the promised land.
First one to the club buys?
Jonathan!
You get off!
- Asshole!
- I'm going to kick your ass, Rid.
You guys are nuts!
- I told you. It's the promised land.
- Yes, sir.
Hey, listen, please take extra special care
of this car, okay?
Thank you.
- Ready for Ridley's great adventure?
- Yeah, let's go play ball.
Gentlemen.
- Rodeo.
- That's great.
I love this country.
Oh, my God. Honeys at 4:00.
Yes, ladies. Sir Ridley's in the house.
- American horses, right?
- Absolutely. And hung like one.
We don't speak much.
That's the way I dig it, yo.
You don't speak much.
"The way I dig it, yo"?
You ever try to get laid
with an accounting degree?
Hey, Jonathan!
Hey, Katya, how are you?
- My number. I got my number on.
- She's official.
She's got her number.
Congratulations. It looks beautiful!
Don't like the idea
of a number tattooed on your face?
You guessed it.
Now we will all get big bonuses,
thanks to you, Uncle Sammies.
To Jonathan and to Ridley.
Thank you very much.
No. This toast should be to Toba.
To Toba.
Hey, come here.
Come here. Take it. Go.
Why do you show me disrespect?
You work 24 hours in the mines,
and it pays you nothing.
I brought you here, and you try to pay?
All right, my gypsy brother. Have a drink.
A little wound tonight, Denny?
What happened could have happened
to any of us.
It's very bad shit, man.
It's a rough game. That's why we get paid.
You make a hundred times what I do.
What's up, Denny?
What if it wasn't an accident?
What are you talking about?
U-Chow.
Show him.
- The chin strap's been cut.
- Where'd you get this?
I found it in the trainer's office.
Look at this.
She says the gambling syndicate
probably put them up to it.
We need to go tell Petrovich.
No, we'll deal with this on the track.
Toba was almost killed, Rid.
He's the owner.
I wouldn't bother him with it.
Fine, captain. I'll go.
Enjoy the party.
No move. Me be back soon.
Tonight was the best game.
Real cowboy shit?
- Is he available?
- Of course, for you.
Gentlemen, please.
My stallion.
Hey, Ridley, my homie.
Let me introduce my friends.
This is John Buckley from the US network.
- Enzo Molinadi, Canale Cinque.
- Hello. Pleasure to meet you.
And Yuri Kotlev, owner of the Horde.
Be careful, Jonathan.
I think he's angry with you.
Dirk Cannon, an investor from Montana.
One of those places, you know.
How do you do, son? Nice to meet you.
Big money.
Could I talk to you for a minute?
Yes, of course. Please, this way.
What can I do for you?
I think the chin strap's been cut.
- Where did you get this?
- It doesn't matter.
No, you're right. It doesn't matter.
If that fat swine was behind this,
I will get the owners to take his team.
- May I keep this?
- What are you gonna do?
I'll take care of it.
I swear on my mother's grave.
Jonathan is the angriest man in the game.
He just doesn't know it yet.
Borges, you still back there?
Discreetly.
And how is Mr. Jonathan tonight?
You play good?
How come it always feels like
we got the freeways to ourselves?
We are not a rich country, sir.
No shit. So why's everybody bet their ass
on the rollerball?
We call it the Atlantic City syndrome.
Watch what you're saying.
My apology, Jonathan.
Our problem. Not your problem.
That's no worry, Borges.
You guys be good tonight.
Don't wait up.
You think we could do this
in a bed sometime?
You know, with sheets and stuff?
We've been through this.
This should be our secret.
How could I forget?
It could be used against us.
Against me.
You're untouchable.
Come on, Aurora.
You don't need to hide all the time.
I don't.
Yes, you do.
You live in the dark, for Christ's sake.
Your face isn't nearly as bad as you think.
I know that.
Yeah, that's why you always turn your
left side to people.
I don't always turn.
Toba's helmet was cut.
I took it to Petrovich.
And you think that does some good?
He seemed pretty upset.
I think he'll take it to the Horde owner.
You are so naive.
- Jonathan, they knew.
- They knew what?
One of the TV guys put me on to this.
I think I can call it up.
Here, look.
That's Toba getting hit.
It's caught clearly on five cameras.
So they were following the action.
Let me back the feeds up five seconds.
Okay, now look.
One camera follows the action...
...and four cameras follow a simple-minded
boy at the other end of the track.
They were called and told to get on him
15 seconds before it happened.
The Horde did not make that happen.
Not on their own.
This TV guy, you know where to find him?
- What's going on?
- Demonstration.
It is the headquarters for the mines.
Hang on.
What do you want me to do?
Get out of the car!
- Get out!
- What's going on?
- Trust me. Get out! Hurry!
- Aurora, what's the matter?
Quick, Jonathan!
Come over here!
Hurry!
Jonathan, get in here!
- Get in here!
- What is going on?
That's my goddamn car!
That's not your car.
It belongs to Petrovich.
He'll have another one for you tomorrow.
Goddamn it. This is unbelievable.
Don't you know they can track you
with these things? Come on.
What's with this place?
The state housing authority sold off
the apartments, they went out of business.
So what?
They never sold off the hallways.
Now there's no one to take care of them.
No shit.
Sergei?
Stop! Don't kill him.
Let me guess,
this isn't your friend Sergei, is it?
No, Sergei's gone.
Of course he is. We can't call the police
about it, either, right?
Let's get out of here.
He may be the police.
You almost missed the flight.
Jonathan, good morning.
It's a beautiful day.
- Yeah.
- It was a long night.
It was, yeah.
Partied, the usual thing with the team.
We found your car. Are you all right?
- Yeah, I just had a little accident.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
Hey, Serokin, did you follow me last night?
I just found your car. That's all.
Wouldn't want you to be without.
So there was a goon in the apartment,
and he bugged out.
Might've been a thousand reasons why.
He might've been lying to Aurora.
Let's say they are screwing with the game.
Then?
Yeah, then what?
Then nothing.
Status quo. We play, we win.
If it gets too sick, we walk.
Come on, guys. I've got meetings.
Why can't I just take a cab to the hotel?
When the circus came to town,
did they let the elephants take a cab?
You're the elephant. Get in the car, son.
It's an honor and a pleasure to be
broadcasting to you this evening...
...with a crowd pushing 50,000...
...in this beautiful desert city
on the shores of the blue, blue...
Jeez, this outfit's got a lot of money.
What is that?
I'd say it's a good time in a can.
Come on in here, and get your ass kicked.
Come on!
I love you.
What channel did you say you
gave us in your territory?
- 109.
- 109. I see.
1-freaking-09.
They do origami on Channel 6...
...of your silly hairball network!
You ungrateful cretin!
I will kill you myself!
I will disappear your whole family!
Tell your people,
you want to do business with us...
...we are on Channels 1 through 5! Got it?
You got that?
Goddamn mouse.
Goal, yes, goal.
The Red Horsemen are rolling
over the home...
No! Stop it!
Are you from Omaha or something?
It was a matter of time
before they realized...
...their take would go up
if they got blood on the track.
Think they struggle with the morality of it?
- Soon they'll kill somebody.
- That's what I'm talking about.
I make more in a season
than I would 10 years doing taxes.
Nothing will happen to us. They need us.
So just close your eyes,
and take the money, okay?
Sergei, the TV guy...
...they found him at the border,
his throat cut and his mouth sewn shut.
Hey, what's up?
You don't look so good. What's going on?
Well, you hit the Pod ramp and jump,
and then I cross under and go.
And then you shot,
and then you did the 4-40...
...so I wasn't sure,
but I think you scored the touchdown.
Got it?
Absolutely.
I scored a touchdown and I win.
Gotcha.
We'll beat them!
This Mongol Blue Team
is on fire and insane!
They're lathered up
like a Siberian wolf pack...
...ready to tear the Reds limb from limb.
You're not wearing
your spine protector, right?
That's right.
With a quarter left to play,
it's the Horsemen...
I see.
We should make some arrangements.
I don't want problems! I want solutions.
It's in the works.
We got ourselves a motorcycle race here!
Aurora just got hammered!
That son of a bitch has got to be
eight feet tall.
Here's your bike, little lady.
Hope I didn't bend it.
I wish you spoke English.
I speak it just fine, asshole.
Bail out!
Easy fellas. Come on, get him out.
We're out of here.
Ridley, my man.
How are you?
I feel like Freddy Krueger.
- How is he, doctor?
- Hey, I'm good.
- He should be resting.
- I feel fine. I can play.
- You sure about that?
- I feel fine.
- Are you up to it?
- It was, after all, just an accident.
You don't know how glad I am
to hear you say that.
All right, that's it. Let's go. Out!
You promised me you'd stop this.
Dear God, your tone.
How have I denied you?
I have made you into a rich man,
an international star.
I created a sport that you could thrive in.
I have given you total freedom
to do as you please, and even satellite TV.
And ask for one thing, your trust.
So, will both my studs
be at practice tomorrow?
- Yes, sir.
- Excellent.
Horsemen, Number 1.
Watch them. They take a shit,
I want to know what it smells like.
Let's go.
Wait.
Don't move.
Close the doors.
It's cold as hell. Please, the door.
Hey, the door!
Come on, Denny.
What about our passports?
Katya tried. She couldn't get them.
She's afraid. They have something on her.
- We have to wing it.
- You get the cash from my place?
Your apartment was being watched
all the time.
The players put this together.
Thanks, Den.
Thank them.
I don't know what to say.
Okay, look. The nearest border is Russia.
You have two crossings
at the Russian border. Here and here.
One is by the river.
Leave now, you can make it by morning.
- I thought you two were coming with us...
- No, he has family here. I have my mother.
If you don't want them to disappear
or have an accident...
You can never really leave.
- Aurora, wait a minute!
- No.
- Are you going to be okay?
- Stop.
Before you say something
even more stupid.
Get the light over there on the wall.
There's no way I'm going to die
in this shithole of a country. No way.
We left the rest of the team, Rid.
How many times
you have to get your head handed to you...
...before you stop picking fights
with people who are too big?
This isn't some college coach you can
flick off. These are dangerous people.
Look, Jon. She's safe.
She's safe. Nobody knew about you two.
Shit. We have company.
Looks like they brought
the whole Russian cavalry.
Great. We're being chased
by our own bodyguards.
Here they come! They're on your bumper!
The fender. Squeeze them!
Shit!
Come on, you son of a bitch!
- That ain't going to work twice.
- They're still coming on us.
- Remember Squeak Harris?
- Of course I remember Squeak Harris.
Remember how he died?
- Change with me.
- Shit.
Let's rock 'n' roll! One, two, three!
Goddamn it! This road isn't even paved!
I haven't seen lights in about an hour.
Why don't we back it off a little?
How fast are we going, anyway?
I don't know. It's in clicks.
- Well, how fast is it in clicks, then?
- 110, 120.
That's not so bad.
Ridley, that's in miles per hour!
- So what?
You're going 120 miles per hour
on a hog on a dirt road!
It's not an off-road bike, Rid!
It's 10 clicks to the border. Chill.
That 10 clicks is going to be a long walk
if one of these tires goes out.
Shit. Ridley, we've got lights!
Don't look! Watch the road!
- It looks like they're gaining on us.
- What?
They're definitely gaining on us, and fast!
What the hell could they be driving?
Look, my limit's 150, man.
Faster!
What in the world are they driving?
Shit!
Son of a bitch!
Come on, baby!
Who said this isn't an off-road bike?
I got news for you, Rid!
They've got an off-road airplane!
There it is.
That's it? That's the border?
What do you want?
A Stuckey's and a casino?
We can make it.
It won't work. Not double.
- Then you go.
- Don't get saintly on me.
Look, I got you into this!
Your kids. Go home.
- Ridley, I'll be fine. I promise.
- No!
Get to the American consulate
on the other side.
They'll have me on a plane first thing
in the morning.
Go! Get out of here! Go!
You better make it.
Serokin.
"Close your eyes, and take the money."
God forgive me.
Wait.
Let's see if he makes it.
Come on.
Magnificent.
Let's go.
Make sure you tip the border guards well.
Did you really think
I could let you pull a stunt like that?
Even if I wanted to? In front of them?
How could you do that to me?
How could you be so...
...thoughtless?
All right. We start again.
I'll give you a bonus of $100,000 US,
payable however...
...you play through the championship.
Play till the goddamn cable deal closes.
Then you may go where you wish!
I'll even give you a retirement game!
Go fuck yourself.
Throw that sack of shit out of here!
Get rid of him!
Jonathan.
What are we going to do with you?
In the old regime, Petrovich was above the
official rank in Spetsnaz before he was 30.
KGB colonels used to cross the street
when they saw him come.
Now they line up to grovel in the dust.
Would you like a drink of water?
No.
You obviously don't care anything
for yourself, but think of the girl.
You don't imagine
you have any secrets, do you?
Why do you think she's still alive?
Because Petrovich needs you.
He'll give you anything,
including the life of that lady...
...if you play your cards right.
You have an opportunity here.
You might call it
the opportunity of a lifetime.
You see Yevgeny over there,
so full of himself now.
He used to work in the post office.
I introduced him to the proper financing,
and now he owns the mines.
Yeah, making a fortune.
Keeps the miners in line. Good business.
You might wonder why I'm not in it myself.
I don't need to own the mines, Jonathan.
Do you know why?
Because I own the man
who owns the mines. All he has, I have.
Same with the supermarkets,
the TV station, locomotive plant.
I don't need a political position,
because I own the men who do.
We learn to separate ourselves
from humanity.
Like you, Jonathan,
separate yourself from your teammates.
You can keep your $100,000.
But I do like the view from up here.
No, I want more.
I want ownership. Part of the media
rights, gambling revenues, the works.
Jonathan, are you fooling with me?
Come on, Alexi, we both want
the same thing here, don't we?
Good. Very good.
Let Serokin take you back home.
You've got a big night ahead of you.
What?
Aurora's kind of bugging me.
You know? Getting way too serious.
I hate that, too. Women.
I want her out of my life.
Do me a favor and trade her.
No problem. People disappear all the time.
No, trade her, Alexi. Just trade her.
I like the lady.
I don't want her disappeared, just gone.
All right. I'll do that.
Play well tonight.
Play well.
He gave me a load of shit
about wanting to become a partner.
Just cover to get the girl out.
Did you give him that?
I thought it was too subtle for him.
So the first chance he gets, he'll bolt.
Shit! I'm this close
to a North American cable deal!
Well, maybe there is one thing we can do
to turn this to a profit.
You did promise him
a retirement game, after all.
Sanjay, you are a rat.
But you are my rat, and I love you.
Go ahead. Trade the girl.
Trade the girl to the Horde.
But we're playing them tonight.
He wants her gone.
Life is full of little disappointments.
Make sure they get a number on her.
We heard you were in a rock-climbing
accident! Are you all right?
Yeah, you know me. I'm hard to hurt.
Where is Ridley?
You guys are always together!
Be careful.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is what it's all about.
One hard-fought struggle for
all the marbles. And the Red Horsemen...
There is unbelievable tension in this arena.
There are four teams in the quarterfinals,
but without Marcus Ridley...
...who was crippled
by an attack of malaria...
...which he contracted in the tropics
on an archeological dig.
Malaria?
If they'll buy it, I'll sell it.
Rid isn't sick, is he?
Don't get in this, Denny. Stay out of it.
- You shouldn't go out there, man.
- I've got to.
That's how I got him to send Aurora away.
He made it real clear.
- Where are they sending her?
- What do I care?
Just as long it's away from here.
- What makes you think you can trust him?
- I don't have a choice.
You can't help me, Denny.
The Golden Horde, however, seem to have
several transfers from other teams.
Hey. See they got a number on you.
Nice. Very nice.
Get the goddamn camera
out of my face, ass-wipe!
And now for all of you out there,
a surprise is on the way.
Despite reports of a rock-climbing accident,
he's coming back.
Despite the pleading of his trainers
and his doctors, he's coming back.
He's coming back for the love of the game.
He's coming back for you and for me.
The greatest rollerballer
who has ever lived...
...your very own Jonathan...
Cross!
Look.
Bravo! Yes.
What's this?
You understand that?
They give this message to you:
"Play well. And she will be on
the Horde team, playing tonight."
Ladies and gentlemen,
a special announcement.
As you all know,
at the last owners' meeting...
...certain rule changes were
proposed and adopted.
In the final elimination round,
normal rules and penalties are to be...
...suspended.
What are they doing?
The game will be played...
...with no fouls called and no penalties.
What is this shit? There's no such rule!
No penalties.
This is going to be interesting.
He tattooed her face.
- What are you going to do?
- Play the goddamn game, I guess.
You ever see thugs like that
on the bench before?
This will make us, my friend.
This will make us.
You have the pictures and resums
on the replacements?
What we've got here...
...is Jonathan and Uglich...
...in a no-holds-barred cockfight.
Say hello to Mr. Denekin!
Cross snags it.
No bogarting this time.
He passes it to Katya...
...who scores!
Boy, this crowd sure appreciates Denekin,
the local boy who made good.
He has a lot of friends in the audience...
...including his entire shift from the mine.
Gold seems to have
an extra player on the track.
Have we got some kind of
grudge match here!
Aurora seems determined
to wipe out Jonathan Cross.
Stay down. Get out of this.
They're going to kill you!
Aurora, get off the track.
Go on, girl.
Holy shit, he's wearing a spine protector.
He knew.
Here's your grudge match!
Uglich and company
singling out Jonathan Cross...
...and trying to put him in the ground!
Shit.
Cross turns it around!
Takes out Robot!
Look out! Uglich's dead meat!
You see? The show is just getting started.
That's about the hardest hit I've ever seen!
I got the Asian flu. Come on, baby.
What the hell are they doing?
Yeah!
This may be getting out of hand.
Maybe we should call the whole thing off.
No.
The Red coach is calling a time-out...
...trying to get her players out of the game.
Come in! We want you to come in.
- She should go kill herself.
- No. She's right. Get off the track.
Is anybody going to stop this?
- We should cut the feed.
- No. Leave it.
Get off the track, Katya.
Denekin, get out of this.
Dumb cowboy.
You don't have to do this.
The man wants a show, Rid.
I guess we'll have to give him one.
Punk!
Cut the satellite feed.
I said cut it.
No more of this! Enough!
Open your eyes, fool.
The world's about to blow up.
Jonathan.
Listen to them.
I'd better go sort this out.
Do it.
Do it!
Holy shit!
Bravo! Jolly good show, and all that.
I wonder what he was looking for.
These probably.
Well, young Jonathan...
...you've done marvelously well.
But one basic rule in this sort of thing is
that you must never kill a tyrant...
...unless you've made an arrangement
with his successor.
You do see what I mean, don't you?
Yeah. It means I'm not done yet.
This game may be over.
Hey, it's me.
You may have started yourself
a revolution.
Get some of these
shotgun pellets removed.
Nah, he missed me.
Not entirely, he didn't.
What are they doing?
You stood up to one of the monsters
that run their lives.
And they saw you do it.
- Where are we headed?
- To a doctor, to start with.
And then if you're able...
...I thought I might take you home
to my bed.