Love is so great that
it's almost unreal.
I feel bad for the
people who can't find it.
We've all met those types who try to convince
their coworkers that they're fine without it.
Then you take a look at their cubicle...
and see heart-shaped
frames all over their desk...
with pictures of their
three-legged cat named Bob.
Not me! Not anymore.
I've paid my dues.
Old people always say: "When
you meet the one you'll know".
They're right.
When I met Richard...
It felt like...
It felt like the butterflies in
my belly dusted off their cobwebs...
and started fluttering again.
He was the one, my only one.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
No, no! I don't get it!
Hey, wait!
Are you guys hiring?
Because no one cares about love anymore...
so why don't you just have sex
and get paid for it, you know?
Oh, come on! Who cares if my vagina
falls off from all the diseases out there?
I'll take some open sores.
Ooooh! Do you want some of this?
Come on! I got what it takes.
- Shit.
- No? Okay.
Oh, my God!
I cannot get last night out of my head!
Richard, Richard and that little...
Wait, what was her name?
Oh, yeah. Whore.
Hi, baby. I'm home!
They paid me 200 bucks to take
a picture of a pink poodle.
Richard? Is this mushu still good?
Good...
Hey, baby.
Come on.
Im sorry.
Because we got it Tuesday
and there's pork in it...
I'm gonna... gonna... oh...
You're late!
I've been waiting...
Sit down!
Come on, sit down.
Give me your hands.
You are such a lost soul.
You're in pain. Someone hurt you.
Someone ripped your heart out and
tried to play badminton with it.
This man who hurt you,
he's a dark spirit.
I see blackness all around him!
But wait.
What?
I see a white pony.
He stands alone.
His spirit is very bright.
He runs towards you and, and...
And?
Oh, you turn away.
I hate that part!
Why do I turn away?
Because you have to learn the lessons...
before you can ride the white pony.
White pony?
Can't be a white stallion or somethin'?
No. It's the white pony that
you will ride into the sunset.
Only then can you have the
happy ending you desire.
But first you have to believe...
and you have to learn the
lessons that come before.
Lessons? What kind of lessons?
Your own spirit not that bright yet.
It needs its roots...
but you're close.
First though you must
go through more pain...
before your heart can
find true happiness.
That just sucks!
It only gets worse.
You gotta be kidding me!
What do I look like? A comedian?
If you don't pay attention...
if you don't listen to
your inner psychic voice...
if you choose the wrong paths
and the wrong situations...
if you think you can just
do it all on your own...
- What?
- if you ignore the signs...
love will never find
its way into your heart.
You'll live a lonely,
desperate, isolated...
miserable existence.
I would not wanna be you.
Hi.
Hi, Carrie. It's Rebecca.
What time is it?
10am.
Why!
I never realized how
beautiful it is in the morning.
Birds chirping...
smell of ass on Hollywood Boulevard.
Hey, you wanna start jogging?
Let's jogl
Are you on crack,
Rebecca? I'm not jogging!
Please.
Have you seen my boobs lately?
Yeah, they're pretty.
Of course they are! And you know why?
Because I don't fucking jog!
Besides, I have my Animal Kingdom
audition in a couple of hours.
Wanna go shopping?
Okay.
He is a jerk, Beck. A
cock sucking loser jerk.
Oh, my God. Every time
something like this happens...
it makes me seriously wanna
consider lesbianism. Ow!
You can't even stand
looking at your own vagina.
That's not true. I just had to
figure out which department did what.
Hey!
Maybe you can concentrate
more on your work now.
I have been concentrating.
It just takes a while to go
from sandwich ads and dog shows...
to Vanity Fair covers.
Doesn't just happen overnight!
Oh! Oh, no!
What?
I left my camera, my lenses,
my tripods, my gels. Everything!
I left my future at Richard's.
Oh, no.
No, no way. I'm not
going over to his house.
I'm not going to his house! Michelle!
Oh, hell, no!
For real? Ooh, girl!
Yeah, you know I'll
get your stuff, girl.
Mm-hm.
No, no, no. I ain't gonna beat his ass.
I can't speak for John, though.
No, that shit would be funny.
I got to go.
What the hell are you doing?
Hot Bacon. Three o'clock.
That's not Bacon.
That's Porter House.
Oh, no! He's wearing sneakers!
You can have him.
Fuck that!
I'm not going near that world.
It's gonna be a very long time before
Rebecca goes searching for another dick.
The best medicine is
to get back out there.
There's nothing wrong with a little
gratuitous sex to help mend the pain.
Remember the last time
we were all single?
We had sex with every one.
Carrie, Brad Pitt's throbbing
cock couldn't help me right now.
Nothing in the world could
heal this pain that I'm go...
What?
Do you remember how jealous Richard
would get when any guy would go near me?
Hey, baby...
What?
Can I help you?
No!
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Pap smear?
Yeah. He would go ape shit.
Exactly!
So, I show up at Richard's fashion
show tonight with another guy.
He sees me mauling him and his insides...
will get eaten up almost
as bad as mine did.
It's the best revenge
revenge! How do I look?
Like a summer flower that
got rained and stung by a bee.
Go, go, go!
Hi.
I was just sitting over
there with my friend...
and saw that you were
kinda staring at... me?
Yeah, I was staring at you.
What do you do for lunch?
Nothing.
Nothing? Do you like Chinese?
Huh?
Chinese food.
Chicken chow mein,
mushu pork, you know.
Mu shu.
You know, if you don't like
Chinese, we could always just...
No, no. Uhm, what are you doing tonight?
Do you wanna go to this
fashion show with me?
Sweetheart, do you have your Gold card?
I seem to have left
mine at home. Who's this?
Oh, I don't know. It's just
some bimbo hitting on me?
Come on, hurry that shit up.
Hey, you know, it's not like I
do this for a living, you know.
Oh, shit!
What?
I can't even believe
you feel for that shit.
Very funny, Michelle.
See how it's done?
That's what I was gonna do.
Ugh!
Look at him thinking
lookin' all good and shit.
This is exactly why I don't date models.
I don't see what she saw in the guy.
But it's all over now.
We can all kiss Richard's
skank ass good bye.
Now, get the shit and let's
go. I gotta call my baby daddy.
Holy shit!
What the hell are you doing?
What's up, dawg?
What?
You got a problem, huh?
You wanna, uh, you wanna dance here?
You wanna take this outside? Huh?
What's up?
Just get the hell out of here.
You screwed up, man.
You had a rose but you
had to go and pluck a weed.
And then to make things even worse you
go and fuck up all the camera equipment?
What kind of sick bastard are you?
That was her whole life, you asshole!
She sucked at it, anyway.
Huh!
You and me, buddy.
You and me!
When?
Some day.
What up, dick?
Just a little warning.
That ain't mud on your bed.
Let's go.
We're giving nonstop excitement.
Thanks for coming with me.
I told you you'd have better luck here.
It can be that hard to find one normal
guy in this town just to use one night.
It's not hard at all. They're begging
to get used. That last guy was a fluke.
Who the fuck would ask some one out...
with their wife shopping two feet away?
I don't get it, Carrie.
I mean, I gave my heart to Richard.
What made him feel the
need to have another woman?
Well, that's easy. Penis insecurity.
When the penis doesn't
get enough showmanship...
it has to remind itself that
it's still an almighty tool
and that it could make any woman moan.
One when it got used to like yours
but one from uncharted waters.
Carrie Winters?
Right here, honey! Wish me luck.
Good luck.
How're you doing?
I'm Mike.
You're so gonna get this part.
Oh! I'm not an actress.
What?
You're so hot!
You're like smoking hot.
You're like hot air popcorn pumper hot.
Thank you.
Like hotter than exhaust hot.
Hotter than a devil's pitch fork hot.
What's that smell?
I don't smell anything.
It's totally doing something to me.
And what is that?
It's coming from you.
What is that beautiful
scent you've got on?
Deodorant?
To me it smells like... obsession!
Hey, baby.
You smell so hot.
Here at the Animal Kingdom we
bring you non-stop excitement.
In a world filled with
lions and tigers and bears...
oh my, we bring you all of the
fun without any of the danger.
Well, maybe a little bit of the danger.
So hold on to your seats every one...
because we're gonna bring you
heart stopping, claw biting...
family action fun!
That was just wonderful!
Really? Right on!
How long have you been in the business?
Longer than you can scream arghhhhh!
Oh, she... You're a feisty little one.
Hey, are you guys single, by any chance?
As... as a matter of
fact we... we both are.
Really? I'll be right back.
Rebecca! Come on in
here. They wanna meet you.
No, no. No, I don't want to.
Just get your ass in here. Hurry up!
Now!
Rebecca, I'd like you to
meet our dates for tonight.
Why, why, why why?
Excuse me!
The least you could do is thank me!
For what?
We have dates!
Yeah, with two guys that are one
chromosome away from being Woody Allen.
Woody is hot and you know it.
Remember in White men can't jump
when they were playing basketball?
And he took off his shirt...
and he looked all golden
like the sunset rising up...
What are you talking
about? I said Woody Allen!
Ooh! Who is he?
Listen to me, Crissy Snow...
if Richard gets one good
look at this mug I'm with...
he'll piss in his pants.
No jealousy, my friend. Just laughter.
I figured it out for you, Janet Woods.
When Richard comes down that
catwalk, I'm gonna shout out to him.
When he looks down you grab Milo...
and you put his head
between your breasts.
He won't see that mug, just
a man nestling in your bosoms.
Not bad.
I'm going, okay?
Sorry, sorry.
I don't understand why we
gotta be running this shit.
Because Beck left a note that
said, "Save me, it's an emergency.
Love. Annie Hall. "
This shit never be starting on time.
Excuse me.
Hold on. Just have to wait.
Way too crowded in there.
Wait for someone to come out.
Oh, hell, dodgy, you know who I am?
Huh?
The small-time crooks are looking
more like Cheech and Chong.
Wow! Look at the beautiful shiksas.
Very beautiful shiksas.
So how was I today?
You were great.
Will you be my bubbela?
Ooh, sorry.
I can do wonders for you baby. Mm-hm.
Is that so?
Yeah, that is so. That's right.
I'm gonna make you cry like
a little baby right now.
Uh-huh.
Let me get all up in that shit.
Mm-hm.
Yeah, baby.
Hey, ya!
Who thinks you're cute? I do.
You wanna take me home?
No.
Is it 'cause I'm too tall?
I've got a ladder with your name on it!
No.
It's 'cause you think I'm ugly?
It's 'cause you're gay? Oh, impotent?
No!
Is it 'cause you just
don't understand the vagina?
I'll be happy to draw a chart.
Carrie, can you just pay attention,
all right? 'Cause he's coming down.
Hey, Richard!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Why this shit happens to me?
He's the one that let his dick
go in the wrong fucking hole!
It's not fair!
I'm the one that's
humiliated all the time!
I mean, it's not fair.
Humiliation right on my face?
Girl!
Are you crazy?
Your big old titty is hanging out.
Fuck it!
Just fucking globs of fat!
That girl crazy.
You know, you're wasting water.
But we really have to get out of here...
'cause there's this giant woman
that's gonna come chasing after me...
any second from now. I'm serious.
You wanna go get some ice cream?
Tell me I don't smell like puke anymore.
You don't smell like puke anymore.
You're a bad liar.
What can I get you two?
I'll have the " I just
got dumped" sundae.
I don't think that's on the menu, dear.
Then make me the best sundae
you could possibly imagine...
that would take away
every painful experience...
that any man ever did you wrong.
- You know what I think?
- What do you think, John?
I think everything happens for a reason.
Oh, God!
Please, don't give me any
of that spiritual crap.
Heard it from a psychic this morning.
The best I'm ever gonna
find is a white pony.
And to tell you the truth
I'd settle for a brown donkey.
You know what? Maybe
that's your problem.
You just keep on
settling for these idiots.
I have known you for so
long and every single day...
you teach me how to be a better person.
But for whatever reason you
will not let someone love you...
the way you deserve to be loved.
And how should I be loved, John?
Thank you!
I just have to go to the
bathroom. I'll be right back.
God, you're such an idiot! You
just gotta fucking say it, John.
Just say the fucking words.
Say it out loud, okay?
Rebecca, you should be loved
like no one else in this world.
You should smile every day...
knowing that every morsel of your
being is being nourished by a man...
that will do anything he
can to make Rebecca happy.
Me, Rebecca. I love you.
The way you should be loved...
is to be loved by me.
See that? There you go.
It's good!
That was beautiful.
Thanks.
Rebecca, there's
something I gotta tell you.
If you tell me that you're
dying of a terminal illness...
I swear to God I'm gonna kill myself.
I'm not dying.
Oh, thank God.
What is it?
Richard destroyed all
your camera equipment.
What?
When I went to your place
to pick up all your stuff...
your equipment was in the corner
and he just... he ruined it.
I'm sorry.
What am I gonna do?
I'm not gonna be able to work. I
can't afford to buy a new equipment.
It'll be fine. I'll... I'll
pawn one of my guitars and...
No! No, John.
You've been collecting those things
since Keanu Reeves started his first band.
Just forget it.
It's useless. I have no future.
I have no future.
No. Rebecca, wha...
What if your future is
sitting right next to you, huh?
Maybe the person
sitting right next to you...
wants to spend their entire
life making Rebecca happy.
You know, stop drowning yourself in
this dark pit and pick yourself up...
and realize that the
person sitting next to you...
might just be your entire existence.
Please, take a chance for once.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Are you by chance my future?
Yes, I believe I am.
What do you think? Shall I go for it?
All right. Wish me luck.
What's your name?
Rebecca.
Can I have one "I'm a complete
dumb ass pussy" sundae, please?
Are you sure this is ecstasy?
Definitely. Without a doubt.
It's even mildly laced with acid.
Huh?
Do you like to experiment sexually?
What do you mean?
You know... try new things.
Not, not really.
Good.
I can't wait to teach you.
Shhhhh!
Now, count to 30 and
come into the bedroom.
Okay.
If this is my future...
I pray a large piano falls from
the sky and hits me right now.
Why can't drug hallucinations be real?
Shit's starting to kick.
What the hell, Rebecca.
Let's have some fun.
Time to go fishing, baby.
Touch my bass, Rebecca.
Touch my bass!
Touch my fucking bass!
Please, touch my bass.
She look dead.
She's not dead.
How do you know?
'Cause she'd be blue.
Hey, girl, you still with us?
Ooooh! She smells like fish.
Oh, my God.
Did you sleep with
Charlie the tuna last night...
or do you need to douche?
Just leave me alone.
Take your time. Nobody wanna smell that.
Mm-hm.
Rebecca, I got you some food.
Huh?
What in the hell are you doing?
I knew that should wake you up, girl.
You've been sleeping for three days.
I was not sleeping.
I was thinking.
Well, you might think better when
you don't smell like a dead fish.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't ever say that word again.
Okay.
Well, I'm gonna cook some frozen food.
I can make you a fish stick.
Shut up!
Oh, shit.
What now?
Aunt Flo came early this month.
Well, girl, at least you ain't pregnant
and shit. You know what I'm saying?
Would you have helped her with the baby?
I don't know. Would you?
Babies are sticky.
Well, at least she can get
some food stamps or somethin'.
Yeah, 'cause you know Richard
would've done nothing to help the baby.
Will you guys shut up?
You need to tell me with
the two of you living here...
you don't have one tampon in the house?
No. We're out.
Can you go buy me some?
I got no money.
Just forget it.
What do you mean I have
herpes? That's not possible!
I've only slept with one
guy in my entire life.
People like me don't get diseases.
People like you get herpes all the time.
It's the naive ones who
think it can't happen to them.
But doctor I...
I can't live with this.
You won't have to.
It's called Herpes Away.
It's a creamy little ointment
without any deadly side effects.
Take once a day to avoid outbreaks.
This is amazing.
I can't wait to tell
my friends all about it!
Just stop.
What's wrong?
I'm not believing a word you're saying!
That's 'cause I'm acting.
I mean, I see quite a
few things on your resume...
and I think how could
anybody have ever hired you?
And It dawns on me. I bet
every time you did get hired...
it was always by a man.
You need to pay your dues
in acting, not with men!
You don't know what
you're talking about.
I hope one day you do know
what I'm talking about.
Yeah?
Well, I hate to rain
on your parade, lady,
but this shit doesn't work.
What's for dinner?
We've got a special on
ground chuck today, ladies.
You can't go wrong with meat.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no!
Shit.
Hello?
Hello. Please, please
hurry up. It's an emergency.
This is an emergency, too, sweetheart.
Herb, we're gonna clean up on aisle two.
Oh, help. I've fallen!
Oh, and I'm bleeding! Oh, no!
Oh!
Herb, we're gonna clean up.
Oh, shit!
No. Thanks, Herb, I've got it covered!
When they were in the
bag, they were $1.99.
Well, I can't ring them up
unless they're in the bag.
There's no bag. This is
all that's left, okay?
I already told you if they're not
in the bag, I can't ring them up.
Listen, sweetheart,
we're both girls, okay?
Just give me a break.
The longer I stand here, the more
Herb's gonna have to clean up.
Well, that seems to be
your problem, not mine.
No, please.
Herb, we got a price check,
please, on the super size maxi pads...
for the woman who keeps
bleeding all over the store.
Stop her!
Come back here. Come back here!
Gonna get you, lady.
Hey, Beck. How is it going?
What have you got there?
Nothing.
His body is ridiculous.
So, when are you going to see him again?
Tonight. He's taking
me to the Tantra Grill.
You're so lucky to be dating a model.
He's not just a model, Lilly. He's
fucking Richard Huntington, the top model.
And he just landed three
commercials. That's huge!
Wow! Maybe I'll catch up
with a drink after dinner.
You can't.
Why not?
'Cause after dinner I'm gonna
fuck the shit out of him.
Do you think maybe you can put
me up with one of his friends?
Uhm, no.
You a cyclist or just
play for the other team?
Why? 'Cause I'm waxing my legs?
You know, I get real,
real nosy sometimes.
I like to know everything, you know.
What you need to do is wax that ass.
I'm actually a magician.
I'm doing an underwater trick
on the tonight show next week...
and I can't have any hair on my legs.
Oh, that's cool, that's real dope.
Where are you from?
I flew in from Chicago actually.
Hey! What you doing tonight?
'Cause I would love to hook you up
my girl, you know what I'm saying?
She's been through a
lot of shit, you know.
Take her out to dinner and
make her feel real good.
That could be fun.
That could be real nice. She
need to get out real, real bad...
you know what I'm saying?
She's been through some shit.
Well, she sounds great.
Oh, no, no, no. I didn't mean
for her to sound like that.
She is a super cool Barbie doll
that just got dumped by Ken.
But she's cool, she's a good
girl. You know what I'm saying?
Is there, uhm, some
place, you know, cool...
that you recommend
that I could take her?
Uh,
You know, I was thinking maybe you
could take her to the Tantra Grill.
Around 8:00. Don't be late
'cause I'll beat your ass.
Anything else?
Pay me 40 bucks for the wax...
and 20 bucks 'cause I look good.
Ooh.
Here you go. Keep the change.
Yo, this is only a dollar.
Oh!
Look again.
Hey! Wooh baby! That's my boy!
It's magic.
"You will experience
the tingling sensation...
"as the fatty acids and fruit enzymes...
replenish the nutrients in your skin".
Hi, how are you?
Tom, is it? I'm Rebecca.
You're a magician, huh? That's cool.
This? Oh, it's syphilis.
I caught it in prison.
Where are you going?
"Remove with one smooth motion".
Okay.
Ouch!
Uh... uh!
Uh!
Oh, my God!
One, two... three!
Oh, for crying out loud, Rebecca...
revenge is not the solution.
I'll be fine... I think.
And now you have lost your fiance.
You're not gonna have
kids until you're 50...
Ma, we were never engaged!
That is just great to hear.
You have been living with
this man for two years...
You need to find a good catholic boy.
What about that nice
fellow that works for you?
Who, John?
See? He's even named
after one of the disciples.
Ma, I am so not his type.
So, what are you gonna
do with your life now?
Shoot up some heroine
and become a sex slave.
Oh, for Pete's sakes!
Ma, did you hear that?
Hear what?
Oh, mercy!
Ha!
Come on!
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Okay, now I gotta zip.
Okay, here we go. Here we go.
Fuck!
Come on, please!
Okay, okay. Just one more thing.
Just let me button up. I swear
to God I'll be good, okay?
Here we go God. One, two, three.
Come on.
Okay.
Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck you.
Puff The magic dragon is in the house.
Do you think he can
magically make my ass smaller?
Carrie didn't tell me that her
jeans were size negative four.
They're baggy on me. Don't let your
big ass deter you from your mission.
We want Richard to eat his heart out.
Oh, he will.
Two of hearts.
Oh, my God!
You want a beer?
Yeah. Thanks.
You're welcome.
Magic, huh?
Yeah.
Hi.
I'm Rebecca.
You are gorgeous.
I'm lucky!
Oh! Okay.
Oh, isn't that nice?
I'll go put these in invisible water.
Are you ready?
Okay.
Hey, what's invisible water?
I don't know.
So, Michelle told me you've
been having a tough time lately.
Yeah, yeah. But I'd really
rather not talk about it.
I'm trying to forget about it
for like a whole ten minutes.
I hope I can help.
Me, too. I crave distraction right now.
Really? Huh!
Why don't you look under the table?
Uhm... there's a fucking
bird under the table.
Why don't you look again?
I swear to God there
was a bird a second ago.
It's magic.
Oh.
Uhm... I'm really hungry. Can we
maybe call the waiter over here...
so we can order some food or I'm going
to start gnawing on the tablecloth?
No problem.
Oh, do you have a headache?
Shhhhhh. I'm psychically
calling our waiter.
Are we ready to order?
Es ma'gico!
Would you care to hear the specials?
Sure.
We have a fettuccine
that is out of this world...
bathed in white clam sauce.
And we have a fantastic rabbit.
Rabbit!
I love rabbit.
I'll have the rabbit. Well done, please.
And a bottle of your best chardonnay.
She'll have salad and a water.
Certainly. Very good.
I hope my rabbit doesn't eat your salad.
Sorry.
Will you excuse me? I have
to use the little girls' room.
Oh, come on.
Please!
Where did he get that shirt?
The skank.
She's pretty.
Why do exes look better
when they're active?
Why am I talking to
myself in the mirror?
Well then shut up.
Why did the blonde
jumped off the building?
To see if the maxi pad had wings.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Hi.
Wow!
You look even more beautiful.
What? Huh? No, thank you.
Oh, no, no. I didn't ask you anything.
I said that you look
even more beautiful.
Oh! You made this into a
flower. That's so sweet.
No, no, no. That wasn't
me. That was the waiter.
Oh.
So, beautiful,
where would you like to go after this?
Why don't we figure that out later?
Right now I just wanna sit
in this chair and stay put.
Or maybe not.
You weigh 125 pounds, right?
No!
I'm 115.
125.
Here we are.
A beautiful salad for a delightful lady.
And the rabbit.
Rabbit!
Excuse me.
Can you send a blue fucker on the
rocks to that guy in the corner?
Uh, mm-hm.
I'll go first.
Oh! I didn't know we were taking turns.
Let's see. Your beauty
is like a magic spell.
So mysterious and tricky.
Can make an angel lose his wings.
Where's my wing? Where's my wing?
But conquer any dragon.
I hope you let me look inside because
I'd really love to taste your treasure.
Well, my treasure is under
construction right now, so.
Oh!
Now you.
Okay, uhm,
Excuse me, sir. A blue fucker.
Compliments of the
young lady over there.
Who's that?
Your love spell has worked so well
that it has taken control over my body...
and making me do things I
would never do in my life.
Oooh!
Oh, shit! I'm sorry.
No, no, don't worry about it.
Don't worry about it.
I got it, I got it.
No, no. Tom, Tom, Tom.
It's fine. No, sit down.
No, no, no, no. It's fine.
I swear, don't worry
about it. No, no, no.
Guess what? It ain't magic.
And the wizard says to the little boy...
"You can't do magic
with your bare hands...
You need a magical wand". Ding!
Will you shut up!
Stop it!
What the hell is your problem?
Do you realize you could
have killed somebody?
First of all top of the morning, sen~or.
I'm sorry, officer. There was
actually a big bee in the car.
And I'm allergic.
A bee?
Sir, I'm gonna ask to
search your vehicle.
Could you please pop the trunk for me?
Sure.
Pop!
There you go!
So, what do we got?
A couple of smart-asses.
Whoa.
We got ourselves a couple of bombers.
Sure shit do.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Don't worry. Follow my lead.
Don't move!
You wanna tell me about
what you got in the trunk?
Yeah. I'm a magician.
I didn't know magicians carried C4.
What the hell is C4?
C4 is actually a very
powerful explosive.
Explosive! Are you out of your mind?
Wait, of course you are.
I can explain.
I'm doing a big underwater
trick on The Tonight Show.
And there's a big explosion
at the end. That's all.
That's it, all right. Out of the car.
Step out of the car.
You're under arrest.
I'm gonna write a letter.
Turn around. Hands behind your back.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be
used against you in a court of law.
You know the rest.
This is a big misunderstanding.
We're gonna be fine.
They're not gonna do nothing to us.
I need you to both remove
all of your garments, please.
Uhm,
can we both do this separately?
I mean, I hardly know this guy.
Yeah. Well, that's what they all say.
She doesn't feel comfortable taking
off her clothes. Maybe we should...
Either you do it...
or I do it for you.
Okay.
You're almost there.
Please.
Please, I am begging you. Please!
Let me do this some place else.
What is that? A mattress?
All right. It's your turn, sir.
Let's go.
Well, I won't be giving
her the cavity search...
so... it looks like it's
your lucky day, bastard.
Drop 'em.
Well, well, well.
What do we have here?
I was saving this trick for later.
Magic!
Hi.
Can I ask you something?
I'm not going anywhere.
What made you get into
your... profession?
I found my boyfriend
fucking another girl.
That's it, that's it. I knew it.
I'm joining your posse!
I just need to get
away from all this pain!
You know what I realize?
Some times you just gotta
face the music and move on.
Blah, blah, blah,
blah. Yeah, right lady.
"The hardest love to learn
is that which is dark.
"The kind that causes the most pain.
"It is up to the soul to
look past that dirty love...
"and regain the beauty that
illuminated so bright before.
Pure love".
Yeah, right.
My white pony is probably
in a glue factory by now.
Listen, I... I had to sleep with
a 70-year old man for two years...
to get that ring.
You should have kept your legs together.
You are an asshole.
You're a slut!
I'm aware of that but it's three karats.
Hi!
What have you got for me?
A 1968 Martin V 18.
A... a '59 Gretch Duo
Jet. A '59 Country Western...
and a... a 66 Khoner.
The '66 Khoner, can I see it, please?
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Do you like it?
I cannot believe my eyes.
This is the very guitar I played
for my wife at our wedding.
Are you sure it was that very guitar?
Yes. You see this?
R is Rajul, me.
M is for Moronah, my wife.
I... I always wondered what that meant.
That's... it's pretty amazing, huh?
No, no. It was meant to be.
I always knew it would come back to me.
How much do you want for it?
Name your price.
The others you can keep.
I have no need for them.
$3,000?
Done.
Wait. Wait.
Here's another $500.
Thank you for taking
such good care of it.
You are very, very
welcome. Thank, thank you.
All right. Uhm...
good day.
What are you doing?
I'm practicing. Gosh!
For what?
It's a new kind of mating call
I read in some onion newspaper.
It subconsciously attracts men to women.
By making your nose squeak?
Yeah. Why do you think I
had so many dates this week?
'Cause you were a ho?
Hey, John will drive us tonight, right?
No doubt.
Oh, my God! Look at this. Look!
Why does it have to go
here and not my boobs?
What you need to do is get
your titties done like me.
I might be hungry but I look good!
I think I'm leaning
on one of your boobs.
I can't wait to see this band play.
Yeah. Well, just don't puke all over the
mosh pit and you should be pretty good.
Oh, my God. I totally forgot about that.
Some asshole slipped me a mickey.
That was your boyfriend, Carrie.
Holy shit, you're right!
It's all coming back to me now.
He kept wanting me to go in his van.
You have to be more
careful on who you pick up.
Why do you think I stopped dating grips?
I caught him pretty quick and they have
absolutely no say on the casting process.
You've been going at
this for six years now.
It probably wouldn't hurt to
get in some acting classes.
Nah. I don't like how they want you
to go deep inside yourself and think.
Hurts my head all that.
Find your inner child.
My inner child is a dark muddy tunnel.
I don't wanna step foot in it.
What I can tell you from experience...
once you face the music, you just might
see that light at the end of the tunnel.
Honey, my light at the end of
the tunnel is an oncoming train.
Oh, let's go, people!
Who's the best designated
driver in the whole world?
John is!
Wow, I feel really buzzed.
That's 'cause I put yak in your drink.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Oh, look at these
girls. They're chickies.
Hi.
Hey, man, are you, are you gay?
No.
Oh, man, you gotta be gay. 'Cause that's
the only way a hot chicks like that...
would be sitting with a twinky like you.
Hey, pork chop.
Yeah.
You're just a bit jealous...
because you pump so many
steroids into your body...
that your dicks have
completely shriveled up.
Now him, on the other hand.
She's right.
He's always hard and
makes me wet all day long.
He can tear that ass up.
You know what I'm saying?
All up in it donkey-style.
No. Let's go, man. Let's go.
That was awesome.
I think I got one of his
oily chest hairs in my mouth.
Rebecca, I can stick up for
myself sometimes, you know.
I know. Just helping
out a friend, that's all.
You know, you're kinda
cute when you get turned on.
I was not turned on.
I beg to differ.
Well, what do you expect?
I'm just saying, you
know. I'm impressed.
See me in the shower.
Is that an invitation?
I'm drunk.
Come on!
Here's to the men that we love.
Here's to the men that love us.
But the men that we
love will never love us...
so fuck all the men. Here's to us!
Word!
Oh, God! I can't believe he's here.
Who?
Robert Rodale.
That guy is probably the worst director...
on the face of the planet. I've
seen every single one of his films.
By now he's doing his 100
million dollar piece of crap...
called Night vision.
It's about some guy who can
see in the dark or something.
Who really cares?
When does he start shooting?
I don't know.
Okay, Carrie, here we go.
Ha!
Perfect.
That girl never ceases to amaze me.
I don't believe it.
You need to believe it
'cause I live with her.
No, no, Richard's here.
Why do people have to bump into
their exes when we get past them?
Can't they just die after
we're done with them?
Do you want me to go ask him to leave?
No. No. No. Thanks, doll.
I'm just gonna deal with
this the only way I know how.
Becca, maybe you should just slow...
Oh, poo-poo on you.
I wanna dance. Come on.
John, is that you?
I knew we were totally
meant to be together.
Come on, girl, let's drop
it like it's hot. Come on.
You wanna drop it like
it's hot? Come here!
You believe in destiny?
I used to.
Wow, really?
I was always thinking about
becoming a scientologist.
They're always famous, you know.
Is there like an audition or something?
I could do a monologue
from Ron L. Hubbart.
Why?
You're right. She does
look better from a distance.
I don't know why.
Why don't you just leave us alone?
No, I think you do know why.
Because the night before you
did this, we looked at each other...
and said that we would
always be together.
And I believed you.
This was over a long time ago, Rebecca.
You just weren't giving me
what it was what I needed.
And what was that? Gonorrhea?
Sh, sh.
Get over yourself, Rebecca. Okay?
I don't give a shit about you.
I don't know if I ever did.
Why don't you just get
the fuck away from us, huh?
You see? I told you.
You and me. You and me.
Hi. That was so hot.
Rebecca!
Fuck!
Excuse me!
Yeah?
Do you wanna have sex?
What?
I'm totally gonna have sex with you.
What do I gotta do?
Nothing. I mean, you can try a
cheesy line on me but why bother.
What I'm telling you is no matter
what you do you're gonna get laid.
I don't get it!
But you're going to.
Let's go.
Can I buy you a drink?
I don't know. Can you?
I was thinking about
getting my boobs done.
But then I decided not to.
You wouldn't be able
to see my inner beauty.
I would just be like every other
manufactured Barbie doll in this town.
Just seeking constant
attention from every one.
Hey... are you listening to me?
I wouldn't let a
plastic surgeon go near.
I wouldn't go that far.
I could have my nose done and I
could have collagen put in my lips.
And you can be damn sure when I turn
35, I'm getting the full face pull.
Hey, baby.
Where have you been?
Right here waiting for you.
Who's she?
Just some skank who wants in my movie.
Hey asshole, I heard that.
Good!
You know, one day I'm gonna be big...
and you'll be sorry.
Sure, sweetheart. From
your lips to God's ears.
So why don't you go find
another dick to suck?
'Cause my movie is cast.
You know what?
It's guys like you that make girls think...
they have to play your
tickle my dick game...
to get anywhere in this fucking town.
Not anymore.
In fact, why don't you take
care of your own pencil dick...
and give the new girls in
this town a little bit of time...
to show their stuff before you
rape them of any chance they've got.
There're some people over for an
after-hour. You're welcome to join us.
What? Your mommy out of town?
That's funny.
So,
you good in bed?
'Cause if you're gonna point and shoot...
then I ain't interested.
You see, a woman needs
some warm up, you know.
Some pregame. You know what I'm saying?
You know you're white, right?
Don't you ever call me that.
You're kinda cute for a white boy.
Hey, Michelle, let's get out of here.
I was gonna go to this...
No, let's just go.
All right. I gotta go.
That's cool. I'll see you later.
What the fuck was that, you
fucking pussy? You let her get away?
I was onstage with a fucking
girl. I was gonna fuck her!
You like what I'm doing, baby?
Yeah, just don't talk.
What the hell? Ouch!
It's not bubble gum. You don't chew it.
Sorry. I... I can, I can do it better.
No. No.
I can't do this.
This is so stupid. I'm
not gonna sleep with you.
Come on! Just give me another chance.
It's not you, it's me.
Why the hell the chicks always say that?
I don't know. Hormones, morals,
12 years of catholic school.
All right.
Can we see each other again?
I don't wanna see anybody for a while.
At least till I know it's right.
But let me give you a tip.
Buy yourself a mango, cut
it in half and practice.
What's wrong with girls?
Why do we feel the need to
sleep with someone for revenge?
I don't know how we let
guys make us feel this way.
We're supposed to be
spiritually stronger than men...
yet I feel like we are so much weaker.
I don't know. Maybe we do it
because we need to feel wanted.
Maybe it's just to
fill that deep dark hole...
to make some of that pain
go away. A little company.
Or maybe it's okay to just take
time and go through things alone.
God! Why does love have to be so cruel?
Why did you do this, John?
I did it 'cause...
Becca, you're the most
beautiful girl in the world...
and when you are happy
you face lights up so much...
and I hated seeing you unhappy.
And I knew that if I got you this stuff...
your world would come together and
would, and would make your life better...
and... you deserve the
best life in the world.
I can't.
I can't do this.
No.
It just won't work.
Why?
I'm sorry.
John!
John.
Please, John, just get in
the car. I'm begging you.
Listen, I never meant to hurt you.
I've been through so much...
that... I just can't handle
being in a relationship right now.
Rebecca, do you know that
I've been in love with you...
since the very first moment I saw you?
I really thought that if I was patient...
things would just work itself
out, and I sat there and I watched.
When it just seemed like you'd rather
be with someone who treated you like shit...
than someone who really
fucking cared about you!
Here I am, Rebecca. Here I am.
You know, I'm putting
my heart on the line here...
and you don't seem to care at all.
I do... I do.
Why?
Forget it.
You know? I think I'd
really rather take the bus.
I'm scared.
Fuck!
Shit.
Pony.
White pony.
You're my white pony.
I guess what we're supposed
to do is find someone...
whose soul illuminates
as bright as yours.
To grow with in all the right ways.
John, you're my white pony. Yeah!
Stop the bus. Hey!
Stop the bus!
Becca!
Are you all right?
John.
You're my white pony!
Once you let go of dirty love,
your heart can open up to the
highest love of all... pure love.
The kind of love you've
waited your whole life for.
Just fucking globs of that!
That's good.
That was beautiful.
Thanks.
I got to go.
Take once a day to avoid outbreaks.
This is amazing.
I can't wait to tell
my friends all about it.
Es ma'gico.
(It's my thing)
Touch my baass.
Touch my fucking bass.
Yeah?