Shit. There's an immobilizer.
Someone doesn't want us to leave.
Oh, man.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
You're not going
to believe this shit.
- They've got one in my truck too.
- Well, now what?
What now is,
we wait for bravo unit,
then we all walk out
of here together.
Victor! Victor! Victor!
It's not gonna work.
Don't sweat it.
Stay sharp, fellas.
Contact, ten o'clock!
Victor! Victor! Victor!
Hold your fire!
Calm down. What's going on
out there? What's the damage?
We got hit hard.
There are no other survivors.
Okay. Continue on to base,
find Chernov
and tell her what's happened.
Get back-up. Got it?
- We got slaughtered.
- Got it!?
- Yes, sir.
- Get moving!
Hit the lights!
Position around the humvee.
Fire!
Cease fire! Cease fire!
Is that it!
Is that all you've got!?
Chernov!
Chernov! We need help!
That was the last one, Dr. Krieger.
Outstanding.
Absolutely outstanding.
Where are the whales, Jack?
This is a whale
watching tour, right?
Well that's funny,
because we scheduled them
to breach over our
boat exactly at 2:45 and...
You promised me whales,
George.
You hear that?
You go get us some whales
or you get us our money back.
I told you, we don't guarantee
you see any whales.
You get your three hours out
like everyone else
and take your chances.
Oh, we're staying out here until
we see some whales.
You might be,
but this boat's going
to be back in the harbor...
at the three hour mark exactly.
What's that accent?
You're German, right?
Well let me tell you something
about American customer service.
We're staying out.
Okay.
Can you come over here?
Can you hold on to this for a sec?
Where are you going?
Anybody want some beer?
George,
what are you doing driving?
What?
Hey, and watch out for those rocks.
They're pretty sharp and big.
We're alright, Jack.
Take us back.
But, George,
what about the whales?
You wanna see a damn whale,
you drive the boat
- George.
- This was your idea.
This was not my idea.
You blame everything on me.
You're the one who bought all
that picture-book stuff
with whales on it for Christmas.
You gave it to me,
but you wanted it for yourself...
You blame everything on me.
- You couldn't stop...
- You're the one who made us...
- talking about the whales.
- Sign up for Greenpeace.
Chernov.
- Good work last night, Katia.
- Thank you, doctor.
And they were some
of your best men.
The best money can buy.
Doctor,
why wasn't I informed about
the maneuvers...
outside the perimeter?
Because it was part of research.
Anything that takes place
outside on this island
is a security matter
that concerns me.
Captain,
I didn't want to trouble you.
I knew how you
would feel about testing.
Testing?
Yes.
Our subject engaged live targets.
You mean you tested him
on my men.
One unarmed,
genetically modified soldier
eliminated ten
heavy-armed men.
This is, um...
This is way beyond anything
the command would authorize.
Captain,
they're not even your men.
They're Chernov's people.
All of those genetically
modified soldiers,
or whatever you want
to call those creatures,
were all once human.
Yes, that's right.
Now, if you would excuse me,
I have to finish my painting.
Chernov,
is he back in his holding pen?
Yes. The time-released tranquilizer
worked perfectly.
Good. You know, if Parker wants
to get that much involved,
why don't you have him and
his men clean up all the mess?
I'm not sure how much more
of this I can stomach.
You mean having that hard bitch
as your boss?
You know well enough
what I mean.
Yeah, well I have my orders,
but you have a choice, Max.
Why don't you just leave?
I keep thinking I can do more
good by staying. We'll see.
Not much of a killer instinct
for a soldier.
Yeah, well maybe he'll send you
out there next time.
Don't you think
it's a little farfetched
- genetically modified soldiers?
- I've got it from a good source.
Nice.
You know, it looks like something
from your sasquatch file.
Very funny.
It's a surveillance photo taken
outside Krieger's research facility.
I don't need to tell you
how much trouble you can...
get into snooping around
military affairs, do I?
That's just the thing. All my
usual sources say there's no...
official military installation
on that island.
This is from another source.
Gorgeous shot of a lumber mill.
Who are these guys?
Okay,
so maybe it's super covert.
That's all the more reason not
to go snooping around.
Paul, Krieger has been known
to perform genetic experiments
on humans.
Now he resurfaces on an island
secured by soldiers.
Valerie, I trust your intuition,
but I am not going to have you
follow up on this lead.
Do you understand?
Fine, I'll do it on my own time.
What time? You work
fourteen hours a day on this paper.
I'll take some vacation then
You? Vacation?
I must have a few
weeks banked, right?
Why are you so determined
to follow this lead?
Because it's too good
of a story to pass up.
Paul.
Besides,
I've got a personal interest.
General.
- General.
- Doctor.
I'm assuming you've got
something interesting to show me.
See for yourself. Parker.
Please.
As you can see, General,
your money was put to good use.
Doctor, I couldn't care
about fancy facilities.
What I care about is your results.
I'm positive
that you'll be satisfied.
We'll see about that.
See for yourself.
He looks fit.
We have ten holding cells.
And now I have to show you
something really incredible.
Here's one we took the liberty
of field testing ourselves.
Chernov,
the gun.
- Shoot him.
- Shoot him?
Yes, but be careful.
Not in the eyes...
and not in the mouth.
- Subcutaneous armor?
- The skin itself,
twenty times more resistant
to puncture than Kevlar.
His muscles absorb the blows
and protect his organs.
Let him loose.
Let's see how he moves.
I cannot do that
without sedating him.
He would kill everybody
in this room including me.
Are you saying
that you can't control him?
I can control him,
but I have to work on his?
What good is that,
a weapon that we can't control?
You can use him under certain
circumstances for...
That's not what we commissioned
from you, doctor.
You asked me to create
an invincible soldier.
That's what I'm presenting
to you today.
Basically bulletproof,
no need for sleep,
and he can fight harder and longer
than any human soldier.
A soldier? You're making
brainless monsters!
Sedate him!
More!
If he can't take orders then he's
no better than a vicious animal.
But some more time
- and some more money.
- No more funding...
until you produce something
that we can use.
Chernov.
Working late, Max?
Hey, Uncle Max, it's me.
I thought I'd leave you
a voice mail
just in case you were
picking up your messages.
I responded to your last email,
but I never heard anything back.
I just wanted to check...
if we were still meeting
at that spot that you sent me.
Anyway, I'm heading up now,
so I'll see you soon.
Hi, this is...
Valerie Cardinal calling.
I'm calling to confirm that
you were able to get that...
boat captain that
I requested... Jack Carver.
That's right.
Terrific.
I'll be up there in a few hours.
- Thank you.
- See you soon.
- Ralph,
- What?
You made sure to tell jack
about the client today, right?
- He knows.
- He should be on the dock,
fueling up and preparing by now.
I thought I saw him going
in to the Golden Spruce last night.
That wouldn't be too unlike him.
Well his boat is just sitting
out over there.
Do you see him on deck?
No, pet, I don't.
Which means he's probably
sleeping it off.
He could be.
Well, aren't you going
to go get him up?
Hey, look, he'll be here.
I'm not going to have a captain
represent us,
showing up unshaven
and hung over for a client!
Get him up!
Yes, Pet.
Medusa, Medusa,
this is Day Beacon, over.
Medusa, Medusa, wakey-wakey.
This is Day Beacon, over.
Shit.
Turn his head.
Slowly, slowly.
Max,
can you hear me?
- Camera's working.
- Yes, sir, it is.
Max,
can you hear me?
Light.
Max,
what color?
Red.
Perfect.
And now?
- Green.
- Perfect. Perfect.
Take the light.
Max. Max, I think
you're going to earn us...
the rest of our funding.
Good, good, good, good.
- Stitch him up.
- Yes, doctor.
She'll be here soon.
Maybe you should take
the skiff out and check in on him.
You know he doesn't like
people dropping in on him.
Ralph, you're his boss.
Well, technically,
he's a contractor.
What? Are you scared of him?
Pet, you've heard all the stories.
That's all they are, stories.
Special army my ass.
He's a drunk.
Just because he drinks
doesn't mean he's a drunk.
It's special forces, pet,
not special army.
Whatever.
If you're not going to do anything,
I will. I'm gonna go get my gun.
Menopause.
Reload.
I don't think you should be
playing with him like this Pat.
Well, if he's as tough
as you all think...
he is he should be able to handle
a little shooting.
Someone could get hurt.
I mean you could take out
an eye or something.
Special army my ass.
Hi. Is this...
Day Beacon Boat Charters?
- Yes it is and you must be Valerie.
- Hi.
Hi. I hope I won't be needing one
of those where I'm going.
Hey, we've got some
paperwork to do. Come on in.
Keep flipping those, will ya?
I didn't realize the tour
came with a meal.
We head straight
back after lunch.
How much to charter
your boat for the night?
For the night?
We are not that kind of operation.
You chartered me for six hours,
okay?
Jack, did you serve in Germany
with a man by the name
of Max Cardinal?
- Who said I was in the services?
- Max is my uncle.
Very sorry, but I don't know
anybody by that name.
He said he was really glad to run
into you after he came out here.
Did he? I really don't know
the guy you're talking about.
Tischtennis.
What?
That was your safe word.
So you're his niece, huh?
That would make you
the hotshot reporter.
I prefer journalist.
Right.
What brings you out here?
I'm meeting with Max.
- Where, on that island?
- Yeah.
That island's off limits
to the public.
Everyone around here knows
to stay well away from it.
They're expecting me.
Right. That's why you
chartered your own boat
for a little night landing, huh?
It's a personal visit.
- Are you going to take me or not?
- No I won't.
Max would understand why.
Did Max tell you what
they're doing over there?
- No.
- You're not curious?
I'm curious how that fish
is going to turn out.
It's almost done.
I think Max might be in trouble.
That man is perfectly capable
of taking care of himself.
He set up this meeting.
He sent me a message and
I haven't heard from him since.
He found out that his client...
was doing something
that he didn't like.
Your uncle doesn't like things,
he'd quit.
I asked him to stay on.
You're writing a little story, huh?
That money will buy you
a ride exactly...
to the island and back.
That's it.
So much for camaraderie
between soldiers.
Hey, your fish is cooked.
Let's see.
This is burnt.
- They're crispy.
- Crispy?
No sign of anyone.
Max wanted me to meet him up
on the landing, in the woods.
Why didn't he want
to meet you up on the pier?
I don't know. Like I said,
all I got was the last message.
Wanna come with me?
No. I can take you to the shore,
but that's about it.
- Okay.
- You sure you wanna go?
Yeah. Max is waiting for me.
Fine.
- I can take you back.
- No. Let's go.
Here, take this.
- Thank you.
- I'm giving you exactly six hours.
You better be
here when I get back.
Max?
Miss Cardinal,
welcome to the party.
Let's go.
- Get rid of the boat.
- My pleasure.
You're late.
Check her body.
I hope you didn't leave anything
important on that boat.
You just killed a man.
I'd be more concerned
about yourself.
- What have you done with Max?
- You'll see soon enough.
I don't know why we're bothering.
The guy's dead. Bitch.
You go that way.
I'll check over here.
- Chernov.
- Docter I have her.
Good.
I'm checking for survivors. I'll be
back with the reporter shortly.
Russell.
Where are those guys?
Check the wood line, nine o'clock.
- Yes sir. Go.
- Move! Move! / clear.
We've lost contact
with Russell and Kyle.
- Send a backup team.
- 10-4. Backup team on the way.
Go after them!
- Go! Go!
- Go!
Go! Go! Go! Here we up.
- I'm handcuffed.
- Wait a second.
- Universal handcuff key.
- Where'd you get that?
Never leave home without one.
Turn around.
- Uh-oh. Here they come.
- Stop them.
- Here, do it yourself.
- Great. Thanks.
Are you okay?
- Okay.
- I'm great.
Come on.
Let's go.
Got it!
Holy shit!
- How about pitching in a little?
- I'm trying.
Try harder, please.
More help?
- What are these?
- Well that's sweet.
It's called a hand grenade.
Try throwing one.
- It didn't work.
- Did you pull the pin?
They're useless with the pin.
Hurry up!
- Did you throw it?
- Uh, yeah.
Wooo! Yeah.
- What's happening?
- Oh no.
Please tell me you have something
else back there.
I'm trying.
Hey, what's this thing?
- What the hell was that?
- I don't know.
What do you mean
you don't know?
Look out!
You've gotta be kidding me.
Come on. Come on.
Start the search.
I want confirmation they're dead.
Let's go inside.
Are you hurt?
You've been shot.
That's just a scratch.
You better get out
of those wet clothes.
Okay.
Turn around.
Okay,
you can turn around now.
Thanks.
I told you Max is in trouble.
It's my fault he stayed though.
I convinced him I could take
the story public.
It was his decision to stay.
What do we do now?
That's easy.
Get off this island.
I told you, I'm not leaving
without finding Max.
You can get us into the mill
to look for him
No. You hired me
as a water captain.
Shore excursions aren't
part of the deal.
Don't you ever think
about anybody...
except yourself and money.
Did I mention you owe me a boat.
Oh, it's cold.
I think I'm getting hypothermia.
Can I come in?
Okay.
Good. I have to take off
my wet pants, you know.
Turn around.
This bed's very uncomfortable,
- itchy.
- Sorry, the Hyatt was booked out.
- It's cold.
- Yeah.
You know what we used
to do in the military?
No. What?
It was called shared body heat.
Like spooning?
- You could say so.
- Okay.
Much better.
Is that your gun.
Well I never
go to bed without it.
Gone.
So, how was I?
Where are we headed?
There's a dock by the mill
on the other side of the island.
We're going to grab a boat there.
I told you,
I'm not leaving without Max.
Don't start again.
We're going to get a boat
and leave this island.
You didn't answer my question.
What do you mean?
What do I mean?
On a scale from one to ten,
how would you rate me?
Two.
Two? A two?
What?
Am I seeing this?
I'm gonna check it out.
Get your hands up.
Get 'em up.
You're coming back
to base camp.
Undress.
I wasn't talking to you.
I was talking to her.
You wish, huh? I was kidding.
Keep going.
I was really only a two.
Okay, a three.
Hat.
Yes sir.
Parker,
we need two of your trucks.
Yeah? Well I heard
what happened last night.
Why don't you leave
island security to us
and you just stick
to what you're good at,
- whatever that is.
- Just give me those trucks.
- I need a word with you.
- Oh.
Being cannon fodder for mutants
was never part of the deal
and there have been
a lot of us dying lately.
We compensate you well enough,
so you'll whatever
we tell you to do.
And if we're dead,
you won't have to pay us at all.
You don't like it you can leave.
Yeah? Well I'll take
what I know with me.
You'll be sorry for this.
Anymore complaints?
Come on. It's clear.
- Oww.
- You're my prisoner.
Okay. Inside.
You wait here
and I'll get us a boat.
I told you, I'm not going.
Your ride is leaving now, whether
you're on it or not.
I mean it.
Not without Max.
I'm going to bring the boat here
and you better be
here when I'm back.
You better be
Dr. Krieger,
you might want to see this.
Look at this.
Is that her?
Yes.
I thought she was dead.
- She soon will be.
- Chernov,
I want to speak to her.
Yes, sir.
Up.
Take her to the cell
until the doctor's ready.
Why couldn't they load
this up on the main dock,
huh? Tell me that. Then we
could have used the forklift.
Now we have to hump
all these ourselves.
This is ridiculous!
Oh, my back.
I think I compressed a disc.
Forget this.
I'm taking a break.
Oh. Oh.
I wouldn't be sitting down
if I were you.
You don't want the commandant
to catch you. Come on.
What the hell do I care?
Because of that tight-ass?
- What, am I a soldier?
- No!
- Whatever, man.
Oh, shit.
I've been thinking about
you all day, all day.
That's good.
Okay?
Okay? Okay?
Oh, my back! Oh, my back! Oh.
I was a goner.
Oh my god. You saved my life!
You saved my life!
- Oh my god. I was...
- It's okay.
Who the hell are you anyway?
What are you doing sneaking up
on me like that?
Hey! What are you two doing?
Who are you?
Answer me.
I said who are you?
I'm the food guy.
I'm the food guy
- I came for a friend, one of yours.
- Who?
Max Cardinal.
He's a good man, but he's gone.
What do you mean he's gone?
He got caught spying
and he's as good as dead.
Get back.
Oh, my back. Oh. My back.
- Get him off the boat.
- Hey,
there's someone down here!
He's got Parker!
Oh my god!
Where are we going?
Keep going!
- We got him.
- Oh, no.
Hold! Stop the boat!
- What's your name?
- Jack.
I'm Emilio.
Nice to meet you.
You owe me a meatball sandwich.
So, you are the cause
of our recent troubles.
Tell you what. Replace my boat
and we'll call it even.
Who sent you?
I'm just a driver.
I see.
You're just a simple boatman.
Is that your story?
I haven't said anything
about being simple.
Whatever.
We have your colleague
and I'm sure
she will have much more to say.
That's great. So you won't
be needing me then.
That's correct. I don't need you,
but as you're here
I may as well use you
to be part of my new experiment.
See you then.
Well I think that went quite well,
don't you?
He wasn't looking at me,
was he?
He was just talking
about you, right?
You mind if we sit?
I have a feeling this
is going to take a while.
Sure.
On three. I used to do this
in dance camp.
One, two, three.
Except we weren't cuffed
in dance camp.
So, uh...
you ever have anything
like this ever happen
to you and you get out
of the situation or
anything remotely like this?
I wanted to die fast, you know,
like by a shark.
Get up.
Take her to Dr. Krieger's office.
Leave us.
Sorry about the rough treatment,
but these people only know
one way to deal with intruders.
Sit down.
Dr. Krieger,
you should know that
the newspaper
is aware that I'm here
and will be alerting
the authorities.
It's all been taken care of.
The coast guard reported
you lost at sea.
What you don't know
is my bodyguard
is on his way to the mainland
in a boat.
Strange.
He told me that
he was just your driver.
You know, if he wouldn't
have turned around,
we would have never caught him.
Us being without
a helicopter these days.
You know that you
owe me a helicopter.
Where's Max?
Looking at you, you don't look
at all like your Uncle Max.
I want to see him
or I'm not saying another word.
You will see him
and you will say another word,
when the time has come.
Applying the foundation?
Sit down.
Go back and sit down.
You ever play I spy?
- Nah. You wanna play I spy?
- Yeah, let's play I spy.
Well, now, we can if you want.
Let's play I spy.
Okay. I'll go first.
- Okay. You got it?
- Yeah.
Okay. Is it a freaky doctor?
My creations.
You are looking at
the deadliest ground troop...
to ever walk the planet.
Have a look for yourself.
You won't find a more technically
advanced facility anywhere
in the world.
Max!
He can't hear you.
He just finished his treatment.
He's still coming out
of his sedation.
What have you done to him?
Made him a better soldier
than he ever was before.
Max is right. You're a sick,
egotistical maniac.
Let's not go over the top.
I'm just greed.
You can't imagine
how much money...
the government is paying
for research like that.
How can you live like that?
I live fine, thank you.
Let's continue the tour.
Jack!
Are you okay?
- Make them pay.
- Happy reunions.
He turned Max into one
of his creatures.
We like to refer
to them as genetically
modified soldiers around here.
Your two friends will be
undergoing the same process.
Your friend Jack
has real potential.
Did he say friends? Yeah, hi.
...
I don't know these people.
I've never even seen her before.
Then why did you try
to help them escape?
Escape? No, no, no.
He hijacked the boat,
and then he hijacked me.
I don't like him.
I don't even know him.
My process
will be a waste on you.
Yeah, that's right.
I'm covered in flab.
What should we do with him, sir?
May be just kill him.
No. No. No. No.
You don't want to kill me!
Come on.
I'll be your personal valet.
I can help you in many ways.
I'm the food guy! Oh,
Oh! No! Goddammit.
Come on! Will you shut up?
We've gotta escape.
Stop choking, you big baby.
Come on. Spit it out. Spit it out.
- Pick it up.
- Pick up what?
- What does it look like?
- Holy tomato.
Where'd you get that?
Come on. Let me get it.
Let me get it. That's pretty good.
That's very good. Buddy...
I... I got it.
Okay. Okay. Open the cuffs.
There it goes.
Now I missed it. You do it.
Okay up.
- Up like dance camp.
- One!
- Two! Three!
Okay. You do it. I can't do it.
You do it. You got it?
Come on. Just do it.
- Where is it?
- It's right there. Got it?
Okay, good. Nice. Nice.
- Hey, what about me?
- Come on.
Let's see if my work
on Max has been successful.
Release GMS nine.
Yes, doctor.
This room is making me
claustrophobic.
Whatever happens, I got your
back you got mine, okay?
Max.
You know this guy?
Man, he looks rough.
Good thing he doesn't know
you're banging his niece.
Hey, he used to be a nice guy,
okay?
- Max?
- I don't know, man.
He doesn't look so nice.
If I've done my job correctly,
your Uncle Max won't rip
the arms off your friends yet,
unless I give the command.
Max, remember me? I'm Jack.
I'm going to let you two sort
this out, okay?
Max,
- execute.
- Max, no! Don't do it.
Let's not get carried away,
please.
Max, remember me?
I'm Jack.
- Remember?
- Max!
Max! Kill them!
- Max.
- It's a dead end.
Max,
tischtennis. Remember?
Tischtennis
There's Valerie, up there.
Max, kill them!
Come on. Come on
- What are you doing?
- He wised up.
Release GMS 7 and 8.
Go! Go! Go!
Same team. Same team.
That's it? That's your plan,
stay here and paint?
- I can't get a clean shot!
- Get him! Take him down!
Stop.
We still looking for that broad?
Holy shit. They must
do a lot of humping here,
because those things
breed like rabbits.
Go.
Where are we going?
Run, hide.
I'm just a food guy.
Asshole.
Everybody, drop down!
Be aware!
Remember, eyes and mouth!
Mr. Masaki, it's Dr. Krieger.
I'm ready to deliver.
Are you still interested?
Good. We agree to the terms?
Wonderful.
I'll see you in Shanghai.
What day?
See you then.
- What is it?
- Doctor, the perimeter is overrun.
We are sustaining
heavy casualties.
I'm going to sound
an evacuation.
Let's make one thing clear.
You're holding your position.
My men are getting slaughtered.
I'm going to order a fallback.
You're not falling back.
You are holding your position.
Is that clear?
Sir, with all due respect...
go shove your civilian orders...
up your civilian ass.
Cover me!
Chernov.
- Doctor.
- Some problems.
- Eliminate Parker.
- Yes, doctor.
Chernov.
I need an escort to the pier.
- Copy that.
- Get back! Come on!
Sir, Dr. Krieger's personal
boat is readying for launch.
Of course. The biggest rat
is first off the sinking ship.
We sure as hell ain't
going to cover his retreat.
If we get there first,
we take his boat.
Get all remaining units...
to rendezvous
at rally point bravo.
All units, this is Claw Zero Six.
All claw units rendezvous at rally
point bravo. Confirm. Over.
Copy. Rally point bravo.
Come on. Pull back.
Pull back!
- We lost him, sir.
- We're going to have to leave him.
You are one persistent son
of a bitch.
Yes I am. Let me pass.
We're leaving.
Why don't you come with us?
Krieger still has my colleague.
Well Krieger's about to leave.
I won't let him leave with her.
I admire your loyalty.
It's something
in short supply around here.
But once Krieger gets
on that boat,
he's no longer our concern.
Okay. I'm going to put
my weapon down.
How do I find his boat?
Passageway,
back the way you came.
Follow it, the stairs down
to the ground floor
and head straight to the far
end of the building.
Thanks.
Wait a second.
Your gun is empty.
Take that.
Happy hunting.
Remember, aim for the eyes
or the mouth.
Thank you.
Parker.
Get everyone back to the boats
and leave immediately.
- But, sir.
- It's okay. Now move.
Where are they going?
They're withdrawing,
on my orders.
Traitor. Get out.
Parker! Parker!
Oh, shit.
Bitch.
Chernov.
- Chernov.
- Yes, sir.
What's going on down there?
- I'm on it.
- I'm waiting.
Give me two minutes.
I'm waiting!
- I'm waiting!
- Good.
You first.
Chernov,
let's go to the boat.
Tell your men to hold exactly
where they are.
Don't move.
Stay exactly where you are.
Let her go.
Let the girl go.
Chernov, let the girl go!
- Gun down.
- Dream on.
Let her go.
Gun down.
Kill him.
Max!
Max.
Let's go.
Jack! Jack! Jack!
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Those freaky things
are following you.
- Come on. Let's go.
- Can anybody hear me?
Can anybody hear me?
Captain, where's the boat?!
You must be joking.
Step back!
As my editor expected, we got...
a visit from the men
in black suits.
No story can run that
jeopardizes national security.
So what are you going to do?
I'll keep working on it.
That's good.
So, here she is.
Where'd you get that?
Insurance bought it for me.
- Wait a minute. Is that Emilio?
- Yeah.
He's my new deckhand
and my new cook.
- A pretty decent cook.
- Wow.
Well, I should probably
get back to work.
Hey, uh...
the day when you rated me two
out of ten you were joking, right?
Will I see you tomorrow?
Yes.
Two points.
She wouldn't see me...
if I was only two points.
Jack,
we got our first customers.
That's great.
Hey, Jack.
I think you owe
us some whales, Jack.
Yeah, we wanna see whales.
You hear that? The little lady
wants to see some whales.
They wanna see whales.
Come on, Jack.
This is boat looks like...
it's faster than your last one.
Where?
Wait...
Where are you going, Jack?
Jack?
- Jack?
- You do it, Emilio.
- What? I don't know...
- It's all yours.
- Anything about the whales!
- I don't care.
He's just having a little hissy-fit.
He'll come right back.
Just shut up.
You're scaring him. Jack! Jack!
He's German. He's emotional.
Come on.
I'm making franks and beans!