Let's dance, big dog.
Okay, all around defense, boys.
You know the drill.
Second Battallon found some new kind
of IED's.
I heard.
Hope you kept that thing Ellen
and the kids sent up for you.
If I can't eat it, forget about it...
especially fuzzy shit.
Vermont teddy bears ain't cheap,
soldier.
Teddy bear.
I ain't no kid, man.
Naw, man, it ain't that.
It's a good luck thing.
By the way, she's gonna ask.
Better have your story straight.
I'll tell her a goat ate it.
Don't you dare, soldier.
Don't you dare.
Go go go go!
Mortar. An eighty-three.
We gotta cIear that fucker
for the convoy.
Grab your squad, fIank 'em on the right.
Me and my boys'll go left.
Got it?
Roger that.
- Let's move!
Alright boys, stay on my ass!
Go go go!
Dowdy, Johnson, wait here!
Pena, Carver, against the fence!
I see them, Sergeant! I see them!
Get the fuck back!
Cease fire, Dowdy! Get the fuck down!
Dowdy! Goddamnit!
Sarge, Sarge, are you there?
Sarge, are you there?
That stupid sonofabitch, Dowdy!
He's got his ass pinned down
under the bridge.
Put Carver and Johnson on Dowdy
and suppress that fire.
Then hook to the right with Pena.
Hold your positions.
Your eyes on the road.
Roger that.
Let's move!
Johnson, Carver, we need cover fire now!
Stat! Stat!
Pena, Come with me!
Move! Move!
In position, Sarge.
There's a pick-up passin' me now, Ron.
I think there's gonna be one passin'
you pretty quick.
Right on, Sarge. I see 'em coming.
Let's get set for a double switchback.
Just Iet it roll.
It'll take the heat off Dowdy.
Then we get 'em on the way out.
Yeah, I got em, guys. Wheeoo!
I got the sonuvabitch!
You okay, Pena?
Still breathing, sarge.
I got 'em!
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
you wish, little buddy.
You just thank your ol' Uncle Deke.
Hey, way to tumble, meatball.
Open fire!
RPG! Get down!
(RPG: Rocket Propelied Grenade)
Doc!
Shit!
Alright, defense, now!
Get his shit off!. Get his shit off!.
Gut wound. He's losing a ton of blood.
We need an immediate medevac.
No! By the time they scramble a helo,
and get it out here
he'll be dead from sestemic poisoning.
He needs surgery FAST
or he hasn't got a prayer.
A bunch of us dellvered med-supplies
to an Iraqi hospital around here
about a week ago.
It's about five minutes away.
Area seemed okay.
No, no, fuck that,
Cohen, you know how long it'd take
to get clearance
for something like that?
Fuck the clearance.
It's on me.
I left before you got here.
I'll lose a stripe for
the sarge any day.
Same here.
Me too.
Fuck it.
You can keep your damn stripe Jackson.
This one's on me.
Carver! Johnson!
Stretcher, let's go!
Move!
We're going now.
Easy... easy.
Come on, breathe.
Hang in there, man.
Hang in there, Sarge.
Listen guys,
keep your heads up
and watch for movement.
How's it going up there, Jackson?
Looks quiet so far, sarge.
Can't this tub of shit go any faster?
We're losing him!
Yeah, well fast ain't gonna mean
dick if we hit an IED, doc.
We gotta play this thing smart.
It's all my fault, sarge.
Get off it.
You did your best, sarge did his.
Shit went down, okay?
That's war, Billy.
You just gotta regroup and move on.
Sarge, man, you think
DeIvecchio's got a chance?
I mean he was bIeeding out, man.
Gonna be pIenty of blood
where we're going. Don't you worry.
Yeah, but I wish there
were more of us, sarge.
I mean this city shit is way freaky.
Well, tell him to put
on some Depends, sarge,
then he can piss himseIf all he wants.
Listen, we're the last shot he's got.
I'd drive into hell in a
gasoline tanker for that man.
So if the shit goes down, so be it.
Dowdy, get your tall back on your gun.
Johnson, on the 240.
Carver,
I need an open watch, right now!
Doc, these guys run away
from you last week?
No sarge!
Jackson. Somethin's hinkey, man.
You guys stay frosty.
Alright, reposition the vehicles.
Am I dead yet?
No sarge. You're in a hospital.
We got to operate on you.
Okay... easy.
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
Gunshot wounds.
This must be one of the motherfuckers
who tried to whack us.
Fuck 'em. You go save the sarge first.
He needs O-positive blood,
and his intestine sutured -
-- sewn back together, understand?
No, no if we don't operate on them,
the others, they'll kill us.
There's others?
Yes. Down the hallway.
Operate!
Doc, give 'em some motivation.
No, stay on the sarge.
You, get some blood, now!
You! Get some anesthetic
and start surgery.
Take it easy, baby, we got you.
Easy now. Easy.
Sarge, are you okay?
You're okay. Easy.
Look, I'm sorry about all this.
We just came here for help.
Hey Sarge...?
-Yeah?
Some asshole has an RPG! Get down!
I'm always having to
save your ass, Pena.
Hey, that's my job, sarge.
Keeping you on your toes.
I guess I deserve a raise, huh?
The shit's hitting the fan.
Doc, how you doing?
It's getting hot out there.
Good.
Newsflash, doc,
sarge says we got to do it.
Doc, is sarge ready to be moved?
The operation's done
but I don't think --
No no no, no buts.
That's an order.
Okay, get him in there,
get him ready to go.
Listen, if it's too hot for gunships,
you give me fixed wing support, sir.
No, I don't have a forward
air controller.
Come on,
let's go. Let's go!
Move your asses, lot's go!
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
well that's just fucking great, sir.
Goddamnit!
Move! Move! Move!
Doc, the sarge, how is he?
We've got to get back to base ASAP.
Roger that, Jackson.
Doc says we gotta get there fast.
We need a shortcut.
Sarge, why the fuck are these guys
so pissed off at us, man?
Just cuz we're here.
Yeah, but I don't get it.
We shit-canned Sadam...
what, that doesn't count for nothing?
Yeah? Well how would you feel
if they were in Miami?
Don't even go there, man, because
Miami'd be a totally different story
Alright.
These guys would be toast.
Fuck with my home town
you're goin' down.
That's just the way it is, Alright?
That's my point, dumbass.
Nobody likes being occupied.
It's like living with your parents.
Doc...
Sarge...I can't make out a
word you're saying. Just relax.
Just go back to sleep sarge,
take it easy.
Let the anaesthetic do its job.
We've got this, Alright.
Hold your fire, too many civilians.
He's not gonna make it back.
Not like this we're not.
Sarge, this ain't cuttin' it.
Give me a man.
Let's go with the Louisana two-step.
Go Jackson.
Pena, you're up,
Louisana two-step.
Say hello to my little friend,
you fucking cock-a-roaches.
What the hell's a Louisana two-step?
You're about to find out.
Go Pena, go!
You Alright, Jackson?-Yeah.
You okay, Pena?-Yeah.
Good job, boys.
Wheeooo! That's what I call
Iraqification, motherfuckers.
Hey! Dowdy, you shut the hell up.
You show a little bit more respect,
Alright?
But sarge...
No buts!
That goes for the rest of y'all.
Let's get the hell outta here.
Back to base.
Guys, guys, I got an idea.
Cubans, hand-rolled.
All you got to do is ride the
smoke right to heaven, my friend --
Hey, Mr. Miami. It ain't over 'tll
we're back on base, Alright?
So you put those away.
Sarge, man,
you got to think positive, dude.
I mean guys,
you know what I think he needs?
Some prime ass Miami tall, my friend.
The meanest bikinis and
the best hotties in the world.
Every night's like girls gone wild.
That'll put a shit-eating grin
on your face, I swear to you.
I thought this war was over, Jesse.
We're building schools,
hospitals, roads,
Seems to me like we're getting a lot of
hate and discontent in return.
Makes me homesick for Afghanistan.
Steady guys. These folks are friendlies
until they prove different.
Stop--stop--STOP! IED!
Sarge, stop! IED!
Where?
Right there.
What's up?
We think we got an IED.
Just don't worry about it,
go back to sleep.
Count sheep or strippers or something.
Okay, listen up,
I want everybody to dismount
and move these people
back behind the truck.
Keep your eyes open.
Get those marshmallows ready.
Come on, let's get those sandaIs moving.
There's a big-ass fire coming up.
Coast is cIear, Aikens, take your shot.
Stop that kid!
Shit doc, get in there.
Holy fuck! Deke...Deke?
Is everyone all right?
Doc! Doc!
You okay?
How's the kid?
You Alright, man?
Oh my God. Move, move, move!
What's wrong with you, boss?
Where am I hit, doc?
Where am I hit?
I don't know, give me a second.
Why the fuck did you
run out like that, man?
You lucky son of a bitch, Deke,
it's just a fucking superficial wound.
It's just a scratch
on the surface, baby.
Jackson, get in here, please.
It took balls, Deke.
It took balls.
I got two sisters back home
as young as that kid.
I don't want my famlly to get hurt,
I don't want no famllies to get hurt.
It ain't what I signed up for.
It's fine, Deke, it's fine.
I ain't never seen so much blood on
such a pussy wound, buddy.
Hold him up, Hold him up.
Okay guys, we got work to do.
We need him in the truck fast.
You good?
-I couId have been killed, man.
You good to drive?
You want me to drive for you?
Yeah, I seen your driving.
Hey Deke, how'd it feel?
How did what feel, sarge?
When you got hit.
Yeah, right. Scary, I guess...
Peaceful.
Peaceful huh?
Ease up on yourseIf, sarge.
Y'know, I just want to get
us all home safe, Deke.
I just want to get us all home.
Hey, how's the sarge doin' back there?
Talking in his sleep.
Probably giving orders.
That sounds about right.
What about you, doc?
How you Holdin' up?
Till we get him back to base
I'm just one ball of stress, babe.
I don't know what it is, dude,
but I feel like a bucket
of chum right now.
You know, the shit they put in
the water to attract the sharks.
What, am I the onIy guy that watches
Discovery ChanneI around here or what?
Look, just don't think about it.
Don't think about it?
Wait a minute,
what the hell am I supposed
to think about,
you know what I mean?
Think about the best day you ever had.
Are you kidding? That's really hard,
man, how am I supposed to do that?
Okay bitch, I'll think about it then...
um, my best day...Probably when
I hooked up with the sarge.
Alright, well whatever you do on your
time with him is fine with me
just don't do it in front of me.
Fuck you, Alright.
Hey Jackson.
-Yeah.
How do you activate a car bomb again?
Why you askin', dude?
Because I think we're right beside one.
Sarge, we got ourselves a car bomb.
Roger that.
Deke, back it up, back it up.
we got a possible car bomb IED.
What the fuck do we do?
We back up slowly.
Backing up...
Run.
Get back! Get back! It's a car bomb.
Move it! Get the hell out of here!
In the alley!
Turn! Turn! Turn!
Keep your eyes open!
Don't bunch up! Don't bunch up!
Shoot them!
Sarge! He's hit!
Sarge is down!
Factory 12:00.
Sarge is hit! I repeat, sarge is hit!
I'm coming to see you now.
Jesse, give me a wall!
Damn! The engine's fried.
The engine's fried.
Doc man, Doc, come on.
Come on, you got to help him out.
Come on, you got to help him.
Romeo, Dowdy, we need a sweep.
Let's go!
Come on, man, hang in there.
Come on, Doc, come on, let's go,
let's go. Come on.
You got to help him out, man.
Oh Jesus! Fuck!
What? Come on, what is it? What is it?
His artery's severed.
Do something. Come on doc, come on.
Okay, we got you.
You're a fighter, baby, get in there.
Don't worry about it,
stick with us now, stick with us.
Shit!
It ain't your fault. doc.
I can't fucking clamp
this fucking thing.
It's just getting shredded.
Listen,
-What?
I want you to tell
my ma I...Iove her.
I'm not telling her anything, man.
You're gonna be there to tell her,
Alright?
Alright, listen up...
You guys better watch each others backs.
You watch each others backs...Alright?
You keep your ass up
-and you get home.
Get home.
Come on, Doc, man,
you got to help him out, man.
Say hi to EIvis for me.
He's not going anywhere, man!
He's going to stay right here.
You're not going anywhere,
you're staying right here.
You're a goddamn hero, sarge.
Come on, Doc...
What are you doing?
Come on, man,
let's go. Come on, doc.
No Pena, he's gone.
No man, what are you doing?
Come on, man?
He's gone. I'm sorry.
He's not going anywhere,
he's here.
Come on, bring him back.
You're the fucking doctor, man.
Just take it easy,
okay! It's over!
Pena...
What?
You gotta put your hurtin'
time on Hold, son...
we need your ass now...
right doc?
Goddamn right, sarge.
So stop bitchin'...and
act like you got a fuckin' pair.
That's how you pay your respects
back to Sgt. STalker, you hear?
Yeah, I got it. I got it.
Doc, ain't nothing about
what you did or didn't do.
It's just the way it is.
I need you guys.
Sarge, hurtin' much?
Pain's cool.
Means it ain't plantin' time.
So what are we gonna
do about this, soldier?
You tell me. We're trapped
Let's start with
getting untrapped first.
Get our own battallon.
Base can't help us,
they got hit by truck bombs.
And there's Still no air.
We got to hang on until troops
from all the way from brigade get here.
Fuck!
We'll do it ourseIves.
SaddIe 'em up, Jackson.
Now!
Pena, he was as much a friend
to me as he was to you.
And he was a good soldier.
He's in a better place
than this fucking hell, man.
But right now
we gotta do this right.
You understand
what I'm saying to you, soldier?
Yeah sarge. I do.-Okay.
Hey guys, it's a TripIe Decker
Hall Mary like we learned on base.
You all know what to do.
Carver, it's time.
You're on the left with the guys.
It's a shitstorm out there, Jesse.
You scared?
Hell no, man,
I'm just tired of this place.
Then let's go home.
Me and you.
Every step of the way.
Shit!
Our guys couIdn't make it,
but guess who did.
Romeo, let's go!
Go, go, go!
Those Johnny Jihads
got a hard on for us.
We got help comin'. But right now
we need a place to hoIe up, lieutenant.
Go my station.
Police station. Go left.
Romeo. Do it.
Got it, sarge!
I am Lieutenant Ahmed.
Your enemy are my enemy,
my friend.
We heard on radio you were under fire.
You guys came just
in the nick of time, buddy.
Just in the nick of time.
Where'd you get that pig?
Pig?
The M60, dude.
Blackmarket.
You need,
how do you say, an edge?
Oh yeah.
Got to have an edge, yeah.
WeIcome to the new Iraq,
my friend.
My home is your home.
Is not much, but it is ours.
Allah Akbah!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
What the hell's going on back there?
Don't shoot. He has a bomb.
Hold your fire.
[SPEAKS ARABIC]
HoIy shit!
Is everyone all right?
Thanks, man.
You're a straight up dude,
you know that, right?
Doc, see if there's
anything you can do?
Yeah.
Jackson?
-Yeah?
Cover his ass.
Okay.
Finding when and where to take
a pissbreak,
now that is truly the art of war.
What the fuck, Dowdy, come on man,
you're pissing on my boots.
Control your sprinkler.
Sorry, dude.
It's kind of hard to drain your
snake when people are bumping into you.
Hey, you know they got
pills you can take that'll
grow that little nub of yours.
Fuck you, Jesse.
Whoa man, now you got me
to piss on my boots!
Will you guys please
Control your dicks!
Hey, you guys think we'll be
doin' this tomorrow? Together?
people might start Talkin'
we make a habit of it.
That ain't what I mean.
I know what you mean.
Y'all kept your peckers hard
and powder dry... so far.
Keep it up you bet your ass
we're gonna come outta this together.
Every last swingin' dick.
Lieutenant, how many cops you got?
Not enough.
Kind of hard to keep
the position full, huh?
No. For every man they kill,
his brother or son comes to fight
in his place.
The rest of my men
are out on the street.
After weeks of quiet
we have many gunfights.
They are rattling our chain today, yes?
You got that right, Lieutenant.
Alright guys, load up.
Sir, we have one soldier KIA...
2 wounded,
and our squad leader is critical.
Now we need help, and we need it fast.
What is the ETA on your support column?
Captain...?
Fuck.
What's up?
We need to get sarge out,
we need to do it on our own.
No, we're gonna sit tight and
wait this shit out. Right here.
Sarge, with all due respect,
no fucking way.
He's bareIy stable.
We need to get him out.
Sorry, sarge. Doc outranks you
on this medicaI shit, and you know it.
What is this? Free stripe
hand outs all of a sudden?
Incoming.
Get the sarge down! Everybody down!
Sarge, you okay?
Dowdy, time to get
out the other stretcher.
CIear this shit away!
Up! Up!
All around defense, now!
Fuck!
You'll be Alright, doc.
Fuck, his stitches have torn loose,
we got major blood fIow.
He needs a hospital.
He needs a surgeon.
And he needs a real fucking doctor.
And he needs it now, man.
It ain't happening, doc.
Shit!
I got to go in.
I'll see what I can do.
I'll try and stitch him back up.
You can do that, doc?
I don't know! I'm just a fucking medic.
I've never done surgery before
and I shouIdn't be fucking doing it now.
But you're gonna fucking do it.
I'm not gonna Iay here on my ass
and bIeed my llfe away, doc, do it!
Do it!
Yeah. Pressure.
Get some morphine.
Morphine'll drop your
blood pressure too Iow.
I can't give it to you.
I got some IocaI shit that might
take the edge off, if we're lucky.
TyIer...?
Right here, sarge. I'm right here.
if I don't come outta this,
you get these boys home-you hear?
Don't fucking even go there, sarge.
Don't be afraid of it.
Afraid of what?
You taking over.
Is that all you think you are to me,
sarge?
A fuckin' way to dodge command?
No disrespect, sarge, fuck you.
Coming in. Easy.
Hold her steady. Just a second, baby.
Don't fuckin' move!
Get your weapon off my man.
Come on, Lieutenant.
This motherfucker was in the other room
on a cell phone when
we heard the first blast.
Now we're all in the same room again
and he's on a cell phone
in another room.
Do the math.
You don't belleve me? Check his fucking
cell phone. Hit the readout button.
[SPEAKS ARABIC]
No! No, no!
Cover the doc and sarge.
Nobody gets in here.
Nobody.
Who can I trust, if I can't
trust my own men? Tell me.
Lieutenant, you okay?
All that matters is
you can trust me - Alright?
I trust you, and we gotta
wade outta this shit together
or it's gonna fuckin'
sink both of us, okay?
Together, yes.
Keep pressure on that blood bag, Carver.
Jesus Christ.
I'm no surgeon, man.
Your folks are docs, right?
It's aImost the same thing.
I'm not wired right for this shit!
That's why I joined up, Deke...
To get away from all that pressure
to be daddy's little doctor
as soon as I finished basic,
they found out I was pre-med in college.
Bam! SuddenIy I'm a medic.
Sarge deserves better than this.
Better than I can give him.
Hey! One foot in front of
the other gets it done. Alright?
It's the onIy way we're
going to get through this shit.
You just gotta have faith.
Doc, how we doin'?
I don't know!
Maybe sarge can field that one.
Got a beat or two
left in me yet, doc.
Look, whlle you been goin'
through this I been thinkin' sarge,
And I never really thanked you,
I mean said the words for
everything you've done for me,
Thank the army, son.
I do...along with that judge.
What judge, sarge?
One who gave me the choice...
between servin' time or servin'
my country.
Are you trying to tell us
you were a badass once?
I had a thing for
fast cars that weren't mine.
Army straightened my ass out...
Shit! There's a special
fucking delivery for us.
Fuck!-Great.
Alright
we got incoming...Truck bomb.
Let's go.
double time...double time...
Deke, stay here with Doc
watch the doors.
Still here!
Romeo, you good?
Fuck!
Romeo, how you doing, man.
You guys good?
You Still got your balls, man?
Everybody Alright over here?
Good?
Yeah, we're good.
Nice work, guys
We took it to 'em, brothers.
Rest in peace, motherfuckers.
Whiskey, one one.
You are Lima Zulu at grid four one
seven eight eight one seven two two...
over.
Hey man, that was a fine piece
of homeland defense!
Alright, y'all, listen up.
I got some good news
and some bad news.
The bad news is ground
support's Still hung up,
the good news is the LZ
coordinates are on-hand.
We're getting our butts
air-llfted outta here!
Yeah baby, Alright.
You sorry ass bastards
Iook like you've been in a war.
You seem awful cheery, doc.
Sarge is Still kicking
in this world of shit.
Right sarge?
As soon as I get me a fllIup
I'm good to go.
See, I toId you you couId do it
man.
You got magic in those hands.
Where's Jackson?
I'm right here, sarge.
I see you heId Fort Apache, huh?
The team did.
Hell of a team, all of them.
You gotta eat somethin'
other'n adrenallne.
Break out those MRE'S.
You want to toss me one, dog?
Lieutenant, we gotta go.
I wish I couId go with you,
but I cannot.
As you can see,
I must stay with my dead and my wounded.
May Allah protect you
and make strong your hearts.
Back at you, brother.
Good luck, too, lieutenant.
You're a good soldier.
...and a friend.
Good luck.
Move out.
Hey Jackson,
not too much loving down there, Alright?
Well, she ain't the prettiest
landing site I ever did see.
But she's a damn sweet one,
I'll tell you that.
Hey guys, hang on.
Sarge wants to say something.
Now that we're getting out of here,
I just want you to know
that every breath I take from now on,
I owe you.
And if you live your lives
with the same spirit you had today,
it's all gonna work out for you.
So make your lives count for somethin',
you hear,
'cause you boys are the best
goddamn soldiers I've ever had.
Alright guys,
the chopper's going to be here soon.
I need a full defense. Let's go.
Alright, we're on it, dogs.
You think you can get us some R&R sarge?
No problem, Billy.
Hey Dowdy,
where you gonna go for some R&R sllck?
Paris, dude.
Whatcha gonna do in Paris, Billy?
Gonna go to up to the top
of the EiffeI Tower,
and take me a long sIow piss on France.
Me and Craig,
we're heading over to DisneyIand.
Yeah, I know it sounds corney,
but I just I want to feel like
a kid again, you know,
get to feellng so old
so fast around here.
see, I don't know if it's just me...
but I've always kind
of had this thing for Snow White.
She lives with seven dwarves...
shit,
she's got to be a stone freak dogs.
I Iove it.
So doc? What about you?
I don't know, man.
I can't Iet myself think that
far ahead, y'know.
I just gotta get myself through today.
Hey Tyler, what about you?
Maybe I might go back to
that hospital we was at.
See if this nurse there wants to go,
I don't know, dancin' or something.
Aw man,
there ain't no place to dance in Iraq.
There's got to be,
hell, you can dance anywhere, man.
No, dude. I can't dance.
You can't dance?
Man, all you gotta do is just bounce.
Like this?
What the fuck is that?
Look, all you got to do is just...
you know, get ziggy with it,
you know, like this.
Last time this guy
got ziggy with anything
he got arrested for indecent exposure.
Him and the dude he was dancing with.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Dowdy man,
I can't watch you dance
like that without a fucking beat.
Johnson, lay that beatbox down, man.
Okay,
I'm going to throw down a serious beat.
Okay, here's the man with the beat box.
Go go go go. Go.
Tear it up. Tear it up.
Oh oh. That is Romeo's mating dance.
Pump it up, pump it up.
Yeah, Dowdy!
Whiskey One one...over.
Copy that hotel six four...Sarge.
Hey Hush up...hey hush up...
Soul train's over.
Somethin's poppin' on the net.
Evacuation terminated...repeat,
evacuation has been terminated.
Fuck!
Jackson! Mount 'em up.
Sarge, the chopper's coming,
we're getting picked up.
Picked up by who, Jackson.
Our chopperjust got hit by an RPG.
What?
They need our help. Saddle 'em up.
Move.
Oh man. Shit.
Come on, you heard the sarge, let's go!
Move move move move!
Guys, you heard him.
Go! Move! Move!
We were on our way out of here,
goddamnit!
Bullshit!
Fuck!
hotel six-four, this is Whiskey-one-one,
send your Ioc-stat, over.
Loc-stat 416-927-623-Shit!
Fuck!
We're never gonna
get outta here are we?
The shit got deeper. So what?
We just gotta put on
our fuckin' rubber boots now.
And do what?
Stand by our men.
Go check for survivors.
Survivors? What, you shitting me, sarge?
Nothing's gonna be left.
Shit
Fuck, that's a bad omen.
I'm telling you, that's a bad omen.
help me get him up.
Get him up on the bench!
Move!
Move him up.
Sorry, sarge.
We're gonna get you home, I promise.
Poor sons of bitches.
That's got to be it.
Whoever brought down
that chopper couId Still be out there.
First, second fire teams, move out.
Watch your backgrounds.
Jeez.
Now.
Hey! You want hate?
Well, I do fucking hate!
I hate all of you people
and your shithole country.
You better run before
I put a slug up your goddamn ass!
Then you'll be dancing
the funky chicken motherfuckers!
Troy, what's the matter, man.
He's just a kid.
He's a kid with a gun.
He'd kill you the same way a man would.
I didn't come here to kill kids, man.
No. No you didn't.
You came here to do your duty,
just like the rest of us.
Just don't think of 'em, okay?
That road goes nowhere, man.
You're going to need this, buddy.
Good job guys.
You boys good?
We are.
Doc. Call the graves.
Let them know.
Alright, saddle up.
Copy that AIpha Three Zero.
Take cover!
Piece of Horse shit.
Sarge! We lost another engine.
Dismount! We're sitting ducks up here!
Jackson,
get them under cover across the road.
You go! Go go go!
CIear the truck.
We're not going to Ieave them behind.
How the hell are we going to get you
and the sarge out of here on foot?
Don't worry, sarge, we got you.
Take cover.
Return fire!
Sorry, sarge.
Sorry sorry sorry
Cover me!
I'm hit!
How bad is it, doc?
You'll live.
Reloading!
Guys, with your firearms.
Conserve that ammo.
Doc, get on that fucking radio!
It's not going to make a difference,
goddamnit!
No one's coming up fast enough
to mean shit.
Yeah, what are we supposed to do
when we run out of ammo, sarge?
Fuck Tommy,
get some more from the truck!
Yeah? To watch them fucking blow us up?
I fucking don't.
Man up, Johnson!
Who the hell are those guys?
I don't know,
but they're putting out a sniper team.
Wheehoo! Bullseye!
Dammit, I Iove those snipers!
It's okay, Rick.
We're Alright now, man.
It's not okay, man.
Lay him down. Let him down.
Romeo, how's the Ieg?
You gentIemen Alright?
We're good, sir.
Thanks to you.
I'm Sgt. DeIvecchio...
1 st Cav...these are my men.
Lt. Banning, Ohio National Guard.
This is Lt. Diggs, and Sgt. Wlikes.
And I believe
you've aIready met my sniper team.
That was safe shooting, man.
I mean... uh... sir.
Helluva shot.
Jesus Christ,
we got their distress call...
Wish we couId have been here sooner.
Our truck got shot to shit.
Mind giving us a ride back to your base?
No problem.
But we do have to make a stop first.
As you can see we're an MP-unit.
Have some prisoners to drop off.
We're not picky, sir.
Carver, Aikens...
get the 50 caI off the truck.
Lt. Diggs,
make some room for these guys.
C'mon sarge.
Don't be such a tough guy.
We're almost home.
A little Morphine'll knock
that pain right out.
Yeah, things got
a bit active back there, huh?
You know, we Iost a good man today
because of you fucking Johnny Jihads...
We kill enough soldiers,
America Will lose its stomach for Iraq.
It is your history.
Your Engllsh is pretty good.
I was educated in London.
Yeah? What you study?
Bomb making?
Beheadings?
Baby killings?
Law, actually.
Aw, that's fucking hllarious.
You kill our boys. We kill yours.
Kids are butchering kids.
For what?
Explain it to me, huh?
It is a Holy War.
Talk to Allah. Not me, crusader.
God wants you dead.
We were safer under Sadaam.
That I know.
And so do my people.
You only brought more terror
to our country.
Not Iess.
After 9-11 , we gotta take the fight
to the enemy.
And Sadam was our enemy,
but why do YOU have to be our enemy,
Because of my brother's wedding party!
Bombed by you, by mistake,
or such was the cIaim.
My brother was no insurgent,
no, he belleved in you
and you killed him.
You killed my parents, my cousins,
but you missed me.
And that was your mistake,
for I Will fight
you now until my last breath.
This place Iooks like a
fucking dog kenneI.
These guys are all severely dehydrated..
Jesus.
Come on, Jackson, let's move, man.
There's no insignia
on these uniforms, sir.
CIA and its contractors run Camp Zebra.
It's for ghost detainees-
high-vaIue interrogations
of guys the Pentagon
wants kept off the books,
but that is strictly off the record,
Alright?
Yes.
-Come on, let's go.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm Comandante Fredrico Cruz de Ia Roha.
I am a warrrior.
But my battIefield is here, with you.
My skills are extraction of information.
So, I Will share my knowIedge with you,
and you Will share
your knowIedge with me...
...sooner or later, that I promise you.
With the soldiers we are losing
to these despicabIe IED's,
We have orders to push
the envelope of interogation.
And the Geneva Convention?
Does not apply here at Camp Zebra.
These are not prisoners of war.
These are terrorists.
Information!
Information.
Talk to me.
Sgt. Wlikes, can you make sure
that water gets on our trucks, please?
Sir, this place, don't it bother you?
It's not my call, Jackson, Alright?
They're in charge of interrogation.
We're transport.
He's got his orders
just like I've got mine.
That's bullshit.
I've buried some fine men, Alright.
And you're gonna too.
If we can bury fewer of them,
that is a good thing, Jackson.
That's a good thing.
Sarge, I got a big problem here.
Lt. Banning brought these prisoners here
for interrogation
Shit, this place...it's into beatings
and torture and shit like that.
Sorry son, I'm Iosin' it.
You have my command now.
He's fine. It's just the morphine.
So what, if it saves one American llfe,
who cares, right?
Yeah, Iook at what they did to Sgt.
STalker, man.
And the sarge.
Never mind what's been happening to us
all fucking day.
Fuck them, man. They deserve it.
This ain't about them...
It's about us.
That we stand for something...
or we don't.
We got a code
of uniform mllitary justice
that says this type of shit don't fIy,
we have a duty not to walk away.
Fuck it.
I'll go it alone.
You're not going alone.
I'm not going to llve with this.
No fucking way.
You know what, Jackson,
I do stand for something.
This isn't it.
Let's go.
Carv?
Where the fuck you going?
They always got my back,
right? always.
But who the fuck has your back
all the time?
I do.
Serious man, so fuck it.
Watch the sarge.
You're putting yourseIf
into a world of hurt, doc.
Maybe.
But I know right from wrong, Billy.
This is wrong.
And if it's crossing the llne...
then fuck the line!
We're being smart, dude.
What are you doing, Jackson?
Sir, you do not
have to be a part of this.
Part of what?
Cut him down.
Weapons down! Now!
Weapons on the fIoor.
What in God's name are you doing,
soldiers?
Rellevin' you of your command.
I work for the CIA.
You have no authority over me
whatsoever!
I say I do.
Guess we'll be sortin'
that shit out Iater, huh?
You are making the biggest mistake
of your llfe, soldier.
All of you.
If you walk out that door
with MY prisoner --
He is no longer your prisoner.
The entire weight of The Agency
Will fall on your heads -
-- all your heads -
and for what?
For your enemy?
It's insane!
No, this is our duty --
Banning,
you're just going to stand there?
Let's go.
Banning...
Let's go! Move it!
Move!
Sir, just tell your commander
that we took your vehicles at gunpoint
You're right for doing this.
I'll round up my men,
you get the prisoners out of their cells
and we'll get the hell out of here.
Sorry I put you in this position, sir.
I never liked this place, Jackson.
I hope you know that.
I'll see you out there.
Move! Let's go! Front of the gates.
Nice work, Doc.
Keys, where they at?
Weapons down!
How about you guys first?
Put it down...nice and sIow.
You'll never get away with this.
Get the fuck in there and shut up.
Okay, your ribs are cracked.
It won't take the pain away,
but at Ieast the pain
Will Iet you know you're Still allve.
Hold on a second.
Private, see what we've got up here.
Turn right! Turn right!
Do not turn, I repeat Lieutenant,
do not turn! It's an ambush.
Warehouse! Warehouse!
help him up! help him up!
Group! Get to cover in the warehouse!
Move! Cover's this way!
Go! Go!
Get to cover! Go! Go!
No, we've got to keep moving!
We're in a kill zone!
Take cover!
Pena, Romeo, guard the fIank!
The bastards
ain't killing us today, man.
Not today.
Move me by the door.
Sarge, don't push it --
Shut the fuck up, Doc!
Morphine's kicked in.
That's an order.
Lieutenant, we need a perimeter.
Sargeant Wlikes,
give me a defensive perimeter.
Take some men. Go! Now!
Kelly, Cooper! Now! Now! Now!
Doc, come here!
Oh, Jesus Christ!
Come on.
They're walking rounds in on us.
Ain't no job for MP's.
Nah man, it's a caIvary thing?
Give me a heads up and I'll go with you.
I'm so tired of carrying your ass.
Bullshit!
Ro, keep an eye on Troy.
Pena, you're with me.
Let's go.
Move it!
Put pressure on that.
Put your hand on it, goddamnit!
Christ, take this and wrap it
around his Ieg, he's fucking fine.
Hey, those are our sniper boys.
Robin, Sallnsky, we got men down.
Move on it! Move!
Got to get you up.
Got to get you to safety.
Deke! Deke! I'm coming.
Doc, you got to save him.
Move! Move! Move!
He's been hurt bad! ReaI bad!
Fix him up, doc.
Take it easy.
Carver...
What have we got, buddy?
What have we got?
Jesus fucking Christ!
Sarge...
Was it worth it, sarge?
Carver, fight it, please.
please say goodbye to my little brother.
Dog, don't go...fight it dog. Fight it!
Fight it, please!
please, Carver...
Hold him down!
Someone Hold him down!
Do something!
We're all here with you.
We're all here with you, Deke.
We're all here with you, buddy.
We're all here.
Deke!
He's gone.
Fuck!
Goddamn this place to hell.
There ain't one thing in this place
that was worth Deke.
Not one!
Not one.
How the fuck am I gonna make it
through without him now?
I can't.
I'm fuckin' fucked.
Craig...
You Still got us...
all of us.
Jackson...
-Yeah?
I need a help. Now!
Sorry doc.
The other ones need you.
We got to go.
It never ends.
There's no fucking rest.
Lieutenant...
Sir, with all these bombs,
fighters Will be drawn here like
flles to shit.
Doc'll do what he can
to stabllize your guys
but after that we gotta jump.
Bombs chewed us up, sir.
If the fighters come,
our llnes won't Hold.
Okay, then let's saddle up.
Weapons and ammo of the dead, Alright?
Gotta work fucking miracles here.
Doc.
Yes.
Gimme a shot of adrenaline.
What?
You heard me.
I gotta be sharp. Come on.
But sarge, the crash from
an adrenaline surge couId kill you.
And most likeIy Will.
You can stick your diagnosis up
your ass.
Just do it. That's an order.
That's an order?
Fine, but you know what, sarge?
We survive this shit?
You get my ass transferred.
I'm through being a fucking medic.
I hate it.
I been seeing my guys
get killed all damn day!
Okay.
I'm not cut out for this shit.
I got the bodies of good friends
to prove it.
Fuck, come on.
Your shot? Here's your goddamned shot.
Steady. Steady, doc.
Hold that.
Hold Still or
you're going to fucking get it.
You're doin' great,
and you got nothing but talent.
Don't ever forget that.
But you ain't God and onIy
He couIda saved Ron and Deke,
so stop Talking shit.
I'm Still breathing because of you.
Did you forget about that?
I know I didn't.
IED!
Look for survivors, doc! Go!
Pena, cover me!
Shoot anything that moves!
Your guys did this!
It was your guys that did this!
Fuck.
How many men do I have dead?
How many men do I have dead, Jackson?
I want to see my men.
I promised my men
I'd bring them home safe, Jackson...
I promised their famllies
I'd bring them home...
I promised that I would...
...take care of them for them...
They were just weekend warriors,
for Chrissakes.
They wanted to help out with floods
and emergencies back home,
not fight a war in Iraq...
and I commanded them,
and I got them killed.
How am I going to explain
this back home,
I wish I had answers for you
but I don't.
We were trying to do right thing
by these prisoners,
and instead...
Shit!
They were better off
in those fucking cages.
Goddamn!
Good intentions don't mean shit here.
We'll call graves,
they'll take care of the bodies.
But we gotta get out of here now.
Okay.
We have to help ourseIves, Lieutenant.
Because no one is coming to save us.
Not today.
Let's go.
Okay.
Pena, guys...let's go.
This shit's not going to stop.
Your boys did your best for them.
But right now it's time to make it ready
Eyes and ears are everywhere
These fucks want us,
Iet them come get us.
I'm sick of this shit.
Deke's dead...STalker's dead...
And we're Probably dead too.
And for what, Sarge?
I joined up 'cause of 9-11 and WMDs,
and Iraq ain't got shit to do
with neither one.
Iraq don't mean a goddamn thing to me,
sarge!
Not a goddamn thing.
You ain't fightin' for Iraq, numbnuts.
You're fightin' for Romeo and Aikens,
and us and these Ohio boys
and Iraq just happens to be the place
where we have our sorry asses.
This ain't nothin', you hear me?
Just keep your shit focused.
Training and muscIememory
Will take care of the rest.
Today ain't gonna be over
for a long time, man.
It's going to last, dogs.
Hey sarge, check it out.
Doc, get me up.
Jackson...check it out.
Shit.
Fuck, this place has no fucking mercy,
does it.
Think they can smell blood, sarge?
Because it's like they're trackin us
like woIves...like fucking woIves.
We'll never outrun 'em,
not in this truck.
And we're short on ammo.
Jackson...what do you think?
I don't know about you guys,
but I'm tired of runnin'.
Me too.
Lt. Banning, we got troubIe on our ass,
here's the plan, sir...
Open fire!
Johnson, more ammo, hurry up!
Lieutenant!
Johnson, I need a mag!
Johnson, stay Iow!
Johnson, I'm out!
Johnson!
-That's it. I'm out!
Choke on it!
You piece of shit! Die!
What do you got?
What do you got, huh?
Fuck! Fuck!
Doc! Come check out the sarge.
Alright, what you do to yourself now?
Come on, hurry up,
Doc, take a look at it.
Lieutenant,
we got to move these men out.
What do you see?
It's not too bad.
Incoming!
You got a gift, doc.
Use it.
Stay down!
Sarge, no!
Okay, mother fuckers!
What are you doing?
Sarge
What you got? Huh?
Hey, sarge!
Sarge?
No! No! No! No!
No!
I falled you, sarge.
The mission was to save you.
And my best wasn't good enough.
Look sarge...he went out like he lived,
y'know, with the heart of a llon.
We gotta have heart too...
you know, we owe him that.
All this shit...
all I did...
we all did...
it was for nothing...
it was for fucking nothing!
No...
you saved him, doc,
you saved him
so he couId save all of us.
and that's not nothin'.
and Sarge woulda been the first
to tell you that.
We need a perimeter.
Craig, those guys had M-16's,
so that means they have ammo.
Find it.
I want him turned over to competent
military authority
...and treated right.
You have my word.
Lieutenant, thanks for the Humvee.
I'll turn your men over to graves.
This fucking place.
It ain't nothin'.
We just gotta make our lives
count for somethin'.
We did our duty today...
we're soldiers...
that's ourjob.
That's ourjob.
Let's go.
The Department Of Defense
has confirmed the deaths of
the following American soldiers killed
in Iraq on April 12, 2004:DELVECCH
' 'The greatest treasure
the United States
has is our enlisted men and women.
When we put them in harms way,
it had better count