Oh, something's
back there.
Oh.
You got one, too.
Oh! Thanks.
You're welcome.
Oh.
Nice outfit. I meant
to tell you back there.
Thanks.
Yours, too.
They think I'm crazy
to get this
for flying.
Me too. Shows
what they know.
Yeah. It's
all about taste.
I'm Dawn.
Dee.
Cool. Dawn-Dee. That's so cute.
I guess so.
Shall we
take this baby up?
Sounds good to me.
So what's next?
Uh. We start the engine and
we take off into the sky.
Okay. They make it sound so easy.
That's how they
explained it to me.
Oh-uh, tell me if I'm
doing something wrong.
Okay. But I'm sure you'll know first.
I'll just pay
close attention.
Wow, I feel like I'm
at Driver's Ed again.
Hey, great
office supplies!
Oh, thanks.
That's a cute pen.
Alright!
I want to take
some notes.
Okay. Alright. So, seatbelt, check.
Mirrors?
Don't see any.
Um. Blinkers?
Headlights?
I'm just gonna get my book
out. Okay. Um. Alright.
Well, I turn on
the master switch,
then the ignition?
Okay.
Push the throttle.
We're flying!
Turn! Turn!
I did it!
I can't believe it.
Okay. Miss St. Dom
and Miss Dee Twiddle.
We're gonna be flying
over some incredible sce-
Amazing? Incredible scenery.
No!
Ladies!
Ladies, stop the plane.
Ladies! Ladies! Uh! Oh!
Stop the plane!
Alright, here we go!
Up, up and today!
Oh- Oh, God!
What's
wrong, Frank?
Bernie's lost his mind. He
took off without clearance.
Bernie?
That'd
be a first.
What the hell
is he thinking?
You can ask
him yourself.
Oh my God.
They took the plane.
Who took the plane?
Two blondes.
Blondes.
Blondes?
Oh my God.
We're flying!
I can't believe it!
Do you always get this
excited when you fly?
Yeah. Don't you?
Sure.
So when did
you start flying?
Well, today's
my first lesson.
Really? Me, too.
Oh, that's funny.
Sean Bromley
steps up to the tee,
he's an amateur in
this Pro Am Tournament,
and as
you might see,
a par here could tie him for the day.
Oh my God!
We're gonna crash!
Look at that!
What a shot!
Right for the pin.
A hole in one?
Could it be?
That's pretty
freaking low.
Do something!
What?
Turn it off!
We're gonna crash!
Run for your life!
Look out!
Oh,
Oh!
Ladies and gentlemen,
the airplane has
just made a hole in one.
We're going up to the plane right now
there are two
people inside,
They're okay!
There are two women
who just came
out of the plane.
They seem to be okay.
We come in peace.
They're blond.
Is there
a lawyer in here?
Uh, I'm a lawyer!
Yeah, me too.
I'm a lawyer.
I'm a litigation attorney.
Yeah, right here.
So,
the bastard's
living in Vancouver.
Can you
believe the nerve?
Took an add out
using his real name.
"The Beaver
Patch Lounge. "
Seems like old Louie
hasn't changed a bit.
But the Witness Protection Program
don't know nothing about this.
They will soon enough.
Let me take
him out, boss.
It would give
me great pleasure.
No.
We need someone
to move undetected.
Too many FBl
protecting him.
In and out, in
the blink of an eye.
The Cat's eye.
The Cat?
Who better
to kill a rat?
The perfect assassin.
Still completely
unknown even by me.
A mastermind killer with an IQ
off the scale of normal humans.
She's never failed.
Even her victims haven't
seen her. A ghost.
She's not completely unknown
we know she's a woman-
Don't interrupt me! Who's the
freaking Godfather here, huh?
I'm sorry, boss.
Alright.
A ghost,
that never
leaves a trace.
Send half the kill
money to her contact.
If she nails
this one,
we'll let her take out
the infamous Mr. Wong.
Looks like I got
another job, Kit.
Woo Hoo,
party time!
The Godfather
wants me
to take out
Lou Rimoli
at the Beaver
Patch Lounge.
I thought
you were retiring.
Let me take this one.
You have enough kills.
I have to do
this last one, Kit.
A final favor
for the Godfather.
Besides, doing Lou
Rimoli will be a pleasure.
I promise,
after this one I'll turn
the claw over to you.
Meow.
I love you.
For driving
without a license.
Pay a $100 fine and we don't
even have to show up in court.
Aw, those cops
are so sweet.
I know, they
were cute, too.
I know.
Look at John Daley.
I mean, please!
Come on, look around.
Check all this out.
250,000 tons of snow.
All for me.
For my vision.
For my picture.
When I say "Jump" the
studio says "How high"?
Hey!
Oh!
All right! Let's shoot this
thing before the snow melts.
Where's my
megaphone guy?
Too slow!
You're fired!
Get me a new
megaphone guy.
What are
we listening to?
Oh, that's The Sound of Music.
Oh, cool.
What's the
music called?
Move! Hey!
Nobody yells "move" on my set.
I'll tell you when to move.
Move!
Oh!
Are you okay?
Those jerks!
Who were those
crazy blondes?
Are they trying
to get killed?
Didn't they see there
were no crosswalks? Jeez.
God! Stupid
Hill Piggies.
They'd better not
have scratched my car.
I know.
Are you okay?
I think so.
Uh, I
think so, too.
What a day.
Take a left here
and then two rights.
Wait, no. I'm sorry. T ake a
right here and then two lefts.
Wait. Can you
say that again?
Um, I don't think so.
Hey, are we
going in circles?
No, don't be silly.
Go left. Okay,
turn left and just
Here we go!
Wait, sharp right.
Woo! I'm dizzy!
Beep! We're here!
Oh! I'm in this one.
How long have
you lived here?
Nine months.
How about you?
Not nearly that
long. About a year.
Oh. Hey, you wanna come see Virgil?
Is he cute?
He's really cute.
Sure!
It's so cold.
Are you a magician?
No, it always
does that.
Really?
Can I try?
Sure.
I love it! Wow!
I got to see him.
Virgil.
Virgil's your dog?
No, Virgil's
not a dog.
Oh, there he is. Virgil's a turtle.
Oh, Virgil.
It'll take 'em over
a minute to get here.
He's the one to win
the race, right Virgil?
Oh, Virgil. I don't think
you're gonna win many races.
Well, just a
figure of speech.
Baby, come
to mama.
Come here, baby.
He likes to kiss me.
He's so cute. Virgil.
Are we?
Go back under there.
There you go. Don't toot.
What was that?
He has a little
gas problem.
Oh, okay.
I got him from
a turtle orphanage.
Really?
They have them?
Not enough.
That's my dream.
I want to have my own turtle orphanage.
And I want to dance
in a Broadway play.
That's nice.
What's your dream?
My dream is to marry
the man of my dreams.
Who is he?
I'll show you.
Wait 'till you see him.
Oh, that's
what that's for.
Yeah. DVDs.
At Superfly, our destinations
are your dream vacations.
So come fly
high with us.
Isn't he dreamy?
Yeah, he's cute.
Can you help
me land him?
Of course
you can land him.
Really?
I mean, you have
beauty and looks.
You can't lose.
Oh, thank you.
So, where are you dancing? I'd
love to come see you some time.
Oh, well, I'm kinda
between jobs right now.
Oh, me too.
Yeah, I got
fired for typos.
What are typos?
I have no idea.
I was working
at a talent agency,
you know, a receptionist
and secretarial stuff,
and I have to admit,
I'm not much of a typist.
Ah! Sh.
I love White-O.
Mr. Lean, there's something
wrong with the computer.
What, what, what?
Oh, my-
Get out! Now!
Well,
I've been working on a little
Busby Berkeley, Gene Kelley number.
Oh, here. Sorry about
that. Ta-ta-ra-ra.
Ta-ta-ra-ra.
Oh! Oh!
Ta-ra-ta.
Oh!
T a-ta-ra-ra.
Like this. Like that.
Whew!
I always do that. And
then, it's a big fat, oh!
Jeez. And then
it's a big Ta-ra!
Oh! Ow!
Wow!
Ow!
Oh!
That's it.
That's so good!
Wow! My God, you're
a really good dancer.
You came up with all
those moves yourself?
Uh-huh. Well,
I had inspirations.
You're really good.
Thank you. Want to give
it a try? Give it a try.
Oh, God, no. That's a hard act
to follow, I couldn't do that.
You can, I will talk you
through it. Okay? Yeah, do it.
Okay.
I'll start the
music again.
Okay. Hey.
Start with
the kicks.
Oh, shit. Well, sorry. Just, just, um.
Okay. And a one,
and a two and a three.
Flashdance! Flashdance! And perfect, oh!
Now one, two,
kick, kick those legs!
Kick it!
Oh my God.
Look at you.
You're so good.
Big finish!
Big finish?
Okay, big finish.
Big finish!
Jazz hands.
That's so good.
You are a natural.
"Natural", my ass.
I didn't train in
8 years for that.
A lot of good
it did me.
Because, how many jobs really
ask you to do the splits? Zippo.
Were you a dancer?
Gymnast. I tried out for
the National Park Olympics,
I placed 90th.
What happened?
Discovered boys. It was a lot more fun.
Because the guys really
do dig my backbends,
so maybe it wasn't
a total waste.
A waste? With your talent,
honey, you're gonna make us stars!
Oh my God.
At last!
The first thing we do
is build up your resume.
We do that by
getting your first gig.
Oh, look at this!
"Looking for dancers
at the Beaver Patch Lounge"
That sounds like
a nice family show.
Y eah, with animals.
Like Doctor Doolittle.
Yeah.
You're going for this
audition and you'll get it.
With me,
you can't lose.
You think?
You know what they
say, "Great minds do. "
That's right.
I'm so excited.
"Beaver Patch Lounge" that
sounds like a great place to work.
Alright.
While transporting an alleged
perpetrator in the car,
someone passed
some very nasty gas.
And you denied being the guilty
party and blamed the suspect,
Agent Campbell,
was it not in fact you,
who cut the cheese?
No.
Ha!
Damn!
This machine is good.
Alright, alright. It
- it's my turn now. It's my turn. Okay.
Last fall, someone
stole a donut,
off of my desk.
They took a bite,
and they put it back.
Was that in fact you,
Agent Gardenia?
No.
He, he.
Aw.
Okay, thi- this machine
has got to be wacko.
Let's do one more round,
I'll give you, uh, uh,
five to one
odds on this.
Hey.
I got a new job
for you guys.
What's up,
boss?
Rimoli blew his cover
as protected witness.
He's running a joint called
"The Beaver Patch Lounge. "
Until I can convince him to take
on a new identity and relocate,
I want you two to shadow him.
Make sure nobody wacks him.
Leave it to us, boss. No one will
get near him with us watching.
For the past
several months
somebody's been writing
unflattering things about me
in the
bathroom stalls.
Really?
Now, would
that be you?
Or you?
Me? No. I- I-
can assure you, sir,
that we- we would
never do such a thing.
We're professionals.
That's out of character.
I can assure you we would
never do such a thing.
These machines, look,
they're so unreliable
that- that
we're calibrating.
Just get out
of my sight
before I hook up your family
jewels to those things.
Damn. I don't
believe it.
That's a very tasty act
you got there, my dear.
Thank you.
What the hell are you
doing? I'm in an audition.
What am I doing?
Have you seen this ad?
Is the audition over?
No. Stay
upside down.
You interrupt my fun
to show me my ad?
You wrote this in the paper?
You used your real name.
No shit. The name Louie Rimoli used
to mean something in some places.
In powerful
organizations
it means "Kill with
extreme prejudice. "
That was a long time ago.
They've probably forgotten.
Yeah, yeah.
Louie,
Louie, these
people don't forget.
Oh, okay.
You're hired.
Send in the next girl.
So I can finish my lunch.
You know
I didn't join the Agency
to protect the
scum of the earth.
Reformed scum
of the earth.
That's what the Witness
Protection Program is all about.
Look over there.
Tell me
what's reformed.
We're here to
protect Louie Rimoli.
Can't judge a book by
it's cover, Agent Campbell.
This book should have been
judged a long time ago.
My mother was right.
I should have been
a bible salesman.
What?
Bibles.
No way.
Way.
Well, whatever floats
your boat, I guess.
I thought you
were a Buddhist.
What are we doing here, Swan?
We can get in big shit for this.
This is
The Cat's job.
Don't worry, Leo, You're gonna
give yourself a heart attack.
We won't
interfere, you know.
Just wanna put a face to
the reputation. That's all.
Nobody knows
what she looks like.
Ah, that's why we're here.
Okay? Now, keep your eyes peeled.
One of these women
coming in or going out
is the infamous Cat.
You're next, doll face.
Hi.
We're here
for the audition.
Aren't
we all.
It amazes me the lengths people
go to to get these auditions.
I know.
I like
your shorts.
Are those
real nylon?
Oh, excuse me, do you guys
know what the show's about?
About?
Yeah.
Yeah. The plot. The
driving force if you will.
Oh! Oh,
the driving force?
Yeah, it's about producing erections.
Oh.
It's a musical
about architecture.
That's unusual, right?
No, not really.
Producing. Cool!
Mmm.
So, uh, what've
you got for me?
Surprise
of a lifetime.
Uh-huh?
It's nice.
You got another
surprise for me?
You like this?
Oh!
Ah! Just give uncle
Louie a taste maybe, huh?
You know what? Time
is money. Come with me.
Come on, show
me what you got.
There's an idea.
The Godfather
says goodbye.
Can I help
you girls
Mr. Ravioli?
Uh, no, he's inside. I'm Manny,
the Talent Manager.
What's your act?
We're a new team.
Together?
Yeah.
Well that I
would like to see.
We're excited about
producing your erections.
Good one.
Are you gonna
watch us, too?
It's tempting.
Tempting,
but, uh, Louie prefers to
do his business one on one,
but I'm sure he wouldn't object to a
two on one, if you know what I mean.
Ha.
Hi, Mr. Ravioli. I'm Dee
and this is my partner Dawn.
We're here to audition for your show.
No, no! Don't say a
word. Don't say anything.
Just relax, sit there, have
a drink, smoke your cigar,
and enjoy the show.
Ready Freddie?
You're gonna
like this.
I think
he's interested.
I'm really good
at reading people.
Definitely.
You ready, Dee?
Yeah.
Six, seven, eight,
One, two, three, four.
Six, seven, eight.
Sorry.
Starfish!
Big finish!
Oh, big finish.
Big finish.
Jazz hands!
Mr. Ravioli.
Oh!
You killed him!
I killed him?
You threw a
stick at him.
Now he's never
gonna give us a job.
Oh my God,
you're right.
Oh, no.
I know we didn't kill' em. Maybe he's,
maybe he had a heart attack from
watching our crazy moves. It happens.
Give him the
hammock remover.
The hammock remover?
Oh!
Um, okay.
Oh, oh! His piece of
hair! Oh my God. oh!
Someone's here.
Hey.
I'll come back later.
Wow, some guys get to have all the fun.
What are we gonna do?
Just leave him
alone there.
Let's leave discreetly.
Oh my God!
Oh!
He's on fire!
Oh my God!
Oh!
Oh, no! What
have you done?
Oh God!
Hurry up!
Move it!
Oh my God.
Them?
No.
The Cat works alone. Besides,
those outfits are way too flashy.
A good assassin keeps
a very low profile, Leo.
You'd better
remember that.
Help! Help! Somebody!
Anybody! There's been a murder!
Murder! Help!
Oh, crap!
Then again.
Come here! There's been a
murder! Come on in! Come here!
Somebody help me!
My boss has been murdered!
Louie's been murdered.
I thought you said it wasn't them.
That's just what she wants you to think,
expecting to work alone,
she brings somebody along.
instead of blending in, she stands out.
She's brilliant!
The Godfather's
gonna want this Cat,
or kitties, if you will, to
take out Mr. Wong for sure.
I warned him, but
he wouldn't listen.
I should've guessed
they'd use The Cat.
So you think this was
the work of The Cat?
Oh yeah,
without a doubt.
They were
professionals.
They even invited me
in to watch them do it.
Oh my God, I could've been killed, too.
Now wait,
you said "they"?
Yeah, there
were two of them.
And we got them on
the surveillance tape.
Good. Good.
She's become brazen
and taken on a partner.
Oh! Oh!
All things considered,
I think the audition
went really well.
It did.
Didn't it?
Well, what are
we gonna do?
Oh!
Okay, we
leave town.
Let's get
out of here.
Pack whatever
you can,
let's get
out of here.
No, we're innocent.
Let's go on a vacation.
We're going to die.
Someone's
at the door.
Oh! Okay.
Oh my God!
Grab something hard.
We're not home
right now.
Leave a message
after the beep.
Here's the
beep. "Beep. "
Good one.
Hello. Yeah. Oh my God. It's Warren,
What?
You know how they killed Louie?
They burned his friggen head off.
What?
They burned his friggen head off!
Holy shit.
Hello,
we're friends, ladies, uh,
we're here to offer you a job.
Oh, job. I could
really use a job.
So could I.
May we come in?
Sure.
So we were
thinking, oh.
We work for
Mr. Capella, uh,
there's no
need for violence.
Oh!
I'll be the
judge of that.
Are you
guys agents?
No, no, no,
uh, we work for Mr.
Capella, I swear to God.
I think I've actually heard of him.
He runs a
big firm, right?
Yeah, that's it.
A big firm, probably
one of the biggest.
So the rumors are true,
you've taken on a new partner?
Wow, you know,
word travels fast.
I just booked
you in today.
I know.
We won't waste any of your time.
Let's get right to our point of view.
We're listening.
There's a guy. He lives in Niagara
Falls. His name is Hang Wong.
We want you
to take him out.
Take him out?
I don't even
know 'em.
We're willing to pay big bucks.
Say a quarter of a million dollars?
Wait a second.
You're want me to take
this guy out for $25,000?
Just take him out?
250,000 dollars.
Wow. Is that more?
I think so.
Half now and half when you're finished.
Why me?
Why you? 'Cause you're
the best, you know?
For that kind of money I'll take
him out, take him in or all out.
I know you
guys are great,
but it's not
that easy
this guy's
well protected.
Ah, doting mom. Don't
worry, I know the type.
Well, don't worry. I've taken out
tons and tons of guys. Lots of guys.
I've taken out doctors, lawyers, actors,
musicians,
and don't even get me started
with the high school boys.
Oh, woo wee!
High school? You were taking
out people in high school?
Oh yeah, only
the ones I liked.
Wait, have you
ever done any girls?
Once. I just wanted to
see what it felt like.
Me, too.
Really?
Wait, we don't have
to do this do we?
Listen, I don't care what you do to
the guy just get the job done, okay?
Well, when is
he expecting us?
He's not. But the
sooner the better, okay?
I think it fits
into our schedule.
Okay, we'll do it.
Okay, deal. Alright,
here's the, uh,
show of good faith.
Oh my God.
Pleasure doing
business with you.
It's American.
Woo! Woo!
We're going
to Niagara Falls!
Woo!
How'd it go?
Piece of cake.
Couldn't bring yourself to
turn down one last slice, huh?
What are you
talking about?
Oh, come on. It's
all over the street.
You agreed to take out
Mr. Wong in Niagara Falls.
You told me I'd
get the next one.
Wait,
someone hired The Cat
to hit Mr. Wong? Who?
Like you don't know.
The Godfather, for
a quarter of a million.
Well, well, well,
someone finally decided
to step on my paws.
Fatal mistake.
Are you saying someone
is pretending to be you?
Someone's about to
get scratched. Badly.
I'm coming with you.
Tell you what,
kitten, this time,
you get to
do the honors.
I'm in.
Meow.
Have you seen
these two women?
Yeah, I
remember 'em.
Two dumb blondes,
they came in
early this morning.
Amazing.
Their cover's flawless.
Yeah, they bought a red
Minicooper from the lot. Paid cash.
Of course, no credit
card, no paper trail.
Continue.
That's it. They left their car,
said they'd
pick it up,
when they returned from Niagara Falls,
said they were gonna take
out a Mr. Wong or something.
You'll never
see them again.
Hey, can I
keep their car?
No, I'm sorry,
it's evidence.
They'll probably use it to
run over innocent babies.
Can I get out
of the rain now?
Oh, please.
Okay.
Simply brilliant.
They knew we'd have the train
station and airport staked out.
But, we didn't.
Well, we should have.
Smart Mr. Wong.
Looks like they're celebrating another
notch in their kill pole, Campbell.
Run up all available agents.
We're goin to Niagara Falls.
Boss, we
need to talk.
So talk.
Uh,
We did like you said. We
delivered the money to The Cat.
And?
She's not working
alone anymore, boss,
She's hired on
another assassin.
They torched Guido at The
Beaver Patch pretty bad.
Burned his
whole head off.
They're bad
to the bone, boss.
Yeah, he's right,
if we didn't stand our ground
when delivering the money,
we wouldn't
be here now.
They were drooling
at the mouth.
They were crazed with blood lust
from the hit on Louie Rimoli.
They were gonna do some fancy
high moves of karate on us,
but we stared them
right down their eyes.
You would've
been proud of us.
Yeah, we looked death right
in the face and we laughed.
It's right. They knew
better than to mess with us,
finely tuned
killing machines.
What?
An apprentice?
Yeah.
But The Cat
knows better.
Any self-respecting assassin
works alone. This is not good.
No.
Nope.
She's got
some cojones.
You're
telling me.
Does she ever.
Yeah, she
looks good.
Boss, what
are cojones?
Yeah.
Nuts.
Teabags?
Oh, she's English.
That don't match here.
Nads.
Nothing.
She's got balls,
you idiots!
Oh!
Okay, yeah.
Now I get it.
So you're
telling me,
the number one assassin in
the whole wide world, The Cat,
is a dude?
Moron! Don't you know
what a metaphor is?
Yeah, of course.
Sort of a man trapped
in a woman's body?
No.
It's when a
chick's got a dink.
No, that's-
you're an idiot.
No, it's not.
Will you two pea
brains knock it off?
Boss, is this metaphor thing contagious?
Never mind,
you idiots.
This could be serious.
Ah, the book.
Ah, here it is.
Chapter 9,
Subsection 4.
"Under no circumstance may an assassin,
"engage an apprentice
for a contracted hit,
"without the express
written permission,
of the contractor
of said hit. "
Right. You know,
when they mention
the contractor,
they're talking
about you.
Don't you think I know that, Einstein!
There are
reasons for rules,
and the rules should not
be broken. This is not good.
No.
I'll have to send
someone to make sure
that things go
according to planned.
I want Wong wacked!
Oh, you know,
we would love to do it,
but, I get a bit of migraines
when I travel by air, boss.
It's bad. He does. And you know what?
I got a couple
of sick days coming.
Where the hell
did I find you two?!
You're turning a couple
of different shades of hue
you should calm down, you're
blood pressure is going.
I've got the solution.
Since you
two tough guys
just finished telling me how you
"Faced death" and stared down The Cat,
you can
have the job.
You won't get
a migraine driving.
And you, can consider
this trip to Niagara Falls
your sick days, huh?
Capische? Huh?
Boss, I don't
think it's a good idea
Enough talk!
I've spoken.
And unless you two
want something broken,
No, no, no. We get it,
boss. We get it, we get it.
Swan and I'll follow
'em to Niagara Falls
and make sure Wong is
wacked good and proper.
Yes.
So I guess
we'll just-
Whew. That's
disgusting!
Sorry.
You two keep
a low profile.
Remember Louie Rimoli was
wacked right under the nose
of the Witness
Protection Program.
The Feds are gonna have
their brightest and their best
all over The
Cat's scent.
Yes, Godfather.
Sir.
You freaking
imbeciles.
I can see
the headlines now.
Louie the Lip, executed
in broad daylight
under the Witness
Protection Program.
You know what kind of
putzes we're gonna look like?
What's a putz?
You're a putz, moron.
I think it's
redundant, sir.
Aren't they
mutually exclusive?
Enough!
Enough.
Let's go over
the facts.
Okay. At least we have
a lead on the killer now,
we can start to turn
around this bad publicity.
It's killers, sir.
What?
Killers.
Plural, sir.
It's true, sir.
Louie the Lip was indeed
taken out by the infamous Cat,
but it gets worse.
Now, not only does
she have a new MO
but she has a
new partner as well.
Well, I think The Cat's
made her first mistake.
I won't be long until
the kitten leaves the roost.
Because you can't have
two cats in the same nest.
You mean
litter, sir.
We're not after
a litterbug, you idiot.
Not garbage litter, we're
talking about cat litter.
Are you two
geniuses mocking me?
Because I'm getting
a very bad vibe here.
Now, maybe we're not on the same page.
Maybe I should put you
back on foot patrol,
because you seem kind
of fixated on garbage.
Well, there, there
is something else, sir.
Yeah, well?
Cat and her new partner
went to Niagara Falls
to do another hit.
Damn! We gotta stay on top of this.
Should we
go after them?
No. I want you to stay here
and bust people for littering.
Of course I want you
two knuckleheads to go!
You think I'll let them flatfoot from
Niagara Falls steal our lightening?
Thunder, sir.
First you mock me about
litter, now about lightening?
I should have
you two shot.
If you had us shot, it would
be very difficult for us to-
It's a figment of speech! You
moron! I'm not gonna shoot you.
Figure of speech, sir.
Get out!
Now! Just get The Cat
and if you fail I suggest
you stay in Niagara Falls.
Do you understand?
I can't believe
we bought this car!
I can't either.
Oh! Niagara Falls,
here we come!
Yeah!
Where is it?
I don't know.
Oh, we'll find it.
It can't
be too far.
I don't even see them,
are we on the right road?
There's only one road,
they've gotta be up there.
Alright.
Did you ever have
a dream, Leo?
Yeah, it involves you, cement
socks and a fishing trip.
What?
Well, I
have a dream.
Long time ago, when I clutched
my first protection money,
it was a nickle, for
not thumping on a kid.
You know how
old I was?
40?
No, 7.
47?
No, just 7.
Oh.
Yeah, I was a skinny
little thug back then.
I had a big dream. I
wanted to be a Don someday.
A Don?
Yeah. A Don.
A Don's got it all.
Respect, women, power, money.
But your last
name's Keith.
So?
So you'd be Don
Keith
Sounds like a donkey
with a lisp or something.
A friggen what?
Your enemies would be
shaking in their boots.
Here comes Don Keith.
Hee-haw! Hee-haw!
You'd be
laughed outta town!
Forget I
mentioned it.
No, that's classic.
Hee-haw! Hee-haw!
Hee-haw!
Alright! Shut up!
You're distracting me,
they're gonna see us.
I gotta pee again.
Me too.
Keep up and don't
let them see us.
Alright, Jeez.
Hey, are
we being followed?
No.
Okay.
What do you think
they'd do if they saw us?
Chop our heads off
and leave us
in the desert.
Why the desert?
I saw it on CSl.
Oh, I love
that show.
Yeah.
Did you see the one where
they put a victim in dog food?
What?
It's the best one.
I'd put
you in dog food.
What?
Aw, never mind.
Never mind.
Do you think they know
where they're goin'?
Probably making sure
they're not followed.
Pure genius.
Have you been
to Niagara Falls?
No, I saw a movie with
Marylin Monroe called Niagara.
You'd better pull
over at the next stop.
Why?
Because I gotta
take a leak.
Come on, I just pulled
over two hours ago.
Yeah, two hours ago,
when I had a large coffee.
Well, I'm
not stopping.
What am I
supposed to do?
Hold it. What
do you think?
Hold it? Yeah,
I understand "hold it"
but I think my bladder
might have another idea.
Ugh, you know, easy
with the bumps. Okay?
You're an adult,
control your bladder.
It's mind
over matter.
Well it ain't working.
Okay? It's not working.
Hey, Gardenia, why don't you
try controlling my bladder?
Huh? Excuse me?
Yeah, why don't you try
controlling my bladder?
Yes, have a nice, long
conversation with my full bladder.
You know, you could reason with it
and you can lay some guilt trips on it.
Hey, Gardenia!
Aren't you the Sigmund
Freud of bladders?
So that you would know,
you know, how I was feeling
so, like, if I were
dreaming about waterfalls,
and I'm feeling like I'm about
to explode or something like that,
Alright! Alright! I'll
pull over at the next stop.
Thank you.
Just promise me you won't
use that creepy voice.
The bladder voice?
Yes! Yes!
It scares me.
I'm so glad we met.
Me too.
I'm so glad
we have a job.
Now we're-
we're more genius.
Yeah, you're
no genius.
Just because you took the test
doesn't make you a genius, Leo.
I missed by one freaking question.
What frequency is a sperm whale's mating
call measured at? I mean, who knows that?
47 megahertz,
come on!
That was lucky.
So I'm a genius.
No, you're not a genius,
I'm an almost genius.
Whatever. Okay, Leo. Just
don't lose 'em, almost genius.
I'm not gonna lose em! Wait
a minute, where did they go?
I think we're
getting close.
You think you're
ready for Wong?
How can I not be when it feels so right!
We're here!
Oh, I can't wait
to get in there.
Hm.
Wait a second.
This looks familiar.
What?
Maybe we should
ask for some help.
Oh! Oh!
Oh! Good,
here we are.
Let's go.
Hi there.
Hi.
Are you ladies
staying here?
Yeah, we're not
checked in though.
No problem,
I'll have your bags,
and may I ask you what is on your back?
Oh, that's
Virgil.
He's a turtle.
Isn't he cute?
I'm sorry we actually have a, uh,
very strict no pet policy here.
Um.
What?
It's a
back pack.
Yeah, it's fake. He's a turtle backpack.
Okay! Right
this way.
Thank you.
I'll take these.
Oh, excuse me.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Hi.
We'd like to get two
rooms with one bed.
No, wait. One
room and two beds.
That's right.
A suite.
It's called
a suite, right?
Well, we're
pretty booked up.
Let's check
the computer.
Aw.
That was
two beds?
Oh, I'm sorry, it seems
we're out of suites.
We can just take whatever you
have then, that's okay. Thanks.
How about
a penthouse?
There you go.
Enjoy your stay.
Thank you.
Right this
way, ladies.
Excusie.
Here we
are, ladies.
If there's anything else
that I can do for you.
Please don't
hesitate to ask.
Actually, there's something
you could do for us.
Work on
your manners.
No, that's not
a good feeling.
Are you okay?
Uh, yeah,
I'm just um,
trying
Wow.
I wonder who's
staying there.
Wow. Probably
the Shrink of Araby.
Yeah, a Shrek.
Shrek.
Wow!
Wow. Look! They have trees in the room!
Oh my God!
I'm so excited!
Cool! Look at our room!
Oh! There's a pool
in the bedroom!
Oh, look
at the fireplace.
Wow, oh, my God!
Wow.
Oh, Jesus. Hey, that's our suitcase.
Oh my God, this
must be our room.
Oh my God!
I'm so excited!
Wait. This is going
to be so expensive.
No. Remember they couldn't find
us a suite so they gave us this.
Oh.
Oh, I gotta feed Virgil.
He must be starving.
Poor little boy.
Oh.
No pesticides.
Dee, come
look at this!
Come look at this.
What? Oh my God! Oh my God! We're here!
We're here!
Whoopie!
Oh, I can
see the sky!
I can see
the Big Dipper!
I can too!
Let's get you
ready, girlie.
Only one way to
accent the tushy.
Okay. Oh,
what are they?
Guess.
Uh, okay.
Miss Sixty.
No, Guess.
Oh, I like this.
Okay. Um,
Frankie B.
They're Guess.
Miss Sixty.
These are Guess.
Okay, okay, just
give me a minute.
Jay Ben.
Forget it. Hey,
check these babies out.
For your legs,
highest heels.
Oh, highest heels.
There are high, higher
and highest heels.
Try 'em on.
Huh? They're cute.
I, uh, I didn't know you
guys would be in here.
Uh, uh, the sandwiches are on the cart.
and, uh, I, uh,
the door was
Oh.
I think
this still fits you.
Yeah, let me try.
Arms up.
Okay.
I can do it.
I love this clean air.
So pure, untouched.
Do you know
where we look first?
I won't have to.
She'll come to me.
We locate
Mr. Wong and we wait.
When the hit goes down
we kill my impostor
and we carry out
the job ourselves.
Two dead, a lesson
taught, The Cat,
or I should say Kit?
is back on top.
You go get
us a room
while I make my presence
a little less known.
Why's everybody staring?
It's a good
thing, right?
Yeah.
You know what? I'll go find
Wong, I'll be right back.
Okay.
Excuse me, Miss.
I could use
some lady luck.
Would you mind throwing the dice for me?
Oh, sure.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
Excuse me.
Hey, where's the
information booth?
It's, uh, right
over there, Ma'am.
Oh, thanks.
Thank you.
No, no, no.
Yes? Can
I help you?
Oh, I hope so.
I'm trying to find Hang
Wong. I think he's French.
Brilliant. I would've
thought Italian.
Maybe.
Have you heard of him?
Hotel and casino.
They're doing a
Dancalicious here.
That's Dee's favorite show. I
must tell her, I'm so excited.
You're here to audition for Mr. Wong?
Oh, no, we're
here to take him out.
That'll be a date
he'll never forget.
I'm sure.
You can find him at
the casino restaurant.
It's called the Tramonto. He's
always there before the show starts.
The Tramonto.
Starts with a T.
I'll find it.
That's right.
Thanks so much.
Yeah? Sorry.
Dee.
Oh! Hi.
I found Wong.
He's at a restaurant in the hotel.
That was easy.
He owns the hotel.
Oh my God.
We need the money. No
gambling, no drinking.
Okay, okay.
Drinking's okay.
No gambling.
I don't know
how to gamble.
We'll keep
a low profile.
We're here for one thing
only, to take out Wong.
I'll be at Tramonto.
In his restaurant.
There's a big sign that says Tramonto
and it's the restaurant underneath it.
Okay, got it.
Have fun.
Okay.
Oh!
Money plays?
What?
Money plays, Ma'am.
Will you let
the money play?
Uh, I don't care.
No more bets.
Thirteen black. We have a
winner. Paying out 10, 000.
Would you like
to let it ride, Ma'am?
What?
Would you like to
let the money ride?
Let the money ride?
Um.
Let it ride!
Sure.
All right,
place your bets.
Tra, Tra, uh,
Tram, Tramonto.
Tramonto.
Hello.
Hello. Hm.
Are you
sure that's her?
Without a doubt.
I heard her partner tell a total
stranger what she was going to do.
Almost bragging.
cold fish.
She just walks
in the front door.
Either she's
incredibly brave,
or incredibly stupid.
Come on, I want
to watch her moves,
and when she
strikes, we pounce.
Hello.
Hi, I'm sorry, Miss Dee,
restaurant is closed for an hour.
There's a
private party.
Oh, for Mr. Wong?
Are you with
Mr. Wong's party?
I plan to be.
One moment.
Please wait here.
Thank you.
Mm.
Mr. Wong's assistant will
be joining us shortly.
Don't say anything
about his eye.
Oh. Okay.
What kind of candies
are these? They're good.
Candies?
Those are rocks from
the Japanese rock garden.
I hate sushi. Ugh.
Oh!
What is it?
I don't know. She hit
me with something hard.
We have a
new casino record!
This is the most fun I've
had with my clothes on!
What's your
bet, Ma'am?
You know, I think
I'll just let it ride!
Hello.
Are you introduced
to Mr. Wong?
Yes, um, you must
be Mr. Wong's pirate.
I mean,
ass- ociate.
Come with me.
Where are
you taking me?
To have
a little talk.
How could she know? I can
even think that she saw me.
Do you think
they're on to us?
No. Nobody's that good unless
they've the sixth sense of a-
Cat.
The lady's room?
You are not supposed to be in here.
Neither are you.
What?
Why are you here?
Well, I'm here to see,
um, I mean, I'm looking,
Mr. Wong is busy.
I just saw him sitting at a table,
I saw him with my own two eyes.
Who are you?
My name is Dee.
What's your name?
Wun Eye.
But my friends
call me Eye.
Ay, ay, ay.
Well, I hope you and,
I hope we can be friends.
You and, I.
Well, we can get
better acquainted.
Okay. Oh! Jeez, not
that kind of friends.
Gosh, you know, you should
treat me a lot better than that.
Okay, you're clean.
Oh, okay, well.
Once in the morning,
once at night.
Is Mr. Wong
expecting you?
No, it gonna be
a pleasant surprise.
Look, oh shoot,
I mean, listen,
Mr. Capellini hired me
to take Mr. Wong out.
That's a good one. Alright,
you can call me Eye.
You don't think I'm
good enough for him?
Sure. You just
have to wait in line.
Oh, so he's quite
the lady killer, huh?
Oh, yeah.
He's a killer.
Come on, let's go with
Mr. Wong. He'll like you.
You couldn't have
come at a better time.
She's good,
I'll give her that.
Sweet talk your way
in and then strike.
Excellent.
Too bad I
have to kill her.
I have a friend, she
might be looking for me.
She's a really cute blonde. Could
you keep and eye out for her?
Oops. Sorry. Um,
I forgot my purse
in the bathroom.
No. No. Stay
here. I'll get it.
Okay. Hey, do you
have a breath mint?
I have a little
bad breath.
Don't want to
meet him like that.
No.
But I have
a breath spray.
Oh, that's good,
thanks. Oh!
Stay right here.
Okay.
Sure.
Oh!
It's that one-eyed guy.
Let's get some practice.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Thanks, guys.
Wow!
As you are fully aware,
I do not work for Capella.
I work for no one.
Yeah. We know.
Mr. Capella just
wanted us to talk to you
one last time.
One last time?
Yeah.
Is that a
threat, Mr. Swan?
I don't know.
Hugo and I don't take kindly to threats.
Whew.
It's going down.
It's breath spray.
What?
Breath spray.
It's not a gun?
Ah. Okay. Okay.
Uh.
Holy mackerel, I thought I
lost a contact down there.
I got astigmatism I
can't drive without them.
I know.
So, sorry.
Now he knows it's not polite to
interrupt a woman in the bathroom.
Hm.
No obvious weapons.
She's better
than I thought.
My turn?
You'll
get your turn.
Hello.
Do you three
know each other?
Nope, never
seen her before.
Who is she?
Yeah. These are the
guys that hired me to-
to, uh, just show
you a good time.
Sorry.
Oh, so you must
be Mr. Wong.
Yes, I am
Hang Wong.
Ouch!
Please, sit
down and join us.
Now, this method
I prefer much more.
Friends in Hong Kong
give each other gifts.
You are learning.
Cheers.
Cheers. I'm glad we're
all here together.
Ah!
So, you are a
professional girl?
Oh, yeah, I'm
a professional.
What is your,
uh, your specialty?
If you don't
mind me asking.
My specialty?
Well, um,
I'm a really
good dancer,
and I wanna
dance on Broadway!
Oh! Haya, holy!
Is that so?
Well maybe you'll be interested
in my play Dancalicious.
Dancalicious?
You produce
I have my hands involved
in so many operations
as I'm sure Mr.
Swan could attest.
I, uh
My God!
Dancalicious!
You know,
I love that musical.
I know every word
and I know every lyric.
There's a six o'clock show tonight.
Perhaps you
could join me.
There is? How are we gonna get a seat?
I mean, that show must be sold
out for at least two years!
No problem, we'll just
kill two ticket holders.
Where did Eye
disappear to?
Well you're
right there.
Not me, Eye.
Well, I don't know
if it's proper English,
but, um, you're still
sitting right there.
Hugo. Find him.
Okay.
No, no, no.
Sit down.
Go.
You just told
me to go get him.
No, I said Hugo.
Right.
No, no, no. Sit!
Um, you just told me to go get him.
No, not
"You go", Hugo.
Do you want me to stay
or do you want me to go?
I want you to stay.
Eye! Are you here?
Who are you?
The last pretty
face you'll ever see.
Meow!
Agh!
Not bad.
A little messy.
Anyway, let's
go talk strategy.
We have a little time. Would
you like to, uh, ride my yacht?
Is that what
they're calling it now?
You can ride
my dinghy.
I have to go
to the bathroom.
I'm gonna freshen up.
Oh, I got blood
on my stole.
I have a feeling tonight
will be very memorable.
Oh! Sorry.
There you are.
I was wondering
who left that.
I think I'm a little
anxious about tonight.
Hot date?
Well, kinda.
Very profitable.
But I think Mr.
Wong is so sweet.
You know you should
be careful on dates.
A guy might already
belong to somebody else.
Somebody who
might get upset
if they feel their
territory is being invaded.
You think he might
have a girlfriend?
Something like that.
Or maybe
something worse.
Jeez, everybody's
speaking in widdles tonight.
Well, it's a good thing
I'm almost done with him.
It'll be through soon.
Maybe you're
through now.
She's the luckiest
bitch that ever lived.
God, I want her now.
Why didn't she kill 'em?
She had 'em right there.
She's toying with 'em, waiting
for the cruelest moment,
She's good,
man, really good.
Yeah, but she seemed so
sincere, so naive, back there.
You don't think maybe
we got the wrong girl?
Nah.
Come on, Kit. Let's kill the bitch.
Oh, hello.
Hello, shall we?
Sure.
Can we check on my friend in the casino?
Of course.
Shut up.
Whoa.
Blood.
Who's blood?
I don't know.
It's going into the
women's bathroom?
Hello?
Hey, you guys?
She's gosh darn
Charles Manson.
But she's not
after us, right?
The hell with it,
we're out of here.
Out of
the bathroom?
No, out of
the country!
Well, uh, but
we're we gonna go?
I don't know.
Korea or Iraq.
Cuba! Yeah, Castro
will take care of us.
Oh, there she is!
Dee, hi!
Oh, hi,
Wong, I'm Dawn.
Hello.
You'll never
believe this.
I won.
Won what?
About five pounds.
A million dollars
worth of chips.
My God,
that's great!
I know,
I'm so excited.
That's so cool!
Have fun.
Nice to meet you.
Bye.
Gosh, I hope
she's hungry.
Would she
like to join us?
Hello, Mr. Wong.
Meow. Hiss.
Shall we, uh,
visit my yacht?
Oh, sure.
I don't know how we're gonna
find them in this madhouse.
Don't worry, I've got men staked out
on every hot spot in the strip.
If they're here,
we'll find 'em.
You're damn right. Son, have
you seen these two blondes?
Yeah, they checked in
a couple of hours ago.
Really?
You sure?
Yeah, I wouldn't
forget them,
um, she
assaulted me.
You know,
it's nothing.
I just saw one of them, they're
in the hotel if you need them.
All units report to me right away.
A suspect has been
spotted in the hotel.
I repeat. A blonde
has been spotted.
Approach with
extreme caution.
Show me where.
Are they dangerous?
This looks
like trouble.
I gotta go
find Dee.
Well, she
was just here.
Uh, I think I saw the other
blonde with, uh, Mr. Wong.
Mr. Wong?
Yeah, he
owns the hotel.
Yes, I know
who he is. Where?
I think I saw
him go that way.
All units, we're heading
for the front of the casino.
There goes that job.
God! You're that guy in the commercial.
My friend
loves you!
I knew it.
Hey, you!
Stop! Police!
What? What?!
You're coming
with me. Come here.
Dawn really loves him, I
gotta get his autograph.
This way!
Show time.
Oh, excuse me.
Oh my God!
It's you.
Yeah.
You're the
love of my life.
That's very sweet-
Wait a second.
2001,
Dead and Deader.
Yes, I was
an extra.
Yeah, I looked for
you after my close up.
I couldn't find you.
You did?
Oh my God.
I'm trying to find my
friend. She's in trouble.
Did you see her?
The cops chased
her through that door.
She did? Okay.
Is there anything-?
Yeah, can you
hold this for me?
Yeah, sure.
there's a million dollars
in there, so be careful.
These shoes are really
uncomfortable to run in.
Thank you so
much. Thank you.
I love you.
Thank you.
Yeah. Uh,
what's your name?
Dee! I mean, Dawn.
I'm looking for Dee.
Bye!
An autograph,
please.
Uh, yeah. Right.
Come on. Go.
Oh!
Oh God!
Where does
this elevator go?
It only goes down.
We'll take the stairs.
Um, put that
in my room.
Ladies, I love you. I
love you. I love you.
No, don't go!
Why are the
police after you?
I don't know if they're the police.
Many people are trying to kill me.
They can be
killers in disguise.
If they're cops, they
can talk to my lawyer.
All units. I'm in pursuit of a
blonde and an unidentified male.
I want all air, land and
sea assets on standby.
Have my helicopter pick me
up at the west parking lot.
Come on.
Everyone! We're
in the wharf.
Open up!
Get me a helicopter. Right away!
Go! Go!
Oh, Jesus, Where are we going?
We're taking
a little trip.
I didn't pack.
You won't
need anything.
We going
to Tahiti?
Six feet under.
Australia? I've
never been there.
Shut up,
Shut up!
If you talk to me like
that I'm not going anywhere.
You won't have a choice in the matter.
Is that real?
What?
Yes! With real
bullets. Now move!
All right!
Okay. Action. Go.
Rolling?
It's been one year of planning
and it all comes down to this.
Okay, no smiling,
more serious. Okay?
I'm being serious.
I know, but
don't smile, eh.
It's been one
year of planning
and it all comes down to this moment.
I plan to
sneak over-
Help! Help!
I must find the yacht. My
friend's been kidnapped.
How do I get
to that yacht?
The fastest way is probably right there.
That boat there?
Yeah, we're
making web history-
Do you mind?
This is serious.
We're filming
Crime of Mr. Wong.
I will sneak over that yacht,
I'll climb aboard and blend in.
Oh, what-
what's she-
Hey, no!
She's kinda hot.
No, wait!
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
I'm sorry. I have
to save my friend.
I'll bring her
back, I promise!
Keep it rolling.
Trim down on the motor
or you'll drop the bow.
Come on.
Oh.
It's- Viagra!
What?
I know what that is.
You think you'll use that
artificial stuff on me,
you might as
well shoot me now.
I'm not gonna
ride your dinghy.
What?
It's Viagara.
It's my uncle's name.
It's named after him.
I'm not gonna ride your dinghy
when you made a promise to
You shut your mouth, I
promise I won't kill you.
Go, Go. Go.
Call my lawyer.
Where is
she going?
Back to the casino, we're
sending a helicopter.
Go! We're heading
down stream to the haven.
Move. Move. Move.
Hey! Dawn! Dee!
I mean, Dawn!
Let me take
the wheel.
Keys.
Easy Ma'am.
I just clean 'em.
The keys!
She's all yours.
Untie us.
Bon voyage!
There it is.
That's Wong's boat.
You're crazy.
Take a seat, sweetheart. It's show time!
Let's move it. Come
on, get the lead out.
There she is. She's got a goon with her.
That bitch! She thinks she's
gonna waste Wong before I do.
Should I
kill her first?
Let me do it. And you can
take your time with Wong.
You've already had your
kill today. I want to do it.
Who the
hell are they?
I don't know.
But it looks like
they're chasing,
that boat!
This is
Agent Gardenia.
I want all available
river patrol craft
to intercept Hang Wong's
speedboat called the Viagara.
We're headed downriver
from River Rock Casino.
Ha, ha. I love this. Like Nam. Woo-hoo!
What are you gonna
do when we catch them?
I don't know. Maybe you
should tell me what's going on.
I don't know. Some rich
guy gave us a bunch of money
to go to Niagara and take Mr. Wong out.
What? Take
Wong out?
Yeah, just take him
out to have a good time.
Whose following us?
They're
shooting at us.
Get down!
What the hell?
Hey, take
a position.
Oh! That's
my friend Dawn.
Hey, do you know how to swim?
I was in a
hot tub once.
Then maybe you'd better shut up!
Don't shoot Dawn!
Hey, it's
the blonde.
One of them. Wong must be on to
them. He's got the other blonde.
There should
be a flare gun.
Intercept
the speedboat
with two dark haired
women in it. They're armed.
I got it.
Okay.
Oh my God!
All units. All units. Gunfire. Gunfire.
They shot my
dream guy!
Buzz the one with a weapon. Come on!
Whoa!
Drop your weapons, ladies. We
have you covered. Give it up, now!
God I hope this works.
I don't know what the hell's
going on. Let's go to Wong's boat.
Can you say
something, please?
Patch me
into the P.A.
Stop that boat now. Lie it down.
Stop. Don't make us fire on you.
This is Agent
Gardenia, Wong.
Give it up. Drop your weapons
and prepare to be boarded.
And with what
am I charged?
Oh, where
do I start, Wong?
And be warned, that blonde that you're
holding might be the infamous Cat.
Yes, she says she was gonna take me out.
All units.
Take everybody
into custody,
we'll sort it out back at
the River Rock Casino. Out.
I can't wait to
see this report.
Let's head back
to the casino.
You know, I was just trying
to show you a good time.
I can't remember when I've had more fun.
I had some fun.
You have fun?
Look at the
camera, people.
Alright. Let's
go over this.
The two blondes were Kit and
Cat. So we can arrest them.
The dark haired girl shot the actor.
So we can
arrest her.
And Wong
kidnapped Cat.
Can we arrest
him for that?
I'm not sure.
Let's go
over it again.
So-
It's cold.
Dee! Oh my God,
you're okay.
God, you
really love me.
Mwah!
Oh, Dee. This is my dream man.
Ken.
Meet Dee.
I'm Ken. It's interesting
to meet you. Both.
I don't understand.
Don't you know who I am?
You can't arrest me. I'm Hang Wong.
Did he just say he was hung wrong?
Yeah, he's Wong. That's
why he's getting arrested.
So, you're a
Navy Seal, huh?
Uh, was.
Navy Seal doesn't
sound very scary.
Maybe Navy Shark or Navy
Lion. That's a good one.
I'll let
them know.
Thanks. But you're my seal, now.
When you save someone's life,
you're responsible for it.
It sounds
good to me.
Dawn tells me you're a talented dancer.
Well, I try.
A couple of our dancers
are unable to make it
for next week's
performance.
How would you like to be in the show?
Oh my God,
are you serious?
Oh my
- I'd love to. Only if Dawn can be in it too.
I think that can be arranged.
Oh, my God! We got a job!
Let's arrest
them all.
Alright everybody,
gather round, listen up.
Officers, I want you
to arrest these two women.
This is the infamous
Cat and her protegee.
Oh yeah, I've been
following you for six years.
They're wanted for a string of
murders all across this country.
No, you
idiot! It's me!
You've been waiting
six years to capture me.
I'm the one responsible for killing
over 30 people without a trace.
I'm the criminal
mastermind!
I did the Lone Shark
with a piano wire.
I snapped Louie
Rimoli's neck.
I
- I'm responsible for blowing up the governor's kitchen
with putting the explosives
in his pate that day.
Me! Me! Not
these two idiots.
I want my credit,
and I want it now!
She knows about the
piano wire and the pate.
Pate?
Arrest that woman!
Finally,
some respect.
Well,
I guess I'm
free to go?
Oh, wrong-o wungy.
You've been charged with
kidnapping this innocent young girl.
Cuff 'em!
What? Wait! Hey! You
can't do this to me.
These girls
are innocent.
Free to go, ladies.
Oh, shoot.
I knew it all along. They
were using them as decoys.
Anybody can
see that.
So what do
we do now?
Spend a
million dollars.
Oh my God!
Dream man.
Mmm.
Oh, Virgil.
Why were you taking
flying lessons, anyway?
Well, Dawn,
statistically,
um, flying is safer
than driving, I read it.
For you,
definitely.
Hi, guys.
Hey, you all
little chitlands. Hi!
Hi.
Welcome to
Dee and Dawn's
Famous
Turtle Sanctuary.
One day we'll have
a lot of these turtles.
We're gonna
rescue them,
and they'll be able to
run free and have fun.
Um, this
is Virgil.
It's Virgil. Yes.
He's my friend.
And Virgil does a lot
of tricks. Right, Dee?
Right. Yeah. Kind of. There you go.
Come on, Virgil.
Wow, look at him.
He likes you guys.
We only have one now, but we're
gonna have a lot pretty soon
Now, turtles
can teach us a lot.
We already know
how to do that.