Here she comes
Lies in her hair
With poison lips and deadly tongue
She's a highway to hell
And she knows it well
She's a high..
Sometimes when I'm immersed
in my thoughts I wonder
Highway to hell
About how you..
Have been made
To hell
For me
Baby, she's a
Your place is with the
stars, and I ponder
You've been brought down
to earth for us to be
Mrs. Makwana used to say that
the world is a pond..
...and our actions are
stones thrown into it.
If the actions are good,
you get a happy wave..
...but if they're bad
you get a storm.
I always had to listen to her,
because she wasn't just Mrs. Makwana..
...she was my mother! And when
she said these things..
...only one word rang in my head.
Bullshit!
Double bullshit with cherry on top!!
So guys the next time mummy says
something, listen to her..
...I mean it could save your life.
If I had understood this six months
ago, I would not be here.
But six months ago, I
was a different guy.
Six months back I was someone
else, I was somewhere else.
Six months back this was my world..
...where even Hindi is spoken
with a British accent.
Where an ordinary Jitendra Kumar
Makwana becomes Jimmy Cliff.
How may I help you?
The smartest executive
at Smartnet Call Centre
THAT'S ME! Six months ago I was
only interested in two things.
Hi Jimmy!
Women.. and work! And I was
pretty good at both.
Not only did I speak English,
I also taught it. Two jobs!
Life was pretty good. India
was rocking and so was I.
Good morning class.
Good morning sir.
How may I help you?
Superb! Okay.
DAY
EIGHT
PLANE
RAIN
DAY
These were the call centre
executives of the future.
Tomorrow's Jimmy Cliffs
and Janet Jacksons.
But today I wasn't assessing
their accents.
I was looking at their faces.
My last three girlfriends
were all from here.
Jimmy I love you.
Yummy yummy Jimmy!
Jimmy you're so hot!!
Normally, I get the bimbettes
and I'm okay with that.
But not any more.. I want a change.
I mean pizzas and burgers everyday
give you a bad stomach.
Now I wanted a new girlfriend.
Someone like I've never known.
Someone.. with a flavor so unique.
Separate from all others.
Just someone very special.
That was the first time
I saw lightning..
...tear the sky in broad daylight..
That was the first time I saw her..
She was beautiful..
If I were smart.. I should
have run away from her.
I ran but I ran towards her.
Hey come in. Come in, please.
Umbrella got blown away or
did u forget to bring it?
It was sunny when I left my house.
Are you new to Bombay?
It suddenly starts raining here,
without even a warning.
You also arrived without a warning.
The rain had no idea you
were stepping out.
My name is Jimmy.. Jimmy Cliff.
I teach here.
I know. I'm here to meet
with you. Pooja Singh
Nice to meet you Pooja. So tell
me.. what can I do for you?
Have you come for coaching?
Do you take private tuitions?
Private?
Yes, if someone is unable to come
here.. would you go over?
Any time you say. Whatever payment
you ask. Please Sir..
This was my last chance to say no.
But I'd never said no
to a beautiful girl.
You live here?
No, this is my office.
Office?
You have to teach my
boss English, not me.
I thought if you meet him, everything
can be discussed.
You know.. this is the biggest
problem with us men.
The moment we see a woman,
we think of..
So much sex, that we
forget the basics.
Of course, she never said
SHE needed a teacher.
And here I was, braking again,
and again.. shit!
And Sir.. whatever terms you have,
please tell them to me.
Okay. I'll come in on one condition.
What?
Stop this 'sir' thing. You're
making me feel like an old man.
Oh, is this the new professor?
Guruji.. I'm Misir.
Bhaiyyaji has been waiting for
you for such a long time.
Please do come in.. come
in maharaj. Bhaiyyaji...!
Bhaiyyaji
This is Mr. Jimmy, Jimmy Cliff.
Hundred percent English! Good morning.
Greetings! Please come..
Welcome.. Welcome!
No, please don't say Namaste.
From where I come, a teacher is
equal to God. Right Misir...?
Correct! It seems as though
the Lord Krishna himself..
...has come to Sudama's home.
Guruji, what will you have.. cold
drinks, hot drinks? - Hot drinks?
No, thank you.
This is your first visit. You must
have something. Hey, Pintu..
Yes Bhaiyyaji.
Pintu.. Please get some snacks
organized for Guruji.
Yes Bhaiyyaji..
No I.. I.. I just ate something
some time back.
I'm really not hungry. Thank you,
thank you for offering though.
See Misir, when he speaks, he
sounds just like George Bush.
George Bush?
George..
- Busss..
Pooja, you have done wonderfully
Guruji, just teach me English the way
you speak it. That's all I want!
L.. er.. whoaa.. er..
Guruji takes coaching
classes for English..
...and also works in a call centre.
Well time might be a problem.
Problem.. Problem is no problem.
See misir, his arrival has already
improved my English!
Guruji, from now on, you are
Dronacharya and I am Arjun.
Wherever you say, whenever
you say I will be present..
Unless I hunt the bird of the English
language I will not rest..
...and I will not leave your feet.
- Whoaa.. er..
Bhaiyyaji is requesting so nicely..
please agree Sir.
No.. no.. no.
- Bhaiyyaji.. snacks!
Forget the bloody snacks and
fall at Guruji's feet. Quick.
No.. no.. that's
really not necessary.
Hold his feet
- Here..
So you are agree Sir?
I am agree? I had to watch it.
I hope while I taught them English
I wouldn't forget what I know..
I am agree.
Man I was loving this whole
Indian traditional thing.
All these grown up men calling me..
Guruji
Thanks guys! And then
there was Pooja..
...now that was a dish
I was dying to taste!
So Guruji, decision's made.
After your morning classes finish,
will begin my tutoring.
Don't worry about the money.
Education costs nothing.
I mean, it's priceless.
In three months..
...I have a crucial meeting
with a foreign delegation.
Just make my English
good enough for it.
I'll try my best Bhaiyyaji.
But you will have to
promise me one thing.
From today onwards whatever you
say just try saying it in English
But that's the.. problem.
You just need to make an effort..
read the English newspaper,
...listen to the English
news bulletin..
I will be here tomorrow
onwards and hopefully..
...In three months, you will
be speaking English fluently.
Just like George Busss ..
A hundred cents..
Pooja was a naive.
And I was a player.
But I had decided that whether
Bhaiyyaji learns English or not,
Pooja will definitely learn
the language of my love!
Jack and Jill ..
Jack .. and Jill ..
Went up the hill ..
To fetch a pale of water.
Pooja was an entirely new experience
for me. - Listen..
She was a nice girl and
very traditional..
Really sweet
Thanks.
She gave me a card!
No one had given me a card
since the tenth grade.
But, it was also sweet.
I mean I thought it was really silly
Jack and Jill, went up the hill..
Stamp , Sweet , Sun.
- .. to fetch a pale of water
T.. for top
Twinkle twinkle..
...little star
How I wonder..
- what you are
Up above there in the sky..
- Huh...?
Huh...?
...and broke his crown, and
Jill came tumbling after
Jimmy Cliff..
Bhaiyyaji has a friend called
Mr. Snehal Desai..
...whose number he's misplaced.
Is it possible for you to
get it from your database?
Sure. Take it down.. 982172749,
Thanks
Don't hang up.. please
I'm at VT station
I'm coming..
Oh sorry.. what's this?
Money. It's come for the new office..
...that Bhaiyyaji is going to open.
Cash...?
Ya, it comes every month.
Bhaiyyaji has twenty
restaurants in UP.
All the revenue is collected
and sent here.
There is something called the bank...?
The bank is where it goes guruji!
Tomorrow morning, it
will go to the bank!
Er.. there's something
I want to tell you..
What?
Guruji, I am waiting.
Humty Dumty sat on a wall, Humty
Dumpty had a great fall,
Humty Dumty sat on a wall,
Bhaiyyaji was murdering the English
language everyday. - Humty Dumty..
And I.. I was slowly losing myself
in the magic of Pooja's eyes.
I was thinking of just one
girl for the entire day..
And suddenly I felt fear. Does
she even think about me?
Does she love me as
much as I love her?
I'm downstairs. I wanted
to tell you something..
I wanted to tell you that when
you laugh, your eyes twinkle..
I wanted to tell you that I
miss you in the evenings..
I don't know how to tell
you without saying it..
Saying that I'm falling in
love with you..l love you.
Bohemian heart
Wandering, lost bohemian heart
Hastening with all its zest
TI
Oh I'll conquer every star in the sky
Into one knot the sun and moon tie
And celebrate this everlasting high
I am but a rootless pilgrim
Oh I'll conquer every star in the sky
Into one knot the sun and moon tie
And celebrate this everlasting high
I am but a rootless pilgrim
Homeless and a vagabond
Roaming from one land to another
Somebody stop me please..
Enchanted by a spell so fond
I can't explain it any further
I'm desperate for release..
I'm lost in love
I'm sacrificed, I'm destroyed
I'm nothing but a moving void
I'm lost
I'm lost in love
Alone I stand, leaving all else behind
Word of honor now futile I find
I look at every star
straight in the eye
I've reached far beyond
every moonlit sky
To whom my story of woe do I tell
Rescue me from this heavenly hell
Somebody.. Anybody..
I'm lost in love
I'm sacrificed, I'm destroyed
I'm nothing but a moving void
I'm lost
I'm lost in love
The path told me that I'll get weary
Return halfway, you'll find it scary
Don't go any further
for a tempest slashes
Thunder cracks and lightning flashes
But I am the fanatic
that moved his lip
Keep me company on this lonesome trip
Say yes before my eye begins to drip
I'm lost in love
I'm sacrificed, I'm destroyed
I'm nothing but a moving void
I'm lost
I'm lost in love
Hastening with all my zest..
I'm sacrificed, I'm destroyed
I'm nothing but a moving void
TASHAN! Tashan the style..
...the good luck, the bloody formula.
Here, here, delegation come..
...talk, shake hands, smile,
ok tata bye bye..
...but Bhaiyyaji feels first
impression is the last impression.
Bhaiyyaji's Tashan was
an 'English' speech.
A speech like none other..
...with language that no one
had ever heard or even seen.
Happy to lots you being today..
...lots happy, because the person,
who till today your temple's
steps not climbing,
who till today in front of
you his head not bowing..
Deewar.
It's Bhaiyyaji's most favorite film!
Who till today in front of you
hands not outstretched..
...that person in front
of you standing is.
I knowing you lots happy
today, lots happy.
Because today I am losing,
but you knowing..
...while I standing here, that lady..
That lady whose forehead rubbing
your fourkhat stone,
So much so that the stone idiot
becoming thin person..
There's no English word
for 'Chaukhat' guruji..
In Hindi 'Chau' means 4,
so he made it 'Fourkhat'
I of you nothing ask, but asking today
...asking today.
My crime's punishment
my mother doesn't give.
I myself surrender.
You do what you do, you do.
God, just give me my mother back.
My mother.. return.
My mother, return me please ..
My mother return me please.
Please God.. please.
Bhaiyyaji's speech was like
a double edged sword.
The foreign delegation will think
that it is some Indian tradition..
...and definitely finalize his deal.
Ahaiyyaii!
In the middle of all this,
the love story of mine..
...that was blossoming was
completely bilingual.
Whether you say it in English
or in Hindi, it was great.
I was on top of the world!
How and why? how and why? How?
I said how come?? HOW???
How did you get the courage? I can
throw you on the streets if I like.
Who are you.. huh?
I gave you a job, gave you respect..
...and you.. you worthless
maidservant.
Remain within your limits.
If I throw you out, you will
end up at a dance bar..
...or brothel, like Umrao Jaan.
You don't mean that Bhaiyyaji.
Guruji please..this is an internal
matter that you know nothing of.
Kindly do not poke your nose
in matters that are private.
Thank you.
What he's thinking? Bhaiyyaji
villain, shouting ladies?
But not knowing truth.
Should I telling truth Pooja?
I made a mistake Bhaiyyaji,
please forgive me.
I would have shot Bhaiyyaji
if I had my way.
Listen, tomorrow we'll
go there together..
...and throw his useless
job in his face.
You needn't work there any more.
I cannot leave this job.
Why?
My life is very complicated.
Your life and my life are
not separate any more..
Listen, before I met you,
I only loved myself.
After I met you, I have
learnt true love.
Please forget me. You're
not my destiny.
My destiny is this job, this debt..
my father's debt to Bhaiyyaji.
I haven't even scattered
my father's ashes yet.
I thought that when I clear the debt..
...I'll go to Haridwar
and scatter them.
I've been working for
him since I was 16..
...and deducting a part
of my salary every month.
Bhaiyyaji says he himself
doesn't like it..
...but the interest alone has
become one and a half crores.
I asked him for the accounts
this morning.
And you saw how he shouted
at me like I was a beggar.
And then later he came
to me and said sorry.
He said he was feeling bad
about what happened.
He said he wants to help
me but was hesitating.
He said he'd forego the
entire debt and interest.
Marry me Pooja, he said.
There's never any debt between
husband and wife silly!
He said that there is an auspicious
time after Diwali.
Oh shut up Pooja.. Marriage?
We will return Bhaiyyaji's money.
How? Where will one and
a half crores come from?
By train..
Every month Bhaiyyaji's
money came into..
...one of Victoria Terminal's lockers.
The key to that locker was only with
Pooja but now Pooja, was with me.
After repaying Bhaiyyaji's
loan (with his own money)..
...we would run far away
into our little world.
That was the plan. I should've
been scared.. but I wasn't.
In our country, people don't
even get caught for murder.
We were only running away with
the money of a small baker.
It's more than the usual.
How much do you think it is?
I don't know. I've never seen
so much money before.
Okay. Remove Bhaiyyaji's amount
and keep it separate.
I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
Office. I need to submit
my leave application..
...and there's some
stuff in my locker.
You be careful and do
not open the door.
I'm taking my keys with me. Jesus!
When I reached the call centre my
supervisor pushed me into a briefing.
I was getting late but how could I
tell him that there's stolen money..
...lying in my house that
I need to run with.
I had to stay and there I met..
My name is A.C.P. K.S. Hooda,
Kuldeep Singh.
Village: Khadkhodha Jilla
Hissar, Haryana.
Anyway, jokes apart..it's not really
a joke. I'm just laughing!
Now, my name and address is
of no importance to you.
However, the names..
...and addresses that I'm going
to tell you are very important.
Yes, run the slide show. And the
names are Mr. Jagan Shah..
...Mr. Satish Jindal
and Mr. Snehal Desai.
Their extremely private and..
...sensitive information
has been leaked..
...from this call centre.
Where they stay, their
mobile numbers..
...land line numbers, office
addresses, etc, etc.
So many things are there.
I'm not saying that you all are
culprits but someone is there.
In the last two months these three..
...gentlemen have received
extortion threats..
...for large amounts that vary from
10 lakhs to 5 crore rupees.
And all these threats have
gone from one man..
...whose name is Lakhan Singh,
aka, Bhaiyyaji.
Bhaiyyaji is an upcoming
underworld king from UP.
Contract killing, murder, kidnapping..
...and land dealings are things
he can do with his eyes closed.
And he does them, every other day.
This Gabbar Singh has two henchmen.
One is Mr. Balakram Misir..
...and the other is Mr. Anand
Mohan Tiwari, aka Pintu.
Pooja, don't leave the
house at any cost.
Do you know that Bhaiyyaji is
one of UP's biggest dons?
Ms. Pooja's phone is with us Guruji.
It was Guruji. He's calling
Bhaiyyaji a don.
But isn't Bhaiyyaji a killer?
Moron! He's a smuggler.
Don't you remember? He
started with killing..
...and then moved on to smuggling.
Pooja.. Pooja.. Pooja where
are you? Pooja come on!
We've got to go. You don't know..
Bhaiyyaji is.. Pooja..
I flirt, I trick I cheat!
Hello Guruji! You've stolen my money?
Tsk.. tsk.. My God that's
funny!! Very funny!
I'm here to meet you. Pooja Singh..
Do you take private classes?
So are you agreeable sir?
I'm at VT station.
The information has been leaked
from this call centre.
My father's debt.. I vowed
to repay every penny..
I've never seen so much money before..
You've stolen my money?
I've destroyed you, haven't I?
Why did they steal the money?
How should I punish that
ungrateful Pooja?
And Guruji turned out to be a snake?
So many questions..my
brain is getting fried.
But Bhaiyyaji's feels that no matter
what kind of question it is..
The answer is available only in one
place - by the banks of the Ganges.
O Lord! In this unknown land of Ashok
Vatika I, Sita, am in solitude.
Surrounded by demons on every side,
I need thee and call upon thy name.
Hey.. At least call Ravan!
Where is Ravan?
Ravan...!!
Oh.. Ravan..
Bachchan, Bachchan Pande
He'll show you the night
in broad daylight
Bachchan, Bachchan Pande. BACHCHAN!
Ready!
Ha.. Ha.. Ha! Lankans! Look
outside of your houses.
These are the morons who
came to burn me down.
All the air is out eh? Flat tires!
Haa.. thu! (spits).
Now if anyone raises their head
in front of me, I will..
Parvatiya, what are you doing here?
She's Sita, you idiot! Parvati is
the heroine of the Shiv-Puran.
Shut up Jackass! If you know
so much about the story..
Why don't you become Ravan?
Come on?? Enact Ravan's
part.. come on???
Dhanpau
- Yup..
Note down this dimwit's
name and address.
Later tonight, we'll teach him
a lesson or two in private.
Don't you have any shame, acting
in front of these losers?
My mother told me to.
That mother of yours
will rest in peace..
...only after she makes you a heroine.
Please take your lines.
Oh yes, lines. Am saying them. Just
get up. Oh..er.. Rajdhoot..
Its Meghdhoot, MEGHdhoot.
Ya, whatever 'dhoot'..
stand there, quickly.
O Sita, stop being stubborn. Don't
waste your tender youth..
...on that worthless Ram. Marry me!
You'll live like a queen.
Which lamebrain has
written these lines?
You wrote these lines?
Er.. no. Not me.
- Who wrote these lines?
You wrote these lines?
No, the original was
written by Tulsidas.
I've just written the screenplay.
Tulsidas wrote these lines - Marry
me and you'll live like a queen..
Otherwise you'll never be able to..
...show your trashy face
to anyone again.
Am I Ravan or Mogambo??
But that line is Gabbar's.
You.. You writers are sons of.. your
mother should've been barren.
Who made you a writer?
Mr. Tiwari told me that these are..
...the kind of lines
that work these days.
Where is Tiwari? Tiwari.. Tiwari!
You gave the main role to the
biggest ruffian in town?
Please go, he's calling you.
Quickly, otherwise he'll come here
and beat the shit out of you.
Tiwari! Come here and let
me strangle you nicely.
Hello sir.
Yes, Mr. Tiwari, who am I?
Ravan, sir.
Hey Dhanpat, who am I in real life?
Bachchan Pande.
BACHCHAN PANDE!!
Sir, I am Bachchan Pande.
I have a little bit of respect around
here. Somebody bring a chair.
I am enacting Ravan's part.
So, if Ravan is not held in
high esteem by the people..
...how will they have respect for me!
Sir, you should play Ram's part.
Oh just give Bachchan Ram's part...!
The audience is waiting for you sir.
I request you to become Ram
and continue this Ramlila.
And let the show go on!
Sir, if you become Ram,
I will feel very humbled.
There is no greater honor for me than
to meet my end at your hands.
My my, I'm no Shah Rukh Khan. I'm
better off with Ravan's part.
I can't do all this. What say, writer?
I'm warning you right now,
Sita will go only with Ram.
Don't ask me to change
it at the nth hour.
Give you an inch, you
take a yard.. huh?
No, no. Of course it
can be changed sir.
Thank your stars that the phone rang.
Hello.. yes Chachi. Yes,
I'm leaving immediately.
Bachchan, Bachchan Pande
Power is the force that runs the world
The sword of power am I
Provoking me will be your mistake
Be destroyed in the blink of an eye
Bachchan, Bachchan Pande
He'll show you the night
In broad daylight
Bachchan, Bachchan Pande. BACHCHAN!
Good evening Chachi!
The recovery is done.
Bachchan, I told you to make
him understand gently.
He's the son of the freaking
Home Minister.
Chachi, that schmuck starting
shouting in English.
That's why Bachchan sir lost
it and taught him a lesson.
Bachchan Pandey, the people
you've messed with..
...this time are beyond my reach.
If they decide to return your
lesson with an encounter..
...I won't be able to
do anything Sushila.
You're going to organize an
encounter.. of my Bachchan?
Chachi had brought me
up like her own son.
She was having an affair
with Inspector Bajpai..
...thanks to which I had gotten
out of trouble a lot of the time.
Yes.. But today it seemed as though
fate was not on my side.
Yes Bhaiyyaji. You don't
need to worry at all.
This boy of mine is more
efficient than Thakur.
Yes.. Yes.. he is a recovery king.
He'll bring them back from hell
Bhaiyyaji! Yes, I'll send him.
Yes.. Yes.. okay. Just
let me hear his voice?
I'm going to send you to Bhaiyyaji.
Whoo.. hoo! Going to work
for Bhaiyyaji is like..
...like telling a boy
who plays cricket on..
...the streets to join
the world cup team.
What Amitab Bachchan is to
the people of Allahabad..
Bhaiyyaji is to us, natives of Kanpur.
They call him the pride of Kanpur.
They say Bhaiyyaji made his..
...beginnings right here
in Chaman Ganj.
Bhaiyyaji used to be
a rickshaw puller.
Not for anyone though. He was
the favorite of Vickram Tiger..
...who was a hi-fi goon of Kanpur.
Such people have more
enemies than friends.
The end is coming. The end is here.
The magic of your craft
makes judgment draw near
Go closer..
If towards the foe you will
just lift your gaze
Move.
If towards the foe you will
just lift your gaze
Into his eye look, leaving
him burnt ablaze
The magic of your craft
fills all with fear
Move out of the way.
When those thugs killed Vickram
Tiger and escaped - nobody knows.
Bhaiyyaji was very upset that in
spite of his desperate efforts..
...he was not able to
save Vickram Tiger.
Although, it did turn out
pretty well for him..
...as he got to keep the gold that
Vickram Tiger was carrying.
After that, Bhaiyyaji began to rise
in a way that was unstoppable.
He is where he is only because
of his own strength and acumen.
I've also heard that Bhaiyyaji has
an enormous hideout in Bombay.
A city of gold.
Light is chic and night is trend
We are made of a unique blend
Every state is ecstasy,
not just a fantasy
Grey is the life that we have led,
our fury can burn the sun dead
Shameful and shameless have we been
Innocence untouched and still keen
Alexander's fatal arrow have we evaded
The oceans have we consumed
and mutated
Alexander's fatal arrow have we evaded
The oceans have we consumed
and mutated
We don't await the fortunes
of destiny's sanction
We are of the extraordinary fashion
Oh yes, our zest brings life to LIFE
Pintu.. Bhaiyyaji's here
Bhaiyyaji, he has a very
large business empire.
Mr. Snehal Rasik Bhai Desai
- Owns a factory.
We tried to make him
understand that for..
...the smooth functioning
of the factory..
...he must give us a
generous donation.
Otherwise, the factory might get
burnt down.. and turn to ashes.
Pintu.
You'll die the death of a
dog..Do you know who I am?
I know who you are.
The question is do you know who I am?
I am the Sachin Tendulkar and
the Brian Lara - Combined!
Aaaaaaaaaa.. ( shouting with pain )
My pleasure.
Hey.. Hey Ali! Get rid of him
and clean this place up.
Ali won't be able to do much..
Everyone come in.
This is your job for today.
Bhaiyyaji was my hero
- international, multinational,
every national!
It didn't get bigger than him.
Greetings Bhaiyyaji
You are Bajpai's son?
I am Bajpai's son. This is Bachchan.
Misir..
Bajpai says you are can
find anything? - Yes.
Finding from hell also?
Yes.. yes..
If that's the case, I welcome you!
Er.. Bhaiyyaji, my English
is not very strong but..
But it is a privilege to meet you.
I don't want to say too
much, except that..
...now you don't need to
worry about anything.
I will throw that English professor
at your feet in the next two days.
If I can't, my name will no
longer be Bachchan Pande.
You don't need to find Guruji.
Guruji has come by himself!
This is Guruji. Surrendered
himself yesterday.
He says that he does not
have anything with him..
...Pooja took all the
money and ran away.
Oww.. Jesus...!
Just saying hello in
Kanpuriya tradition.
Look, I don't have the money.
Beating me up is not
going to produce it.
I haven't hit you for the money.
I hit you for your cheap character.
How did you even think
of cheating Bhaiyyaji?
If you have revere for
Bhaiyyaji so much, ..
...why don't you go and catch Pooja?
Which brings me to my next question.
Where is the girl?
How in heaven's name will I know..
...If I knew where she is,
wouldn't I be with her?
Why_would I be sitting here
getting beaten up by you?
So the girl has all the money?
Yes, Einstein.
If I don't understand something, I
consider it an insult. Understood?
Bhaiyyaji, I can tell from his
eyes that he's not lying.
I can spot a liar anywhere.
Hmmm.. so you tell me,
what should we do now?
Bhaiyyaji, when a person runs away,
he goes to two kinds of places.
He either goes to a place where
he has a support system or..
...he goes to a place where
he's always wanted to go.
For example..Haridwar
Haridwar?
Yes! She's gone to immerse her
father's ashes in Haridwar.
Oww.. Jesus man! Now why'd you hit me?
You should have told us
this earlier, bonehead.
Do you think this is
some kind of joke?
Bachchan, have you used this before?
It's an 8mm German pistol.
Keep it. Take Guruji and find Pooja.
Bring Pooja, Guruji and, most
important - the money back to me.
But if anybody is naughty,
kill them and throw their..
...bodies into the nearest river or
pond. Guruji, do you understand?
Yes Bhaiyyaji, I do.
Huh?.. What? What? What?
Yes, Bhaiyyaji. I understand
that if I make any mistake..
English, please..
Okay, I understand that
if anything goes wrong..
Er.. I understand that, and I..
And I won't do anything
naughty. I promise.
How he speaks Bachchan..like
music to my ears.
The man is a snake but when
he speaks English..
Fully George Bush! Complete ..
Tsk.. tsk.. Prince Charlie!
Prince Charlie..Charlie
Charlie!!Charlie.. ha ha!
Ha.. ha.. ha...!
And then there's this
'Indian foreigner'.
Does the bastard even
think in English?
So this was my destiny.
Roam around with a wild gorilla
and look for Pooja. Pooja..
Here I was with my head on the
block and wherever she is..
...she must be having
a ball. Bloody bitch!
Intoxicating eyes
Deceiving with sublime lies
Tints grey on clear blue skies
I'm drugged by these eyes
My heart is but a cluster of ties
Be mine in vain it cries
TI
I flirt, I trick, I cheat
Stealing your soul is no great feat
I tease, I play, I defeat
You'll never find me,
I vanish in a beat
I flirt, I trick, I cheat
Stealing your soul is no great feat
I tease, I play, I defeat
You'll never find me,
I vanish in a beat
I am the morning dew
I combine day with night's hue
I am your purest view
How will you escape my mesmeric charm
Don't! Don't you dare..
try to give me that stare
Don't look at me like that lover!
Don't! Don't you dare..
try to give me that stare
Don't look at me like that, boy!
Don't! Don't you dare..
try to give me that stare
Don't look at me like that lover!
Don't! Don't you dare..
try to give me that stare
Don't look at me like that, boy!
I flirt, I trick, I cheat
Stealing your soul is no great feat
I am the night sinking
all the stars in sight
Every turn I bloom,
at each sigh of gloom
I am that spell which
your willpower dispel
I will coax you without
you smelling a hoax
I am the emotion of a broken heart
The thought that provokes a poet's art
I am the light, I am delight
How will you escape my mesmeric charm
Don't! Don't you dare..
try to give me that stare
Don't look at me like that lover!
Don't! Don't you dare..
try to give me that stare
Don't look at me like that boy!
Don't! Don't you dare..
try to give me that stare
Don't look at me like that lover!
Don't! Don't you dare..
try to give me that stare
Don't look at me like that boy!
Oh.. I flirt, I trick and I cheat
intoxicating eyes
Deceiving with sublime lies
Tints grey on clear blue skies
I'm drugged by these eyes
My heart is but a cluster of ties
Be mine in vain it cries
I am the secret that seals your lips
The sand that from your hand slips
I am the drop that thunders on you
The unquenchable thirst
you will never adieu
I am the strategy behind all cons
The unsolved web of numerous pawns
I am the light, I am delight
How will you escape my mesmeric charm
Don't! Don't you dare..
try to give me that stare
Don't look at me like that lover!
Don't! Don't you dare..
try to give me that stare
Don't look at me like that, boy!
I flirt, I trick, I cheat
Stealing your soul is no great feat
I tease, I play, I defeat
You'll never find me,
I vanish in a beat
I am the morning dew
I combine day with night's hue
I am your purest view
How will you escape my mesmeric charm
Don't! Don't you dare..
try to give me that stare
Don't look at me like that lover!
Don't! Don't you dare..
try to give me that stare
Don't look at me like that, boy!
Don't! Don't you dare..
try to give me that stare
Don't look at me like that lover!
Don't! Don't you dare..
try to give me that stare
Don't look at me like that, boy!
This is the fastest way
to catch missing people.
Here.. this.. this. In this country..
...people will even sell their
mother for ten lakhs.
That's bullshit.
Especially people like you..
By the way, what did
you think of Pooja?
Would you steal 25 crores for her?
Okay.. Will you kill her if
Bhaiyyaji tells you to?
He didn't say anything like that.
But if he asked me to kill you I
wouldn't hesitate for a second.
I'll park two bullets straight
inside your brain
What? You'll kill me? Just like that??
This is what I came to Mumbai
for.. to be a shooter.
Bang bang!! I'll bury you right
here if you don't shut up now.
Psycho!
Now what happened?
It's none of your business..
I'm feeling hot.
Just sit here quietly.
Have you seen her?
Have you seen her
- No I'm not.
Hey?!.. why?
You're in India, listen
to Indian music.
Man! .. dude, music has no language.
If Bachchan Pande says there is a
language, then there is a language.
Is that understood? Now,
shut your gob..
...and sit there before I change
the shape of your face.
Watch it!
The story thus far has been told
by this 'English' dimwit..
But what is going to happen now?
.. that he doesn't know.
Neither does his mother,
nor does anyone's mother.
Got a light ? Huh?.. Match box?
What?
At least give me a cigarette..
Bitch!
Oh no.. you're not happy to
see me? Why.. naughty boy!
I would've been a happy
man if you had died.
Besides, what the hell were
you doing in our car?
Thanks to your advertisements..
...there was no place safer
than your car for me.
So..
Who's the hunk?
Hunk?
He's quite a stud! You're
not jealous, are you?
Hi hunk! The cold doesn't bother you?
Here.. happy? Now tell me
where is Bhaiyyaji's money?
You think I have 25 crores
hidden in here?
Don't even try to be over-smart
with me. Just answer my question.
Are you also from Kanpur?
Yes.. is there a problem? Look,
I'm not like this moron.
I don't talk much but when I do..
...Ram & Laxman here talk with me..
Whether you're a man or a woman..
...there's only one treatment
for traitors.
So tell me straight..
...or I'll whack you so hard you'll
forget your mother and father
Rajasthanwhat?
Speak loudly.
Money. Rajasthan.
- Lets go..
We can't go like this?
- Why?
We'll reach heaven before
we get to Rajasthan.
Have you heard of pneumonia?
Nothing will happen to you.
Nothing will happen
to you Bheem Singh!
But we don't bathe in
the Ganges everyday.
Lets go after our clothes dry.
Alright. I'll be back in 5 minutes.
We are those that sleep
in peace.. lala..
Excuse me.. can you dry this, please..
I'm not your grandfather's
slave - Please ..
You've destroyed this entire country
with your 'please, please'. Give..
And this.. - Yuck! ..what is this?
- Bra..
I know that. I'm not
going to touch it.
You don't dry your vest?
Yes I do but I'm not going
to.. this.. good Lord!
This is like a vest for us.
There's hardly anything
to be coy about.
When there are posters with women in
tiny bikinis displayed all over..
...I'm sure you have a good look.
I'm not that type, understand?
Ah.. so what type are you?
The other type?
No, not the other type either.
Put it here.
These people wear all kinds of
weird things. Hey! ..dry this.
Haha! Why? ls there an electric
current going through?
Ayee.. quiet. Shut up!
I won't tolerate all this chatter,
you understand?
I'll give you one tight whack and
then everything will be understood.
Now dry your clothes quickly and come.
I'm waiting there.. Move it.
Haha! Foool...!!!
Jimmy..
What?
Can we start again please?
Huh?
Take me.. with you.
There's enough for the two of us.
Remember what you said..in
this country..
...If you have the money and a little
smartness, you'll never get caught.
I've got the money and
you've got the brain.
Just you, me and 25 crores!
How many times do you think..
...you can make a fool out of me
with the same bloody lollypop?
You'll have to be alive
to become a fool..
Huh?
What do you think?
After Bhaiyyaji gets his money back..
...he's going to give us character
certificates and bid us farewell?
Do you even know his name?
Lakhan Singh Ballebaaz, aka Bhaiyyaji.
He would get his picture
printed on the currency..
...notes instead of Gandhi-ji,
if he could.
He's a terror.
Cricket bats, hockey sticks,
football shoes and
even tennis rackets are his murder
weapons. Do you know why?
'Coz killing people is
his favorite sport!
The entire river's dried up
but your clothes haven't?
As if its Draupadi's saree
that just won't dry.
Useless freaks..their English
clothes don't seem to dry only.
And now I've got to piss..
Where can I go?
If anyone can save us from Bhaiyyaji,
its him. Captain wallop.
Him?.. Mr. By-the-banks-of-the-Ganges?
If he's on our side,
we might just escape.
But why would he be on our side?
He knows about us. Same lollypop..
and the same trick.
But the fool's different.
Wow! You've actually become smart
after being made a fool!
I was good for you. But now what?
Now I am going to rape you
Nice
One sec let me .. umm ..er ..
Help! How dare you try to
de-flower me? Bachchan!
Help!! Please leave
me for God's sake..
Why would I leave such a good
thing for God. Haha!!
You're overacting
You are over critical
Please.. help!!
Shameless woman, I'll teach
such a lesson that..
No matter how shameless a woman is,
a lady's honor is still honor.
This is none of your
business Bachchan.
And she does not have any honor
whatsoever, she's a bloody bitch.
You know the mess I'm in because
of her...? You know...!
You're not an angel either..
You can have her too. She's quite
hot. Hey.. I don't mind.
What happened? Broke a tooth?
Didn't even shake, loser.
I hate you Pooja.. bitch!
Are your clothes dry?
Why don't you check?
You see this woman. She's
a not nice girl..
Very bad girl, I'm telling you
Down, down..
What happened?
- Police.
How do you know? That man had
come to the call centre.
He knows Bhaiyyaji's entire history
Where's my phone gone?
Shhhhh.. Shhhh..
Speaking
Good evening Bhaiyyaji
Have you found that unfaithful bitch?
(Aside) Now if I knew
this much English,
I would've been in the IPS or IAS.
(Into phone) Umm.. Bhaiyyaji,
can you please speak louder?
Have you found the bastard
lady, Pooja Singh?
Have you found Pooja?
That traitor woman?
I have found her.
Yes, yes Bhaiyyaji.
Going to collect the money which
she's hidden in Rajasthan.
But there's a small problem.
The master-ji seems to have
recognized a police officer here.
His name is ACP Hooda.
He's dangerous..has been on
my back for some time now.
Bhaiyyaji if you like, I
could get rid of him..
Tsk.. tsk.. Stay away from
him Bachchan. It's risky.
Don't get seen by him, okay?
Okay. I want_ed t9 ask you _one__
question Bhalyyajl.. er..Bhalyyajl
Haha! Bachchan, are you
thinking I am one..
...of the contestants of Who
wants to be a millionaire???
What are you meant for? Huh?
Eating cherry pie? Don't ask
questions, answer first.
Baby, you carry on
Haha! He's saying that you are very..
Shut up schmuck.
I don't need to understand the
language to know what he just said.
Don't teach me, useless fool.
He has a habit of interrupting people.
You keep quiet, slut. Hey Bachchan,
keep her away from me or..
Or what Jeetuuuuu???
Bachchan will break your arm and..
...throw it into the gutter
Jeetenderrrrrr!
Hey.. hey.. stop. Stop it ..
...stop this cat & dog fight
or I give you both one each..
Aaah.. I hate you
- Piss off.
Hey lady..why are you
cutting your jeans?
Hey..why are you cutting your jeans??
Tashan
Now don't think I was staring
Why? Am I that bad?
Any clues?
- No Sir.
Hooda.. here? How??
Who Buddha?
Not Buddha, ACP Hooda. Come on, run.
I want those three. These
are useless, let them go.
Okay, move it..Come on hurry up!
Move it.. move it..
- Run.. run..
Namastey. Namastey..Hi Namastey.
Whoa..
- Oooo .. Jesus
Check every bed, bag and box.
Tapad, check those black boxes.
Can't trust these rascals
for a second.
All the equipment should be here.
Why it hasn't reached man?
Come on just send the extras.
What program are you making?
Sir, shooting sir.. of an English
film. Hollywood sir, Hollywood.
Hey.. prodigy of Spielberg.
Have you joined Hollywood?
Speak in a language that
you know. Speak in Hindi.
Sir, I have all permissions with me.
You can check. They're
very famous people.
Please don't kill me , please.
I am a friend of India.
I'm making a movie.
Its.. its called Holy Widows.
It's a good movie, it's
not like the other crap.
It's definitely going to be
nominated for the Oscars.
He says that he's making a
film called Holy Widows..
...and is a friend of India.
Tell him we're going
to be in his film.
We are going to be in your movie.
Doing what?
What will we do?
Sing a song, what else?
Singing a song
There is no song in my film
He says there's no song in his film.
Now there is!
Dude this is India. There
is song for everything.
TI
When I see a white white face
My heart begins to race
I'm hitting on you in any case!
When I see a white white face
My heart begins to race
I'm hitting on you in any case!
When I see a white white face
My heart begins to race
I'm hitting on you in any case!
Oh very, Oh very
Oh very happy in my heart
It dances away
Very happy in my heart
It dances
It dances in a sway
Oh happy in my heart
It dances away
Oh can't stop my feet..
Can't stop my feet, oh
this tormenting beat
I just can't stop my feet,
it is like torture sweet
Standing steadfast in
the scorching heat
Locked is our gaze as we meet
Don't hide your feelings
Tell me of these sweet tidings
Oh very, Oh very
Oh very happy in my heart
It dances away
Very happy in my heart
It dances
It dances in a sway
Oh happy in my heart
It dances away
Oh as pink as a rose, your cheek glows
As blue as the sky,
your eyes make me fly
A face as pure as the untouched moon
And hair as black as a cloud in June
I can't hide it any further, my
heart beats for you with fervor
Oh my heart beats for you
Louder every time you're in view
For the premier of your
heart, one chance
I'll buy out the theatre
by booking advance
Yes, for the premier of my heart
Of the booking, many want part!
Oh very, Oh very
Oh very happy in my heart,
it dances away
Very happy in my heart, it dances away
Oh it dances
It dances
It dances in a sway
Oh happy in my heart, it dances away
When I see a white white face
My heart begins to race
I'm hitting on you in any case!
When I see a white white face..
Ya.. when I see a white white face
My heart begins to race
I'm hitting on you in any case!
Oh very, Oh very
Oh very happy in my heart
It dances away
It dances
It dances in a sway
Oh happy in my heart, it dances away
Oh very happy in my heart,
it dances in a sway
Oh very, very happy in my
heart, it dances away
Oh very happy in my heart,
it dances in a sway
Oh very, very happy in my
heart, it dances away
Hey Olga.. if you are ever in
Bombay .. What is your problem?
Jimmy, Jimmy, Jimmy!
Listen.. thanks so much.
I really appreciate it.
Ya sure, no problem
Mr. Bachchan, Mr. Bachchan ..
thank you very much..
...I .. I .. I hear
you are a huge star
I told him you're Amitabh Bachchan.
Listen, if you're ever in L.A,
please give me a call.
We'll do lunch okay. Thanks,
thanks really.
Hey, hey Harvey! Ya .. Guess what man?
We got a song. For Holy Widows.
Stars this huge Indian star.
You are going to love it.
I had never seen a girl
so close.. felt strange.
People look so innocent when they're
asleep.. just like children.
She looked like she
couldn't hurt a fly..
I don't know why I wished that she'd..
...keep sleeping on my
shoulder.. forever
And I'd keep sitting here forever.
Good .. good.
You didn't sleep?
If I had slept, you would've
run away again!
No, if I run now, I'll run with you.
I get a really good sleep
on your shoulder!
Pooja, I think you've messed up your
life after falling into bad company.
Sometimes, what's right for you
can be wrong for someone else.
Now Bhaiyyaji may be a big don..
...but when he takes
Pooja Singh's name..
...he'll take it with a little respect.
Are you married?
Will you marry me? I'm serious..
this is not a joke.
Will you elope with me?
Pooja has a rare quality and it's a
quality in very successful people.
She never wastes any time.
Bachchan I'm not scared of
Bhaiyyaji.. if you are with me.
But are you with me??
Twenty-five crores is a lot of money.
And I'm the bonus!
The further you go away from
me, the closer I'll come.
Night eyes.. your black night eyes.
Pooja, can you hear
that groaning sound?
Night eyes, night eyes,
your black night eyes.
Your eyes, your eyes, biting,
biting black eyes.
Night eyes, night eyes,
your black night eyes.
Guruji, sing with me!
Your eyes, your eyes, biting,
biting black eyes!
Hello my dear Pooja! Welcome, welcome!
First you did Guruji, and now
you're doing Bachchan also?
Good afternoon Bhaiyyaji.
God bless you son. About Pooja
one thing is fantastic.
Money stealing by fraud..
...and then hiding it in beautiful
places. Pooja money where is?
Hey Misir, I'll bet you 500?
For what?
After getting the money..
...Bhaiyyaji will first blow Ms.
Pooja's brain out, and then Gurujis.
You idiot, you've spent so much time
with Bhaiyyaji.. He's going first.
So make it a 1000 then?
You enjoy losing, don't you?!
We'll see..
It looks too small
It's one crore
You stole twenty-five,
and are returning one?
I have learnt a couple things
while working with you.
The money is in different places.
Very good! How many places?
Seven
Why only seven?
Tashan
Very slick Pooja! I
am a fan of Tashan.
Now listen to my Tashan.
I want every dime of mine
back to me in seven days.
Seven days is not enough.
Pooja, you bring me my money, or you
won't live to see another day.
The foreign delegation is
coming in seven days.
The money should be with me by then.
You go with them, and after
you've got all the money..
...finish both of them.
You will become a part
of Bhaiyyaji Eleven!
I'll get a suit made for you.
But, if anything goes wrong, I'll
be playing cricket with your balls.
What happened? Not happy?
Bhaiyyaji, there couldn't
be a happier moment for me.
Please smile then.
Officers.. surround them.
Seal the area.
Cover them completely.
Get down.
The bloody bullets always finish
just when you need them.
Don't worry Bachchan.
STOP!
Bhaiyyaji, I know you're
out of bullets.
Surrender now if you know
what's good for you.
Bastard
Go Bachchan.
Bachchan Bachchan Pande
He'll show you the night
in broad daylight
Bachchan, Bachchan Pande
Pooja, here.
I am the spectrum that leaves you dumb
Pay heed to the words
of Bachchan Pande
I am the victor whose words are numb
A, B,C,D.. I am an atom bomb
From the banks of the
Ganges extends my fame
Bachchan Pande is my name
I row my boat that can
any current tame
And for all my credits
I solely take blame
Should I kill you
It'd be nicer if you don't.
Alright, something you
can remember me for!
Sucker..taking the easy way out again.
You're the one who said you're
safest next to the enemy.
That day I ran straight to Hooda.
The police were looking
for me because..
...I had leaked the information
from the call centre.
But I wasn't as worried about the
police as I was about Bhaiyyaji.
Hooda told me that the
only way out of..
...the mess was to help the
police to catch Bhaiyyaji,
by surrendering myself to him.
He said it was my only hope
and I knew he was right.
By the way, why were your
men shooting at me?
That's 'coz nobody else knows
you're working for the police.
Oh, like top secret stuff
eh? Really cool!
So nobody else knows?
Tell me, does Bhaiyyaji have any
idea that you work for us?
After I saw you in Ladakh, I
created such a big noise..
...that it seemed as though you were
chasing me, and not Bhaiyyaji!
The world to me is a
blind and dark place
I'm like the wind throwing
smoke in your face
No deed do I do that makes
me fall from grace
If you blabber too much, you'll
be struck by my mace
The soil by the Ganges is
full of my fame's grain
I am Bachchan Pande,
the sane and insane
Ah.. it seems like we've almost
cornered Bhaiyyaji! Cool.
Where are you going?
I'm coming with you.
No.. you wait here. Why?
You see, you are a delicate
darling from the call centre.
Now if someone were to shove
a gun on you like this..
...you'll be peeing in your pants.
All this bloodshed..
Hello Prince Charlie!
Saving your life..
...yours affectionately,
the Bhaiyyaji!!
Hooda was dead. There were only
two people in this story..
...that were not criminals,
ACP K S Hooda and me.
But now, to stay alive,
I had to be like them
Dangerous..
Cunning..
And a Kanpuriya.
Prayers
Smelling nice
Not for you
Listen whatever you want
to do, do it tonight.
Why?
Because if you make friends with the
hangman, hanging might be smoother.
Bachchan is our hangman?
Yes, I heard Bhaiyyaji
speaking to him.
So.. whatever you plan on doing,
do it now, babes!
It's so dark, I could hardly make
out the east from the west.
You pray everyday?
Normally, early in the morning,
not in the evening.
So what do you do in the evenings?
I drink.. okay?
Now don't presume that just because
I've had two drinks with you..
...It means that I'm on your side.
The nonsense you've
done with Bhaiyyaji
doesn't deserve forgiveness.
And you need not imagine that just
because I'm sitting with you..
...It means that I'll listen
to anything you say.
Given one chance and I'll be
out of here, money and all!
I know.
Anyway, this place is quite beautiful
And me?
And I'm not beautiful?
Of course you're beautiful,
very beautiful.
Liar!
I swear.
Swear on whom?
I swear on my aunt, on Omprakash,
on electricity.
Swearing on aunts and uncles
doesn't mean anything.
Really?
You only swear on someone that
you can't live without.
Someone on whom you can't bear
to see the slightest scratch
ls there anyone like this?
I can only swear on one person
Pooja, but I won't.
What are you looking at?
A cycle.
She rode her cycle in such fury..
...It moved with the
speed of a jet plane!
Hey.. why hasn't the electricity
come back yet?
That's what I'm trying to figure out.
How much longer?
How do I know what this
wire has in mind?
When the electricity returns..
...It will get to your house
automatically, okay.
Hey.. why'd you remove the air?
When the electricity returns
and comes to my house..
...the air will automatically
fill up, okay??
I had been stealing electricity
for seven years..
...but that was the first
time I got a shock.
It felt good.
I felt as though I could
handle shocks like this..
...for the rest of my
life for this girl.
She used to live right opposite..
...the vegetable market,
and I didn't know her.
But I wanted to know her.
Electricity.. er.. is
electricity coming?
Silly goose, the sun is bright and
shining. There's light everywhere!
You want some? Won't
cry now, will you?
Here.. eat.
That day I could've eaten
a zillion chillies.
Gudiyaaa.. Coming..
...because that was the day
I learnt her name. Gudiya!
Hey" Si")! 900se!!
Silly goose, your brain's loose!
You're just a bag of juice!
She didn't know my name but I didn't
mind being a silly goose..
...or an idiot or even
a donkey for her.
Silly goose, your brain's loose!
You're just a bag of juice!
- Silly goose, brain's loose..
Hey silly goose, this
is an all-girls school.
I know that.
- Did you follow me here?
Yes.. I mean no.. ummm..
What's your name?
Gudiya!
I mean what is your school name?
Kumari Udiyan School. I'll meet
after school and tell you!
Where?
At the old ghats.
It was not yet time for school to
be out, but I went there early.
I had decided that come what may..
...I was going to find out
Gudiya's real name today.
And as soon as she'd tell me her name,
I'll give her bangles.. pink bangles.
Hey
It's him, he's the one.
Been stealing electricity
have you, smarty pants?
Hey"
Yes.. the electricity
department is ours.
If anyone steals from it, we will.
Get up scoundrel..
I think he bled a couple
liters of blood.
I'm not sure but thanks to that..
...I spent the next two
years in the remand home.
When I came back, there was no
sign of Gudiya or her house
I heard later that it was
actually her aunt's house.
I looked for her everywhere
desperately..
...but I didn't even know her name..
...or where she was from.
She just disappeared.
Since that day I sometimes call
myself a silly goose. Makes me smile.
On a bad day after a couple drinks..
...I thrash the living daylights
out of some idiot..
...from the electricity department.
And then I go home and
sleep peacefully.
It's not such a depressing story.
I just told you because you asked.
Now you go.. who would you swear on?
Silly goose..
I am Gudiya.
I've always been like this but at
least you could've recognized me..
You're such a donkey. My official
name is Pooja Singh.
I went to the ghats that day after..
...school was over and
waited for two hours.
My aunt came to pick me up
but I was refusing to go..
That was the day my
father passed away.
I lost a lot on that day Bachchan.
I never went back to Kanpur after..
...that but I remember
every single thing.
The school, the chillies, the
pan shop at the corner..
...the market on Ram Devi
four-cross on Mondays, ..
...Imperial Talkies and Nigaar
Talkies right opposite each other..
...the tea stall near my school..
...and boys who ran behind
the girls' rickshaws..
Who went behind your rickshaw?
I used to cycle to school, silly goose
You.. you.. mean..
Yes..
Gudiya..
Yes. I've never sworn
on anyone till today.
You don't believe I'm Gudiya?
Will you believe it if I jump?
I would do anything
for you silly goose.
I don't even know what I'm
supposed to say now..
I love you.
What happened?
Gudiya, I feel shy.. I can't say it..
I can't say it Gudiya
What an actress?!
What comes after I love you?
After I love you?
What do you say after I love you?
Oh.. okay, listen. After I love you..
open the topmost button..
Opened.
Not yours, hers. Then, baby
I love you so much!
...And open her next button..
You're such a one track mind..
always a dirty mind
Fine don't ask me then man
Jimmy.. Jimmy.. Okay, if my feelings
towards her are bigger than love..
...as in a lot more than just love..
For something like that.. in
your English.. to a girl..
What do I say? What do I say?
Dude, people take forever
to just get to love.
No one's ever gone beyond that!
And you've got such a complicated
language for what? Nonsense.
Besides, who are you so
madly in love with?
Gudiya.. Gudiya..
Gudiya.. whose Gudiya?
Pooja! But I'll only call her
Gudiya once we're married.
Married...?
Yes.. you know like in
the English movies..
There is a way in which
they propose to a girl..
Stylish, suave and so romantic!!
But.. but here I am, an illiterate.
If someone's arm needs to be ripped
off, I know what needs to be done.
But if I need to ask
a girl to marry me..
...my tongue becomes
a knot. I get shy.
So I thought.. there's no one better
than Jimmy Sir to help me.
If you can give me some
tips on how to propose..
...maybe I can bring
up marriage with her.
See ..
Bachchan..
Shall we go?
Let's go!
TI
Into the skies, and beyond
Come with me, my fond
Past all horizons we see
Forever, together we'll be
Lying on a blanket of clouds
Wrapped underneath the stars
We'll steal a moment that's just ours
Into the skies, and beyond
Come with me, my fond
Past all horizons we see
Forever, together we'll be
Look at this land we've
found along our way
Where the shadows of night
drown into the arms of day
Let us celebrate these lanes
Soaked in love so insane
Making all dreams come true
I could keep my eyes shut tight
Follow you into an infinite night
This instant at one signal from you
Oh may spring come when
time stands still
And be filled with scrolls
of prayer and goodwill
Of love so true, it
moves a poet's will
Into the skies, and beyond
Come with me, my fond
Past all horizons we see
Forever, together we'll be
I may not be good looking ,
I may not be too quick.
I know I laugh funnily, in
fact I'm a bit of a dick.
And nothing ever will change it
if you be mine forever more..
Like Beckham I will bend it
forever and ever forever!
I love you..
Never before have I seen
such a beautiful sight
I'm in a universe so different,
it feels so right
The sun stirs towards you
Teases the night with its hue
Sitting immovable by your windowsill
At this the moon's temperature
did rise
Melting away into an empty guise
And bringing my eyes to a fill
Then I'll steal the sun's light
Adorn it on you so bright
That dawn will break at your sight
Into the skies, and beyond
Come with me, my fond
Past all horizons we see
Forever, together we'll be
Lying on a blanket of clouds
Wrapped underneath the stars
We'll steal a moment that's just ours
Into the skies, and beyond
Come with me, my fond
Past all horizons we see
Forever, together we'll be
Into the skies, and beyond
Come with me, my fond
My phone's ringing.
Bachchan, where have you reached?
Sir, I've got the last bag in my
hand. All bags with the full amount.
Good. Pooja's not
misbehaving is she?
No Bhaiyyaji, Pooja is
on her best behavior.
And guruii?
Behaving like good boy
Rascal! You're speaking English
as smoothly as melting butter
I've picked up a little Bhaiyyaji!
And now, do you know
what you have to do?
What Bhaiyyaji?
Load the gun with two bullets.
Blow Mr. Guru]I's brains
out and smile.
Tie a weight and throw
the body into the sea.
However, I think that..
...Pooja is a very smart girl.
I like her Tashan. I want her alive.
You bring her to me tomorrow.
It is an auspicious day.
I will marry her.
By the power invested
in me, etc etc...
Are they next to you?
- Yes sir.
This was not a phone
call from Bhaiyyaji..
...It was the alarm clock
of my destiny ringing.
I was back on earth in two seconds.
But in those two seconds, I realized
that no matter how many times..
...I find Gudiya again,
she would never be mine.
Hey!
You can't do this Bachchan..you
are not a killer
Gudiya
Do you have to go?
Bhaiyyaji is only concerned about..
...his money, which I'm
going to give him.
He'll never agree.
He will, don't worry. I'll tell
him that you both ran away.
Worst comes to worst, he'll hit
me.. torture me.. I'll be fine.
I can handle this.
But after all this, you
meet at the ghats, okay?
I'll be waiting.
I'm not very good with goodbyes..
Just keep this.. as.. everything.
And take care of yourself, okay.
Ove English!
You know, you're quite a
bastard but I like you.
Hey by-the-banks-of-the-Ganges,
you are a dude man. Thanks.
Same to all of us
Make sure Gudiya reaches Kanpur
safely. And if she doesn't.
...I'll hunt you down from the very
bottom of the pit of hell..
...and make a big fat hole in your
pretty little face, okay!! Bye.
Good luck.
Let's go!!
All the best dude.
Oh please, stop it Pooja, he's not
even looking at you any more.
Actually you know what, I love
this. You're such a brilliant actress!
So moved by the departure
of her love..
...after making a complete idiot
out of him. Brilliant!!
Please deny us the pleasure
of such fine acting..
I am Gudiya silly goose.
If you could, you'd try to make a
fool out of God and satan together
You're not a Gudiya, you're an
evil doll. Now what happened?
Are you feeling bad or is your
acting prowess still on display?
I haven't spoken truer words in
my life. I really am Gudiya.
Deenanath!
Yes mam.
Deenanath, what connection
have you gotten us?
That boy takes money to
provide electricity..
...but there never is any power.
No TV, no fans.. you're
completely useless.
Gudiya, will you please
go and have a look.
We had an illegal electricity
connection in our house.
Teach him a lesson that
he won't forget.
And when stolen electricity goes,
you experience a higher
level of anger.
When I get pissed off,
I don't spare anyone.
It was the first time I saw the boy
that stole electricity for us ..
...looked like complete donkey.
After that day, even if there
was no electricity in the ..
...entire neighborhood, our
house always had electricity.
He seemed like a bit
of crook to me..
...and also a birdbrain.
But I liked dumbos a lot!
I was very excited when I went
to meet him at the ghats.
But I met someone else there.
Vickram Tiger was my father's name..
...but all of Kanpur trembled
at the mention of him.
They said he resembled the
fierceness of a tiger. But that day..
Grant me this request dear cloud
Go and burst and speak out loud
Tell my father that
you are a disguise
Tell him you are his daughter's eyes
I knew what had actually
happened to my father..
...but I couldn't say anything then.
I lived from that day on only
to destroy Bhaiyyaji.
First I crucified Gudiya..
And a cold Pooja took her place.
A girl who could not be trusted.
Who used anything that came her way.
Including you.
...and landed in the
middle of all this.
He gave life to Gudiya again.
You don't believe me...?
This is probably the
first time I do..
But Bhaiyyaji's going
to kill Bachchan.
What?
There's no money in
the bags he took.
Bachchan, kindly tell
me where the money is?
Bhaiyyaji I swear, I would
never betray you.
Just give me two days and I'll
bring your money back..
...from that English
speaking traitor.
And Pooja?
She has nothing to do with this.
You love her, you dirty fellow!
Look at the irony Misir.
I wanted a murderer and I ended
up with a bloody Romeo.
Bad..
- Luck
Listen dear Romeo.
You can love Pooja all you want..
...but she will marry only me.
I think this punishment should
suffice for the both of you.
I will never let that happen
as long as I live.
Bhaiyyaji ..
Now I have Romeo, Juliet
and Prince Charlie!
We brought your money
Please take it and let Bachchan go
No.. no.. no.. My dear Pooja..
...I'm sorry but that's
not what I had in mind.
Bhaiyyaji, money and Pooja..
...both are yours.
Just let me go.
What's the hurry Mr. Guruji?
Besides, why didn't you
run with the money..
...and the girl, when you could?
I ran with your money once and
I've been running ever since.
My life turned upside down.
If I ran again, you wouldn't
even leave me with a life.
Why are you doing this? This
is not what we discussed.
How else would I have brought
you here my dear?
What did you think?
That I'm going to risk my life to
save you and your hairy gorilla?
No way sweetheart! Does
it hurt? Good..
...because when you left
me in my own house,
I also felt something like this.
This is my house.
Any slapping, I do.
Now I'll show you
the real Bhaiyyaji.
This is the real Bhaiyyaji
from Kanpur.
The Bhaiyyaji who killed
your father..
...stabbed him to death.
Raise that hand again and
its broken, you son of a..
Now I'm going to smash
your bloody brains..
Bhaiyyaji, please.
Smash them, come on.
I also have one Tashan..
I like Tashan.
Just saying hello in my own style.
Enjoyed beating me up did you?
Right that's it. That's
it you bastard..
...I am going to kill you
right here right now.
Bhaiyyaji please, please
give me that gun.
I want to kill him right
here right now.
I want to blow his head off.
Give me your gun.
When you speak English, even
Bramha cannot deny you.
Give me the gun Bhaiyyaji,
I want to kill him.
Bhaiyyaji, TASHAN lS.. You are the
fifty-third card on the deck.
The joker!
And I'm the third king, Don't you
see, I'm the sovereign ruler.
Do you remember this film?
Black stone?
Bhaiyyaji, I am a bit a of a
bastard but you didn't know that.
I may be English in my ways, but
deep down, I'm purely Indian.
Pooja, would you please
free Mr. Bachchan Pande?
And Bachchan, if my clan
fails to continue..
...I will hunt you
down and kill you.
Mr. Misir, Mr. Pintu, kindly
drop your guns ..
...otherwise I'll have to blow
Bhaiyyaji's beautiful brain ..
...on this piece of shit
you call a carpet.
Bhaiyyaji, I've respected you
since I was a little boy.
But you're not what
I thought you to be.
From this day forward..
...If you ever dare to look at my
Gudiya with your dirty eyes..
...I swear I'll pull
out your blooming..
...eyeballs and play
marbles with them.
And yes, this wonderful
little rotten..
...kingdom you've made
for yourself here
I will burn it down to nothing..
...and put the ashes
into your beady eyes.
O English brother!
Thank you.. really.
It's okay Bachchan.
Common, we've got a long way to
take these creeps. After you..
BASTARD!
They've got the style, they've
got the good luck..
...and they have the formula.
But I, Bhaiyyaji, am
the original bastard.
I've got the TASHAN.
I had never imagined that
to save my own life..
...I would have to take another's.
I never thought that
I could fire a gun.
But when the situation is such,
you learn to pull the
trigger automatically.
I knew that now, either
I won't survive this..
...or I'll slay Bhaiyyaji
and walk out of here.
Jimmy..
Bachchannnn!
You can go to your father now.
Romeo Pande huh?
You're very happy today,
very happy..
I wasn't naive or even
straight forward,
but I do have a little
innocence in me.
In our country, no matter how
much of a loser or dumbo..
...or Jackasses people are, when
the time comes they are the ones..
...who come to each other's rescue.
My life didn't change much. I
still work in a call centre.
India's first call centre with only
female employees! And I own it!!
We even got an award from
some feminist NGO. Right?
I mean, that's like eating your
cake and getting a medal for it!
My life changed as much
as it should have.
Nowadays, I get up every morning
with a fresh zest.
I don't go near anything wrong or..
...Illegal because I've
reached my shore.
After all, I'm not some
wild bull on the loose..
...my wife keeps me on
a very tight leash.
And I love it!!
Our life is normal.. As normal
as everyone else's.
But who knows what normal is?
It's quite a subjective word. All
we know is that what is life..
Without TASHAN!
I mean what's life without a little
TASHAN