[RUNNING FOOTSTEPS]
[THE LIONS RAMPANT'S
"LET US IN! (COME ON)" PLAYING]
REESE: Okay. There's three flags,
eight races.
The best freerunners
in the city of Metro.
The one who captures all three
flags, any way he can, wins.
[CAR HORN HONKING]
He's 6 feet.
He's flying, he's flipping.
Speed-demon mayhem.
Odds to win, 4-to-1 .
Ryan.
Five feet, 2 inches of
rabbit-quick reflexes. Kid Elvis.
Mitch, 5 foot 8 inches of
smash-mouth racing excitement.
He's known for his
jet-propelled jumps. Decks.
At 5 foot 8,163,
an unstoppable force, Turk.
A precision jumper with four wins
in the last month, it's West.
Bet now. Don't be slow,
as they race at 3.
Freebo, the newest runner
to the pack.
One win, odds 17-to-1 .
With seven wins this month...
...one word to describe him:
relentless.
Finch. Finch. Finch.
All bets in, the race is on.
[SLOWRIDE'S "PANTHER 1 "
PLAYiNG]
MYLES: You gotta see this.
Ryan got the first two flags.
Myles, i just want him to be okay.
Just teil me Ryan's okay.
-Where is he?
MYLES: He took a shortcut.
[ALL CHEERING]
[HORN HONKiNG]
Whoo! Nice hat.
ViEWERS:
Whoa! Oh!
My God! Finch got the last flag.
I know, Kid Elvis. I was there.
FINCH:
Mitch the bitch. Come and get it.
[CHEERlNG]
WEST: Right behind you, man.
RYAN: Ain't gonna make it.
I'm going over there.
REESE: Way to go, Finch!
There you go, son.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Now, there's a champion.
-Crazy son of a bitch.
ELVIS: He got lucky.
WEST: That couLd've killed you.
RYAN: What happened?
TURK: Finch happened.
REESE: This is a champion.
A true champion.
The winner, Finch!
[CROWD CHEERING]
This is gonna be fun.
That sateLlite feed
for tomorrow's Launch...
...is online, Mr. Frank.
Thank you, Jacque.
[CROWD CHEERING IN DISTANCE]
-Any way you can, right?
-Any way you can, kid. You're right.
-That's what you're teaching them?
-Yeah, why? What's the problem?
-You must be real proud.
-i am. Look at him.
Look at him.
What's the matter with you?
Ryan.
-Heil of a race.
-if you say so.
Look. Just keep at it, okay?
Yeah, l know. Tomorrow, right?
Yeah. There's always tomorrow.
Not the way that son of a bitch runs.
Don't worry about him.
That's history. Come here.
Get yourself off to a doctor.
Have him give you the once-over.
-That's it?
-No, that's just for the doctor.
You'll get the rest tonight, hey?
How much you make
on the race today, Reese?
There's aiways tomorrow, kid.
Don't you ever forget that.
There's aiways tomorrow.
[POLlCE SiREN WAiLlNG]
REESE:
Everybody move! Get out! Get out!
Let's go, baby.
Let's go, let's go!
Reese, baby, I still don't get it.
Okay, Dolores.
I'm gonna explain this
to you one last time.
[POP MUSIC PLAYiNG
INDISTINCTLY OVER CAR STEREO]
At the beginning of every race,
there's three bandanas.
A green one,
a yeilow one and a red one.
The kid that brings in
all three bandanas...
...any way he can, wins the money.
DOLORES: But they can bet on
themselves and fix the race.
I toid them i'd break the legs
of any freerunner...
...that bet on the races.
Yeah, but l'm watching it
on my phone.
That's because we put
cameras on aLl the roofs.
And we attach BLuetooth cameras
to all the runners.
And the kids eat that shit up.
Then l had this idea.
Put it online and make
the kids run against each other.
And boom, baby.
It takes off like wildfire.
Genius. WouLdn't you say,
princess?
-You coming in for a cuddLe?
CHELSEA: Hey, baby
[CHELSEA CHUCKLES]
Oh, wait. Can you shift
to the right a little bit?
-Uh-huh.
-All right. Hold on.
ALl right. Okay.
Maybe we should be
icing those bruises.
Nah, i'm fine.
Let's just lay here
and enjoy paradise.
Smell that salt air?
[CHELSEA LAUGHS]
You mean the pollution?
Which gives us
these amazing sunsets.
[CHELSEA LAUGHS]
You know, we used to talk about
moving closer to the ocean.
What happened?
Life happened.
[CHELSEA SiGHS]
I've got to get ready for work, baby.
Are you bartending
or singing tonight?
Singing. Can you come by?
Yeah, l'm gonna work at the hospitaL
and see my gramps for a bit.
-i'li come by after.
-Okay. I'm on at 9.
-i'li catch a later set?
-Whatever.
If that's your plan, that's your plan.
Reese. Reese.
You used to be one of the leading
heavyweight contenders of the world.
Entrenched with the game of life.
And now you work for me.
Count it if you want.
No, Mr. Frank. it's fine. i trust you.
[RYAN SiGHS]
RYAN [THlNKiNG]:
I gotta get us out of here.
Me, Chelsea, my gramps.
Get him out of that pit of a hospitaL.
Get us to the coast. Fix the boat up.
Man, l'm so damn broke.
Can't bet on the races,
can't bet on myself.
Wait a minute.
[CAR HORNS HONKlNG]
MYLES: l don't know.
Didn't Reese say he'd kilL you...
...you pLace a bet on yourself?
RYAN:
Yeah, if l bet on the race.
lf l bet on the race. But...
...what if i deposit ali of
my money into your account?
Then you couid place a bet, right?
Yeah. Yeah, dude.
Say the word. Done.
[TYPiNG]
Dude, what the heli are you doing?
Dude, I'm hacking into
the government's...
...experimentai software programs,
all right?
They have the next 200 years
of software ready to go.
Check this out, look.
It's these damn congiomerates
that just parceL it out to us...
-...like cheese.
-i'm late for work.
-We're just rats in their cyber maze.
-Gotta go. Good luck.
I'll tell you Later.
[POLlCE SiRENS WAiLING
IN DlSTANCE]
Would you hold still, Gramps?
Hold stilL? For chrissake, you're
hoLding a straight razor to my neck.
Where am i gonna go?
If you stopped talking,
I'd probabiy be finished by now.
You know, I wanna lay down
and relax.
RYAN:
Check that out. What do you think?
It's not bad. Smooth.
Did a good job, kid.
Well, you didn't make it easy,
now, did you?
Nothing great came from easy.
Except great sex from easy women.
How'd l know you were gonna
go somewhere dirty like that?
It shows. There's a little sign
up here that says "dirty."
[LAUGHS]
ALl right. What do you
wanna watch on TV right now?
I don't know.
Let's sit here and just talk
to each other for a Little bit.
Okay. Anything in particular?
I don't know.
Turn on the goddamn TV again.
I don't care.
I was looking at those
pictures earlier today.
GRAMPS: You spend all your
break time in my room?
What, do you come in here
and look at everything?
Sometimes. Remember that day?
Hell, I remember it weLl.
Your dad caught three groupers.
It was a miracle. Funny.
Handsome kid just like you.
He fell off the same pot.
God onLy knows
where we got it from, hey?
You know, sometimes, kid,
a toad and a swan get together...
...and make something
pretty special.
What are you talking about?
You're not a toad.
I wasn't thinking about me,
I was talking about Grandma.
[BOTH LAUGH]
No, that's okay.
She was down with that.
She understood.
We kidded a lot. Yeah, she did.
So, what about that boat?
Where is it?
Still there. Dry dock.
Yeah, the boat's all eaten up
by now anyway.
Rats and termites and muskrats,
whatever eats wood.
-But it's there?
-Yeah, it's stili there.
I bet l could fix it, Gramps.
I know you couid, kiddo.
You can be good
at anything you want.
I just don't Like you working here.
Enough of this male bonding thing.
You wanna watch some TV?
You wanna watch the game?
Yeah, put the game on.
[BAND PLAYiNG
SLOW POP MELODY]
* Driving along
I hear a song *
* It brings back a time
I thought i ieft behind *
* The hate l once had *
* Melts into what i want *
* This doesn't help me
To get over us *
* And i can't go on
Any further *
* 'Cause i know
I'm back to my old habits *
* Falling into your trap
I can't let you out of my head *
* And i want to so bad
I've been here before *
* Can't take it no more
There's no use hoiding on *
* It's aiready been done *
* Yeah, it's already been done **
[AUDIENCE CHEERiNG
AND APPLAUDiNG]
MAN: Ladies and gentlemen,
another round of applause...
...for Kitty Kat Club's own Chelsea.
[ROCK MUSlC PLAYiNG iNSIDE]
Come on.
Just here to pick up my girL.
Boss said no.
-He's a good man, Dedee.
-He's a good kid...
...but none of them are men,
and that's the problem, Cheisea.
I mean, West is, um--
Oh, my God. i don't even wanna
tell you how good he is in bed.
But do l think for a second
it's serious with him?
-Why not?
-Chelsea.
They're freerunners.
Just the kind of guy you wanna
bring home to meet the P's.
Dad, this is West.
[IN DEEP VOiCE]
Hey, West. What do you do?
[MIMiCS WEST]
Well, dude, i Like to climb shit, party...
...and beat the crap
out of my friends.
The band is out there
waiting for you.
I gotta teli you this
every goddamn time?
Sorry, Morris.
I'm just saying, Chelse.
MORRIS:
Break a Leg, Dedee.
[BAND PLAYiNG "BEiN' BLUE"]
[DEDEE GiGGLES]
On second thought,
break them both.
[DOOR OPENS THEN CLOSES]
What is she just saying?
-What do you want, Morris?
-Whoa, whoa, whoa. Wow.
Okay. ls that where
our relationship is right now?
There is no reiationship, Morris.
Never has been, never will be.
DEDEE:
* Bein' bLue, bein' bLue *
Touch me one more time
and you're gonna lose the hands.
-You're such a tease.
-You're such a pervert!
Ha-ha. And proud of it.
[SLAPS]
[CHUCKLES]
Come on, baby. Let's do it.
Stay away from me!
MORRIS: Come on!
RYAN: Let her go!
What the fuck, Morris?
You're fired!
I'm calling the cops.
That guy's a jerk.
I know.
Maybe this ali happened...
...as part of some bigger,
cosmic master plan.
And what is this bigger,
cosmic master plan?
I'll tell you on the way.
Come on, let's go.
That's a crazy pLan, Ryan.
You want me to stop racing
and you want to get out of the city.
This is our chance.
But you said Reese
would break the legs...
...of any freerunner
who bets on themselves.
That's where Myles comes in.
Oh, so you got
my stepbrother involved.
[RYAN SiGHS]
ALl I know is after the race today...
...something just clicked.
-Yeah, it's called a concussion.
-No, it was a revelation.
Seriously, i've had enough of this.
It's time we make our dreams come
true and get out of this place.
It's dangerous.
Where the hell are we?
Reese is throwing a party
for us around the corner.
It's supposed to be
for aLl the freerunners.
But it couid be
our going-away party, right?
Right?
I'm right, right?
Where is the party?
It's around the corner.
Baby, let's just have
fun tonight, okay?
[CROWD CHEERING]
[AMBER'S "GET A REAL WOMAN"
PLAYiNG OVER SPEAKERS]
[ALL CHEERING]
REESE:
Last race tomorrow, boys.
Get them down.
Yeah, drink up, drink up.
REESE: Ryan, you asked me
how much money i made, right?
-Let's have a talk.
RYAN: Okay.
If l hear that you've
been running around...
...biabbing your mouth off
about what l'm doing to anybody--
And i mean anybody,
the fans, the freerunners.
--i'm gonna punch
a hole in your heart.
Do I make myself clear?
Look at me.
Crystal.
-Good.
CHELSEA: Are you guys having fun...
-...or what?
-We're always having fun, sweetheart.
Cheers.
Look at you. Ain't you a picture?
You know we have a saying
back in London...
...for somebody who gets
a prize like this?
You've absolutely rung
the beLl, son. All right?
Be nice to her. She's a winner.
ALl right.
Remember what I said to
you. Come, baby, let's go.
Hey, there's always tomorrow.
See you.
I don't like that guy. What's wrong?
Nothing.
Hey, I know you. What's wrong?
It's just been a really
long day, baby. That's all.
CHELSEA: Come on.
FINCH: Oh.
RYAN:
Let's go.
[LiGHTS BUZZiNG]
[DOOR BELL DlNGS]
RYAN: So, l could rent the boat
out for tours...
...and you could
get a job singing at a club.
I'm scared. I don't know.
RYAN: it'lL be amazing.
-Just the condoms?
Uh-- Yeah, just the condoms.
[SCANNER BEEPiNG]
Not going through. Harry!
Lucky Condoms?
HARRY:
Condoms? Which condoms? Lucky?
-Lucky Condoms.
HARRY: Lucky Condoms?
-Lucky!
-Yes! Lucky!
I'm Mr. Lucky and
I'm getting iucky with this girl.
[BEEPlNG]
Crashed.
See? So much for
getting lucky, smart boy.
[BOTH LAUGH]
RYAN: We should seil it all.
-My car?
RYAN:
Everything.
-i'm not selLing the Volvo.
-Fine.
-What?
-You're forgetting one thing.
-You've never beaten him.
You've never beaten Finch.
I won't lose.
I won't ever let you down.
You promise?
I promise.
[PHONE RlNGING]
RYAN [ON RECORDlNG]:
Hey, it's Ryan. Leave a message.
MYLES:
Ryan, it's Myles.
We're seLling yourseLf
before the race today, right?
I'm at the cyber cafe.
We doing this or not?
lt's your pLan. Big money day.
Last race in the season.
Rise and shine.
CHELSEA:
Are you meeting my brother?
Yeah. l told him that
we'd meet at the cyber cafe.
MYLES: Hey, whatever, dude.
It's your plan, okay?
I'm just a cog in the wheel
of the machine here.
Shut up, Myles.
you shut up.
Ryan told me to calL.
He didn't teil you
to be so annoying.
Myles, we'il meet at the
cyber cafe in a half hour, okay?
Copy that. Oh, CheLsea?
What?
[MYLES BURPS LOUDLY]
CHELSEA:
Disgusting.
[MYLES CHUCKLES]
RYAN:
Baby.
I don't want you to do this
for me or my grandfather.
You can stay if you want.
I want you to do this because
it's what you wanna do.
Shut up.
This piece of shit?
I'll give you
one, two, three, four, five...
...six, seven, eight, nine and 1 0.
RYAN:
Well, that's it.
MYLES: you sold all your stuff, man?
I can't believe it.
MYLES:
We got, like, over eight grand.
RYAN:
It's time for you to pLace that bet.
MYLES: You better win, dude.
RYAN: Yeah.
RYAN:
And you see that?
You can have virtual friends
onLine, Gramps.
I have virtual friends.
They're called my friends.
I know, i know. But here,
check it out. That's the site.
GRAMPS: What? What is this?
RYAN: Hoid on, Gramps. lt's loading.
These are some of my racing
friends. Click here, that's me.
GRAMPS: What is that there?
RYAN: That's how you place a bet.
That's me, Gramps. That's what
I do when I'm not working here.
-What is that? A race?
-Yeah.
-What are you racing for?
-To get us back to the ocean.
-Then win the fucking race.
-i plan to...
...but how would Grandma feel
with you taLking like that?
She didn't like the word,
but she iiked doing it.
You couldn't stop her
when she got going.
[LAUGHS]
ALl right, look, i'm--
Just watch at 3, okay?
I'm gonna sit here
and wait for it to come on.
-i gotta go do this.
-Yeah, okay. i'll watch.
Think about your grandma.
You can let go of my iip now.
I thought you liked my love bites.
I love your love bites.
I'm just trying to stay focused.
Ryan wins, Ryan wins, Ryan wins.
Tell me, do you always
talk to yourself?
Uh-- Yeah.
I'm very good company.
I bet.
DEDEE:
Do you always talk to yourself?
MYLES: I'm very good company.
DEDEE: l bet.
I bet.
Shit! The bet. The bet!
REESE: Ail right, here we go.
It's the last race of the season.
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
Here we go.
Make it good and memorable.
-Myles?
REESE: Come on.
Okay, freerunners, line them up.
Now pay attention, because
I'm only gonna say this once.
It's a three-flag race
with three Locations.
The green flag is at the top of
Pantry's Tavern's fire escape.
Then you head on through
the Trust Building's aLleyways...
...to get to the yeilow flag.
And the red flag is at the warehouse
where we were partying iast night.
But do me a favor, boys.
When you get there, try not
to slip on Kid Elvis' puke, hey?
Now, come on, boys.
Whatever it takes, hey? Come on!
Yesterday was a fluke, asshole.
And you stiLl didn't win.
-Only because you tried to kilL me.
-No, I was oniy playing.
I'm not.
-Jeez, Ryan. You frighten me.
REESE: Okay, Dolores, baby. CalL it.
On your mark, get set, go!
CHELSEA: Where's Ryan?
MYLES: Dead last.
TURK: Mitch got the green flag!
Get it! Get it!
WEST:
Ryan's got it!
Wait up!
See, i like this kid,
but he never wins.
Jacque, he'll be there soon.
We're ready here.
* l don't wanna be faLling down
Too high... *
Come on. Come on, baby.
-Look at that.
-Mm-hm.
The kid can run.
JACQUE:
They're heading there now.
Hold on, no ketchup?
[LAUGHlNG]
Shit, yeah!
FINCH: There's no way you're leaving
here with all three flags.
TURK:
Eat a dick, Finch.
Why don't we see about that, huh?
[LOUD THUD]
TURK:
Hey.
What--?
What the--?
What happened? Did he win?
ELVIS:
ALl the doors are locked, man.
Check that. l'm taking those flags.
Stop pulling!
ELVIS: They're aLl locked.
TURK: Fucking Reese is playing us.
WEST: What the hell?
TURK: Is anybody up there?
MiTCH: What the heli is that?
TURK: What the fuck?
WEST:
Let us out!
-What is this?
MiTCH: Who's up there?
-in the middle of a race.
FREEBO: What the fuck is that?
DECKS: What the hell is that?
ELVIS: You guys see that?
TURK:
This is some kind ofjoke, right?
RYAN:
I don't think so.
[GAS HlSSING]
FRANK: I love watching
all the racers, their stats.
Check out their forms
and techniques.
TERENCE: Yeah, you know it's
important to look up races...
...old races, checking out
form and technique.
But always remember the banker:
Past performance does not
guarantee future performance.
GERMAN:
l'Ll bet $2 milLion.
TERENCE:
you know what they say, old son.
Talk is cheap, money buys whiskey.
Eight million.
[ALL GROANiNG]
ELVIS:
Where am i?
-What the fuck?
FINCH: Shit.
[GRUNTiNG]
ELVIS:
Fuck, man.
[ALL GRUNTiNG]
TURK: What the fuck?!
WEST: Goddamn it.
ELVIS:
Ryan, where are we?
[GRUNTiNG AND PANTiNG]
-What?
DECKS: What is that?
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
My name is Mr. Frank.
And for the next 60 minutes...
...you are my unwiLling participants
in a race for your life.
-Here are the rules--
-Yeah, fuck you!
Back up! You better
let me out right fuck-- Aah!
[NECK CRACKING
AND DECKS GRUNTING]
TURK: Oh, what the fuck
are you doing to him?
[DECKS SCREAMS]
Rule number one:
you never interrupt me.
Jacque spent 1 5 years
in a Japanese dojo...
...learning that grip.
And he never gets tired of it.
Rule number two:
The device around your
neck is set to expLode...
...in exactly 60 minutes.
There's no stopping that now.
If you go to the police...
...l wiLl push the manual
detonate button.
And then you're no Longer
members of this pLanet.
OnLy l have the remote,
only L can reLease you.
So you'd better race as if
your Life depended on it.
And let me assure you gentlemen,
heh...
-...it does.
-Bullshit.
See, Jacque? l knew we would
need a littLe demonstration.
FREEBO:
What's going on, man?
-Let me go!
-What the fuck are you doing?
Green means armed.
yellow lights--
No, wait, wait! We'll race!
We'll race! We'll all race!
Red Lights.
[DEVlCE BEEPING
AND MiTCH SCREAMlNG]
for unlimited celebrity sex videos visit
www.celebritysex.tk
TURK:
Fucking mental, man.
I'm sorry I had to expose you...
...to the grim reaLity
of your situation.
But there is some good news.
Jacque?
One million dollars to
the freerunner who makes it...
...to the top of the railroad bridge
before 60 minutes has elapsed.
What about second piace?
Bring it, dickface.
That's the spirit.
I'll let the club's hostess,
Stacey, explain the rest.
Hi, l'm Stacey.
Welcome to the club's
death game of the year.
Heda, please leave alone.
Hold alL my calLs.
-i will not be disturbed now.
-No one is to disturb me...
-...while i'm playing the game.
-Money, money. LoveLy money.
Come to Daddy.
I'm watching the fucking
death game here.
ALl of you shut the fuck up.
Hey, Jersey. We're supposed
to watch alone.
I'm aione.
STACEY:
This year's host...
...the newest and brightest club
member of them all, Mr. Frank.
Well, we'll see about that.
And his game, Freerunner!
Okay, freerunners, time to race
for your lives. Here's the game.
You wiil have exactly 60 minutes...
...to make it across
to the railroad bridge, or kaboom!
Each runner's collar is equipped...
...with built-in video
to capture the action.
-Nice.
-Locked on to their wrists...
...a combo GPS timer
and a one-way videophone...
...that Mr. Frank wiLl be
checking in on you with.
ALong the way, the runners must pass
their neckwear by rooftop scanners.
Number one is on top
of the Giazier Building.
The second scanner is high atop
the Caxson water tower.
And the iast scanner is at the
highest point of the railroad bridge.
Important:
Whoever is in last place...
...has onLy three seconds
to reach the scanner, or:
STACEY & JERSEY:
Kaboom!
Stray away from
the chosen GPS route...
...the runners have only five
minutes to get back on course, or:
Kaboom!
Oh, and don't mess with
Mr. Frank or his coilars.
As you've just seen, he has
no problem activating his detonator.
That's right, boys, five ways
to die, one way to Live:
Win.
Hold on. No, no.
I said 1 0 million
on Decks to die first...
...1 0 million on Turk to win.
Everyone got it?
Oh, and freerunners...
...take them in, boys, because they're
the last tits most of you will ever see.
And the first.
May the best freerunner win.
I'll be calling you
on your wrist devices...
...to check in from time to time.
And i'll be watching you
on your collar cameras.
As well as every security cam...
...traffic cam and satellite cam.
We'lL aLl be watching.
Won't we, gentlemen?
WALL STREET:
Come on, Kid Elvis!
[ALL TALKING iNDiSTiNCTLY]
Five. Put 5 miliion on.
Turk, Turk. Come on, Turkey, baby.
Bring it home to Daddy, baby.
[MEN TALKlNG lNDlSTlNCTLY]
[SPEAKS IN FORElGN LANGUAGE]
-Yeah.
-Why are you doing this?
Why?
TERENCE: Two million. l'll raise that.
KOREAN: Two.
-Because it's fun.
-Oh, this is gonna be fun. Ha-ha-ha.
On your mark, get set....
Release the freerunners!
STACEY:
To get to the first scanner...
...the boys must cross
the top of the pedestrian bridge.
Come on, baby! That's it, bitch.
Yeah, baby. Whoo-hoo.
Stomp his stupid body, West.
STACEY: It's Freebo in fourth place,
Turk in fifth.
Ryan has helped Kid ELvis
and has fallen behind.
Freebo dies first.
I can't believe it. They're doing it.
They're running your race.
Of course they are.
What did i telL you gentlemen?
You may have been playing your littLe
hunting games throughout the years...
...but my game's gonna
blow you away.
[LAUGHS]
TEXAS:
Move! Move! Yeah. All right, now.
Now we're taLking. Let's go.
JERSEY:
Bada-bing. Bada-bing.
Here we go, Freebo, baby.
Come on.
KOREAN: Come on, Ryan.
Come on now. You can do it.
I have a lot of money on you.
Keep going! Keep going, Ryan!
Don't stop!
We shouid go to the right, right,
man? Which way do we go?
FINCH:
How about down?
[SCREAMlNG]
Did Finch just kick Decks off
the building? What an asshole.
GERMAN:
Way to die, Decks!
Ugh! Stupid Decks!
I lost a lot of my money!
What did you do?
Dead man Decks.
Pay all side bets now.
An earlier departure for Decks...
...than predicted by the odds.
lt's anyone's game here,
gentlemen.
Finch! You are my man! Ha-ha-ha.
WEST: Aw, man.
TURK: Shit. Decks!
WEST:
He's dead, man. Come on, let's go.
FRANK: Guess Decks is a safe bet
the day he's died.
[MEN SHOUTlNG AND CHEERING]
MAN 1: Somebody stop him!
MAN 2: There you go.
MAN 3: Got nothing on you, man.
MAN 4: Come on!
MAN 5: Whoa. Shit!
Why the hell's this guy--?
MAN 4: Come on!
MAN 2: There you go.
STACEY: West, Turk and Freebo
clear the first scanner.
[SCANNER BEEPiNG]
But where's Finch?
WEST: Where's Finch?
TURK: Who cares?
After the first scanner,
West is in the lead.
Pay all side bets now.
Pay all side bets.
Hell of a game, Mr. Frank.
Oh, my God,
I just lost my factory.
l told you you shouLdn't
have took that bet, Chinaman.
STACEY:
Remember, the last one...
...has only three seconds
to be scanned.
TERENCE: All right, Kid Elvis.
I've got a lot of money on this.
RYAN:
Kid! The scanner's over here!
ELVIS:
Unh!
-Finch, what the fuck?
FINCH: Kili or be kiLled.
Come on, Kid ELvis. Come on.
Hit him in the face!
Go on, get in there!
GERMAN:
Yeah, Finch!
Finch, help, man!
TERENCE:
My money's on you, Kid.
You want my heip? Drop him.
STACEY: Finch scanned himself.
Who will be left? Ryan or Kid Elvis?
TERENCE: Come on, Kid Elvis.
Pick yourself up! Come on, Kid.
Uh-oh. Ryan accidentally
just scanned himself.
[BEEPlNG]
Mom.
[EXPLOSiON]
Kid!
You couldn't fucking
beat my grandmother!
Whoo! Man! That was-- Man, that
was Like an exploding watermeion.
Man! Whoo! That was something!
Kid Elvis bites the dust.
Two scanners to go and we're
aLready down to five pLayers.
FRANK:
l see you're aLl broken up, Ryan.
-But keep moving.
-You're a murderer.
I'm a businessman.
I'm gonna find you, and when i do....
Well that's very easy to do, Ryan.
you win the race and I will be there.
And i will hand you $1 million.
And then we can work out
life's iittle problems when it's over.
When this is over, so are you.
[POLlCE SiREN WAiLlNG]
Well, you better get
a move on, then.
[GlRL CHUCKLES]
Because I don't think
you're gonna make it.
Bring it to my desk
when you've filled it out.
ALl right.
COP [OVER RADiO]: Explosions at
MagnoLia and 1 2th Street.
Those crazy running guys
we're talking about.
[POLlCE SiREN WAiLlNG]
One is 6 foot, blue sweatshirt.
All suspects heading
towards 7th Street now.
7th Street and MagnoLia.
[POLlCE SiREN WAiLlNG]
[COPS SHOUTlNG lNDlSTlNCTLY]
[HORN HONKiNG]
COP:
Hey, you!
COP [OVER RADiO]: Between Main
and Oak. Between Main and Oak St.
[SIREN WAILlNG]
COP 1 : Freeze!
COP 2: Freeze!
-Wait, wait. You don't understand.
COP 1 : Get your hands up!
Cover him.
RYAN:
Listen, man. There's a guy--
Let me guess.
A criminal mastermind, right?
And you got 30 minutes...
...to deiiver a secret formula
or something. Get in there.
Shut the door.
Let's get out of here.
Uh-oh. An unexpected levei of
difficuLty for the boys.
Unexpected ieveL, my ass. They're
putting those boys in a SWAT van.
I was having so much fun.
GERMAN: Please press the
detonator now, Mr. Frank.
It's gotta be through Reese that
this guy even knows who we are.
-That's buLlshit, man.
-Well, think about it!
The cameras? The scanners?
They're just like the flags in our race.
This whole last year has been nothing
but a rehearsal for today's main event.
TURK: That's twisted.
-So?
So we piay.
One of us goes and locates Reese...
...we get him to teli us
where to find this guy.
-How do we do that?
-From inside the police truck?
FREEBO:
In the next 33 minutes?
What the fuck, Frankie?
BLow them up.
-Why biow them up?
-They'Ll turn us in, Chinaman.
I'm Korean, you dumb fucker.
Mr. Frank, before they turn us in.
Press your detonator!
Gentlemen, i have tremendous faith
in the resourcefulness of my players.
[TlMER BEEPiNG]
WEST: GPS countdown started!
We must be out of the green zone.
TURK: Fuck this bullshit.
WEST: We got Less than 5 minutes!
-it'lL bLow!
COP 2: Quit rocking the van!
That's it.
Get up. We're gonna roli this bitch.
-Get up.
FINCH: That's not gonna work.
RYAN:
One, two, three.
COP 2:
I said cut it out back there!
FREEBO: Shit!
RYAN: Go!
KOREAN:
What are they doing?
-Trying to roil the van!
-Roil it, baby.
I love these fucking guys.
[TlRES SCREECHING]
[ALL GRUNTiNG]
JERSEY: Would you look
at these fucking guys?
RYAN:
yes! Keep going, more!
Holy shit!
[LAUGHS]
Ha-ha-ha. Wow.
TEXAS:
Holy cow!
-You're aLive! You're aLive!
MAN 1 : Yeah, baby!
RYAN: you gotta get back to
this green zone, let's go!
MAN 2: That's my boy!
MAN 3: you're gonna blow up....
MAN 4:
Green zone, baby! Come on!
COP [ON RADIO]: Suspects heading
south, towards 6th and Thistle.
MAN 1: Come on, run!
MAN 2: That's it.
-Go, baby! Go!
RYAN: Chelsea!
Everybody get in the car!
Come on, come on!
We got 40 seconds
to get back to the green zone!
JERSEY:
Who's the broad in the car?
-Get to the green zone!
CHELSEA: What's going on?
FINCH: Go! Chelsea, stop talking
and just drive!
TURK:
Come on, let's go!
Drive faster, baby.
You gotta drive faster!
Why is everyone
yeliing at me, Ryan?
Just drive!
FINCH:
Just drive, stupid-ass!
I'm doing the best that l can!
-You are all out of your minds!
FREEBO: We're dead!
[COLLARS BEEPING]
CHELSEA:
What's up with the collars, guys?
If the boys don't make it back into
the green zone within 20 seconds...
...there's going to be one hell of
a mess to cLean up in that car.
-i love you.
-What are you doing?
RYAN:
I'm sorry, I love you. You gotta go!
What's wrong with--?
Ryan, stop it! Ryan!
Stop it!
The boys made it
to the green zone...
...with one second to spare.
What a rush.
TURK: Oh, my God. We made it.
WEST: We made it!
-We did it! We're alive!
-We made it.
-What the heLl is the matter with you?
-i love you, Chelsea!
WEST & FREEBO:
We iove you, Chelsea!
RYAN: You're so amazing.
-And i'm a great driver.
-TelL her she's a great driver.
TURK: Best driver, Chelsea!
WEST:
Best driver in the worid.
What the hell is going on?
STACEY: And we're back to
the races, gentlemen.
Wow, there's over $70 miilion
in the pot right now.
Let's look at the board.
Best bet to the yelLow scanner,
Finch to win at 2-to-1 .
Ryan to pLace at 4-to-1
and West to finish third at 4-to-1 .
With odds-on favorites
Freebo and Turk to die.
Place aLl yelLow scanner
side bets now!
Side bet, side bet. i play the--
Buy a half-million shares
of iFR lndustries-- Hoid.
Stacey, add 3 million
on Ryan to die here.
I wili put my money
where my mouth is.
Stacey, triple ail of my bets
to the yeLlow scanner.
Finch first, Ryan second,
West third. Turk, dead.
I triple all my bets too, Stacey.
-The fuck. I'm in too. Trip it.
-Ryan, Finch--
Freebo win, Finch show,
Ryan place, West dead.
Bada Bing, you nuts? Freebo?
What? Pacino, De Niro, Freebo.
Name ends in an O.
He's gotta be good.
Oh, oh, oh. Okay.
FRANK: l see you're back
on course, freerunners.
I'd be Lying if l said
I wasn't rooting for you.
Of course you are.
What the hell is Rome
without its gladiators?
CHELSEA: Who's that?
-No one, Chelsea.
Chelsea?
Ah. Exquisite taste, Ryan.
Shut your goddamn mouth!
It's quite a show you're giving
us today, boys. lt's very good.
Glad we could make this
exciting for you, asshole!
-Yeah. Very exciting, Turk.
WEST: Shit.
Now, by my clock...
...you have just under 24 minutes
to make the next two scanners.
FREEBO: We'li never make it!
WEST: Gotta get to Reese's gym!
FINCH: Get to the yellow flag!
RYAN: Gotta find Reese. Turn right!
FINCH: Turn ieft.
-Go right. We're going to Reese's gym.
FINCH: Water tower is left.
RYAN: Take a right.
-Who was that? Which way?
RYAN: Right!
FINCH: Left!
-Right!
FINCH: Goodbye, losers.
TURK: Finch, Finch!
Finch! You son of a bitch!
for unlimited celebrity sex videos visit
www.celebritysex.tk
TURK:
Stop the car! We gotta stop the car!
WEST: If he's racing....
TURK: Stop the car!
No, we gotta find Reese!
He makes it to the last scanner,
that's it, we're dead!
Chelsea. Stop the car.
Come on, West, baby!
Come on! My money's on you!
What's going on? We lost everything.
And i'm sorry, but in 24 minutes,
this thing around my neck explodes.
That'lL be everything.
-That's why you tried to throw me out.
-Yes.
What are you doing?
Send this to Myles.
Tell him to run a search of that logo.
The company it belongs to,
CEO, location...
...anything he can find
that relates to this guy.
He calis himself Mr. Frank.
-Where are you going?
-Gotta go!
I gotta get back in the race
or l'm dead!
I'll take you there. Let's go.
[HORN HONKS]
STACEY: Finch's bold move
launches him into first place.
There's West sprinting into second.
Go, go, go!
Come on, Turk. Go, Turk. Go, Turk!
JERSEY: Here we go, Freebo, baby.
Come on, come on. Bada-bing.
-Come on!
TERENCE: Let's go. Come on, baby.
STACEY: Turk and Freebo are trying
a shortcut through the mall.
JERSEY: Here we go, here we go.
Now we're taLking.
TERENCE: Come on. Let's go.
Here we go, guys.
JERSEY:
Come on, Freebo.
[MEN SPEAKlNG INDlSTlNCTLY]
WALL STREET:
Let's go! Let's go!
TERENCE: Where's my man?
Where the bloody hell is my man?
TEXAS:
Come on. Come on!
JERSEY: We're back in it,
we're back in it. Come on, Freebo!
you're right behind him.
Buddy, let's go!
RYAN: i'li meet you back at my place.
CHELSEA: Go, Ryan!
JERSEY: Get that camera inside.
l wanna see my guy. There he is.
TEXAS: you're gonna win this.
You have to win, l expect you to win.
WALL STREET:
Hustle, hustle.
[COLLAR BEEPING]
Freebo. Your-- Your collar.
FREEBO:
Get back there. Get back!
TERENCE:
What happened to his collar?
TEXAS:
He's ticking. He's ticking.
Freebo's collar short-circuits.
-Goodbye, Freebo. We'll miss you.
JERSEY: No!
-Good luck, Turk.
-Freebo!
Oh!
You stupid,
orange-sweatshirted...
...goddamn motherfucker!
I'm a banker, Jersey.
Should've listened to me.
Bankers? Aiways certain,
seldom right.
Add 1 0 million on round
for yellow scanner.
I reckon your guy's
onLy got one gear...
...somewhat resembLing
an Italian tank:
Reverse.
I'll take Mr. Frank's boy, Finch'll
die here, 14 miLlion. l'm in now.
Fourteen million
against that bet, Jersey.
STACEY:
West, Turk, Finch and Ryan.
For the one that's three
seconds late to the scanner...
...it's sayonara, freerunner.
RYAN:
Turk! Guys, take it easy.
Let's just all stand
and figure out what to do next.
WEST:
I don't trust Finch.
STACEY: lt's a four-runner
showdown. Who will survive?
West takes one in the face.
He'll feel that in the morning,
if he makes it to morning.
TEXAS:
Come on!
Gouge his eyes out!
Tear his head off!
TURK: Back off.
-Aah!
[SAUDi LAUGHS]
STACEY: Ouch. Bye-bye, West.
Three freerunners left.
Go, Turk, baby. Scanner, baby.
Scanner, baby! Get that scan!
[SCANNER BEEPS]
KOREAN: How could you do this
to me? l believed in you.
[SCANNER BEEPS]
JERSEY: Ryan's gonna blow.
RYAN: Come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on!
[SCANNER BEEPiNG ERRATlCALLY]
-Come on!
WOMAN: Crashed.
[CONTlNUOUS BEEP]
COMPUTER: System failure.
-Yeah!
COMPUTER:
System failure. System failure.
Wow. Ryan jammed Mr. Frank's
remote and GPS.
How in the world
did he figure that out?
Mr. Frank must be pissed.
[WRiST PHONE BEEPING]
RYAN:
I beat your game, bitch.
You disrupted my game.
And i applaud your
ingenuity, I really do.
However, if you don't win
the race in the next 1 9 minutes...
...L promise you...
...that colLar is gonna give you
one spLitting headache.
RYAN:
Bullshit.
It's quiet out there, isn't it, Ryan?
But if you just iisten
to your colLar. Just listen.
What does it teLl you?
Yes.
That low-level hum that you hear.
That is your death march, Ryan.
So you better win the race.
Go fuck yourseLf.
What the hell just
happened, Mr. Frank?
Blow that boy's head up.
State-of-the-art technology,
Mr. Frank?
Stacey, what the fuck
just happened?
Ryan's collar update. A sLight
engineering flaw has been detected.
No shit, Sherlock.
STACEY: Mr. Frank's GPS
and detonator have been deactivated.
Mr. Frank can't blow him up.
Ryan can now Leave the green zone.
But his 60-minute countdown...
...is still at 1 9 minutes and his
must-win explosive is still operational.
Put my money
back into my account now!
The race is over.
The race is stilL on, gentiemen.
Like any good race...
...it never quite goes
how you anticipate.
STACEY:
ALl ciub members...
...you have exactly 60 seconds
to place all bets for the red scanner.
You know what?
Fuck you and fuck your bet!
The kid's collar is broken and
he could turn us all in right now!
STACEY: Five runners down,
three freerunners left.
Remember, whoever scans first
at the red scanner Lives.
For everyone eLse: kaboom!
[CELL PHONE RiNGS]
-What do you want?
-Mr. Reese.
Before you fly away
to Never Never Land...
...with a bag of my money,
I have one more mission for you.
The fuck you going on about?
Track down as many
degenerate freerunners...
...from your decrepit
little gym as you can.
And hunt that little fucker
Ryan down.
Fucking wanker.
TURK:
This is for Freebo!
For West.
Aah! And for me!
[LAUGHS]
My man's number one!
RYAN:
Nice, Turk.
The fuck? Run, Turk. Run.
-Freebo didn't deserve this.
-None of us do.
I disabied my collar from
his GPS and his detonator.
TURK:
What? How?
GERMAN: Shut him up, Mr. Frank.
FRANK: you think I'm not listening?
You say one more word, Ryan,
and Turk dies right now.
Turk, you win the race...
...you're a free man and a millionaire.
What happens to Ryan?
Ryan. He wants to be a dead man.
You still have a chance,
my friend. You decide now.
Good luck, man.
FRANK:
Oh, Ryan...
...where did you meet
such a beautifui girl?
I just-- l just can't get
her image out of my head.
-Just keep talking, asshole.
-Oh, i wiil.
Because l've got years
to talk and talk.
You, my friend,
you have minutes to live.
RYAN: l'm gonna spend every minute
I got coming after you.
Okay, now iisten up.
Put it out there.
At the diner, the gym,
whatever it takes.
Tell the boys I'm giving 1 00 K...
...for the head of Ryan Carter.
Text, send an announcement...
...use a fucking buLlhorn
if you have to. l don't give a shit.
Just find him.
Well, telL them to use
a fucking mask. Now, move.
Assassins? What the fuck,
Mr. Frank?
Ryan is my runner!
What the fuck is going on?
JERSEY: Stop that Ryan! KiLl that
son of a bitch right now!
TEXAS: Stop that boy!
He's going to the police! KiLl him!
RUSSlAN: You can't kill him. He's
my runner. AlL my money is on him!
MAN:
No! I just had it waxed!
TEXAS:
Get that boy!
That kid talks, i'm kilLing him...
...l'm killing his family and anyone
he's ever talked to in his life!
[BONE BREAKS
AND MAN SCREAMS]
TEXAS: Oh, my God, he's--
-Out of the green zone.
-Motherfucker!
STACEY: Ryan is out...
...of the green zone but there's
nothing Mr. Frank can do about it.
TEXAS: Now Turk's leaving
the green zone too?
-Fuck you doing, Turk?
-He's losing your bet, asshole.
STACEY:
Turk has left the green zone too.
He has onLy five minutes
to get back.
Chelsea! Chelsea!
Ryan! Thank God.
-Where's MyLes?
-Cyber cafe.
The coliar?
We need to go to the cops.
Get a bomb expert. Someone that--
We're fugitives. By the time
they figure it out, it'li be too late.
I don't know. l gotta
find something on him.
Some kind of leverage.
But we gotta go.
-Okay. Okay.
-We gotta go, okay?
[CHELSEA SCREAMING]
REESE:
Come with me or we tear her apart.
RYAN: No, don't hurt her!
No, stop! Let her go!
I'm sorry it's gotta be like this.
Come on, you gotta come with me.
TURK:
Hello, Reese.
[COLLAR BEEPING]
RYAN: Turk!
TURK: You'd have done it for me!
Turk risks everything...
...by leaving the GPS route
to save his friend Ryan.
-Fucking God!
-What a guy.
A dead guy.
CHELSEA: Ryan, don't even think
about it. No way l'm doing this.
RYAN: No way back.
-But l'm not a freerunner.
RYAN:
You are now.
[CHELSEA SCREAMING]
ALL:
Oh... HoLy shit.
Holy shit.
REESE:
I've got you now, you littLe shit!
RYAN: Chelsea, run!
CHELSEA: Aah!
REESE:
Oh, you wanna play? Let's piay.
CHELSEA:
Officer! Officer!
Offic--
JACQUE:
Chelsea, right?
[CHELSEA SCREAMS]
REESE:
Free-run your way out of this!
RYAN: i always do, asshole.
-Oh!
-Ryan!
-i got you now, you son of a bitch.
How does it feel? Huh?
-Ryan.
-Who is he?!
Look, they cali him Mr. Frank.
He's at the tower.
He's at the tower at the center,
that's all i know.
And the collar, how do i stop it?
How do l fucking stop it?
I don't know.
He's too rich, he's too powerfuL.
There's aiways tomorrow, kid.
But not for me. l'm dead anyway.
Don't do it. Reese!
[BODY THUDS]
If he can kili that guy,
he can get to your police.
Unbeiievabie.
Un-be-fucking-believable.
I officially withdraw my bet.
I withdraw my bet as weLl.
I withdraw Mr. Frank's
cLub membership.
Membership? l'm gonna
withdraw his fucking heart!
-i second that.
-Third it.
Wait a minute. Mr. Obashi--
-Never mention names, Mr. Frank.
-Yes, yes. Of course.
-This is a fucking scam!
RUSSiAN: A scam?
Come on. His bet on Finch
is the same exact amount of money...
...that he took from us
to enter this fakakta race.
Do you know what that means?
Fixes the race, takes our money,
gets us thrown in jail. Then "poof"...
...he disappears with the proceeds.
Right, Frankie boy?
If you're fixing this race...
-Just wait, wait a minute!
-...I wilL fix you.
You wanted a game. i gave you one.
Better than anything you cretins
could ever come up with.
And now you're nervous,
you're worried. What's the matter?
Too much excitement
for your weak tickers?
Watch yourself, Mr. Frank.
Chelsea. Chelsea. Chelsea!
[CAMERA BEEPiNG]
RYAN:
Shit.
TEXAS:
Oh, those guys with the masks again?
They ain't gonna do piss.
TERENCE:
Total degenerate.
You cunt and a half!
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
Finch. Finch?
[WRiST DEVICE BEEPiNG]
-Finch.
-What do you want?
The race is yours to win.
How do l know you're not gonna blow
me up as soon as I win your game?
Because I wilL fucking
blow you up now if you don't.
[SIGHS]
[CAMERA BEEPiNG]
-Nice colLar.
-Hoiy shit, dude! What happened?
-Where's Chelsea? She here?
-She's not with you?
-No, she went looking for the cops.
-All right, I'll caLl her.
What did you find?
The mother lode, dude.
Who is he?
First, that logo belongs to
a company caLled iFR industries.
Its CEO is named ian F. Ricks.
-"F" for Frank.
-Yeah.
Chelse, it's Myles. Ryan's
here at cyber. Call me back.
Dude, these guys are linked to
top internationaL weapons engineers.
They got a super satellite spy system.
He's a conspiracy theorist's
wet dream.
Tell me he's got an office
at tower center.
Yeah, top floor.
Dude's a bLock away.
And the collar?
[SIGHS]
Then l'm dead.
DEDEE:
Smile.
[CAMERA CLlCKS]
Why don't you go film yourself?
Oh, i do, sexy.
Every night at 8, i turn
this camera right around on me.
Gothchyck.com. "Chyck" with a Y.
That's it.
Gothchyck.com is it?
Yeah. Can you hack into
this wrist-phone thing?
Not without accessing
the sateilite computer mainframe.
It's a block away.
Wha--? Wait.
I gotta pack my computer!
FRANK:
Look at that ass, Jacque.
-You're the guy--
-i'm the guy from the watch.
Call me Mr. Frank.
And you're Chelsea...
...the one Ryan's willing to
fly through city streets for.
And i can see why. You're beautiful.
Where's Ryan?
I'm afraid he's no longer
with us, sweetheart.
I don't beiieve you.
If you really wanna see the world...
...you're with the right man now.
Seeing the worid with you
would turn the worLd into shit!
[CHELSEA GASPS]
Ha, ha, ha.
You got a nasty wit about you.
It's okay. I reaLly iike that.
DEDEE: Hey, you ever check out
gothchyck.com? it's my website.
Got my camera on me ail night.
Or maybe you're just too busy
playing with your radio.
MYLES:
That's it, man. Mainframe.
Oh, we turn the cameras
around on them. i get it.
But dude, it's so locked.
How do we get in?
RYAN: We gotta get up to get down.
Come on, let's go.
[WHiSPERiNG]
Hey, hey. This is it. This is it.
We're gonna go through on three.
One, two--
[ALARM BLARING]
COMPUTER:
Security alert.
Are you sure Ryan's not alive?
Jacque, get the girl.
COMPUTER: Security alert.
Control room. Door lock initiated.
Guess counting's not your thing.
-Get the door!
-Shit.
COMPUTER:
Control room. Door lock initiated.
[YELLiNG]
RYAN:
Oh, shit.
[RYAN SCREAMS]
Ryan! Help!
COMPUTER:
Door lock initiated.
Security alert. Control room.
My kid's tree house is better secured
than your fucking buiiding.
You piece of shit!
Gentlemen, your worry is all part...
...of the excitement of the game,
part of the pLaying field.
-i'm coming for you!
-You absolute piece of rubbish.
I'm out of here, boys and girls.
Fuck off and die.
We wiil see you very, very soon!
I'm coming. i'm fucking coming!
-You're dead!
-You're so fucking dead.
Mr. Frank, is everything okay?
COMPUTER: Security alert.
-How's it coming?
MYLES:
Thirty seconds.
We'll be downloading everything off
your wrist and sending it worldwide.
-All right, who am i sending it to?
-Everyone.
[COMPUTER BEEPiNG]
ALl right, you're on.
My name is Ryan Carter.
Today, a man named
Ian Frank Ricks...
...killed six innocent men.
ELVIS: Mom.
-Kid!
No!
COP: Shit.
-Hoiy shit.
They were my friends.
AGENT 1 : Are you tracking this?
AGENT 2: I'm on it.
He kilLed them for the sake
of a multimiilion-dollar...
...gambling ring run by the sick...
...twisted individual billionaires
you see here.
-Shit.
I hate billionaires.
I'm here to tell them aLl:
Game over.
-Way to go, guys.
-Mr. Frank, if I were you...
...l'd start running.
[MACHiNES POWERlNG DOWN]
-Did we get through?
-i think we did.
COMPUTER:
Door locks disabled in 60 seconds.
[CELL PHONE RiNGS]
MYLES: it's Chelsea!
RYAN: Give it to me.
Say hello, CheLsea.
RYAN: Chelsea.
CHELSEA: No.
Now say goodbye, Chelsea.
Hello, Ryan. Can you see me?
I've never used this phone before.
I don't quite know where to hold it.
Where is she?
Sadly, you've got
about five minutes to Live.
Where is she?!
And since i've been forced
to do some immediate traveling...
...regrettably, i won't be able to
say goodbye in person.
But Lucky me.
I found myseLf a lovely
traveling companion.
Chelsea.
Goodbye, Ryan.
Oh, and by the way, good game.
No!
MYLES:
FamiLy plan.
GPS. Come on, come on.
come on.
There they are!
We get GPS on the family plan.
They're going to the bridge.
To the last scanner! Go, Ryan.
COMPUTER:
Door locks now disabLed.
Go, go, go!
-You wanna go? Come on.
GUARD 1 : You take him.
-i'li go after the other one.
MYLES: Ow.
GUARD 1 :
Stop! Hey! Get back here!
GUARD 2:
Hey, hey, hey! Stop!
Hey.
MAN: lt's got a busted headlight,
but this baby really cooks.
RYAN: Sorry. it's an emergency.
MAN: Hey, hey!
Get off my bike. That's my bike!
Get off my--
[POLlCE SiREN WAiLlNG]
FINCH:
Been waiting for you, asshole.
At this scanner, second pLace
is a dead man!
RYAN: Finch! Are you crazy?
They're gonna kiil you anyway!
[PANTlNG]
FINCH: It's not about the colLar,
it's not about dickface!
-This is between me and you!
RYAN: it's not a race, man!
FINCH:
I'll always be the winner, Ryan!
Mr. Frank! i'm not
playing your game anymore.
You're the fucking ioser!
-i quit!
-You fucking idiot.
[BEEP]
Oh, for fuck's sake!
[COLLAR BEEPING,
THEN FINCH SCREAMING]
[EXPLOSiON]
We'll be in City IsLand soon.
And, my truffle, we'lL take
you wherever you wanna go.
You'll have to kill me first.
Oh.
Oh, okay.
[COLLAR BEEPING]
[BEEPlNG STOPS]
[LAUGHlNG]
Ah....
God, I love that face.
[RYAN GRUNTiNG]
[GRUNTiNG]
FRANK: Hey, what are they serving
on the flight this evening?
CAPTAIN:
Pork loin, sir.
-Pork ioin-- Fuck, what are you--?
CHELSEA: Ah!
Bitch. What are you,
fucking stupid? Eh?
Fucking move over there.
Do you wanna get fucking shot?
[LAUGHS]
Ryan!
You stay there. Stay there.
[GUNSHOTS]
CHELSEA:
No! No!
FRANK:
Come here.
Hold it, Ryan. Hold on.
Recognize the collar
she's wearing, yeah?
Now look at your timer.
You got about 30 seconds
to live.
And so does she unless you
do exactly as I say.
-What is it?
-A deal so you don't blow us aLl up.
In this briefcase there's $1 miilion.
Now, i'm a man of my word.
You jump off the boat,
I'll reiease the collar.
You keep the money,
I'll keep the girl.
[FRANK CHUCKLES]
You got about 20 seconds.
Eighteen, 1 7--
-i'li do it!
-Ryan!
Good boy. Ha-ha-ha.
Good decision for both of you.
CHELSEA:
Ryan, no.
-Love bites, doesn't it?
-it sure does.
Aah! Fuck!
[FRANK GROANS]
[BEEP]
RYAN:
Enjoy the headache, asshole!
[COLLAR BEEPING]
[LAUGHlNG]
RYAN:
Decks, Freebo...
...Mitch, West...
...Finch, Turk, Kid Elvis.
They were my friends.
They were freerunners.
And if they don't allow
free-running in heaven, well...
...these guys wilL find a way.
As for me and Chelsea...
...we couldn't beLieve there was a
million bucks in Mr. Frank's briefcase.
Got Gramps back to the ocean.
StiLl cranky,
but you gotta Love the guy.
As for CheLse, she just keeps
getting more and more beautifuL.
Me? l'm good.
I'm just trying to figure out
how a guy free-runs out here.
Um-- A warm welcome
for our unexpected guests...
...the Metro Police Department!
COP: Let's go, honey.
STACEY: Hands off.
COP:
We're going downtown.
STACEY:
Hey, hey! Watch the stick, buddy!
COP:
Let's go.
STACEY: Fuck off! Fuck off!
COP: Take this downtown.
Just put the laptop there.
Terence, which one of your private
islands are you currently residing at?
-What month is it?
-January.
Then the January island.
Twelve private islands,
one for each month of the year.
Don't you get lonely?
Not really.