¶ By the light ¶
¶ Of the silvery moon ¶
¶ I want to spoon ¶
¶ To my honey, I'll croon ¶
¶ Love's tune... ¶
¶ Honey moon ¶
¶ Keep a-shinin' in June ¶
¶ Your silvery beams ¶
¶ Will bring love's dreams ¶
¶ We'll be cuddling soon ¶
¶ By the silvery moon ¶
Get her out of my house!
Elizabeth!
I said get out!
Ohh!
You don't give the orders
in this house.
I do.
Get out.
We're done here.
You promised me,
not in the house.
Get out of my room.
Oh...
you poor child.
You know, we... we could leave,
if you want to.
We'd just pack all our things.
Where would we go?
Oh...
Did you see the ghosts?
No, that's just the storm.
It's time for sleeping,
my angels.
No, I can't go to sleep.
I'm afraid of the storm.
You're safe inside, darling.
Mommy, what happened
to your lip?
Are you hurt?
I'm all right, sweet pea.
It's just an accident.
Why don't you kiss it
and make it better?
Mother, you need to be
more careful.
I will, Amanda.
Now it's time for bed.
Good night.
Good night. Heh.
Sean?
Are you all right?
Sean, dear, what's the matter?
Is it the storm?
Let's go to bed.
Auntie May?
Why are you not in bed?
Oh, God.
Uhh!
¶ I can't ¶
¶ Seem to shake ¶
¶ This feeling ¶
¶ Can't help thinking no one ¶
¶ Really likes me... ¶
You know what? I think I was killed.
You know that?
What are you talking about?
In my last life. There was...
I'm reading about this guy here.
He smoked this crazy shit.
Now he remembers
his past life and everything,
even speaks the language.
Okay.
Come on, man. You ever
think about that? Come on,
like, what you were before,
what you might come back as?
Like... I don't know...
a ballerina or something?
I probably was,
but now I'm a very bad dancer.
- I know that.
- Ha ha!
I think about that shit
every day.
Yeah, well, see, I have a life.
I mean, look at this guy,
though, man.
That explains a lot.
- Ha ha!
- Yeah, it does.
Hey, did...
Well, look, I find it... it's just
fascinating shit to me.
You okay?
Yeah.
Boy,
this is a quiet bunch.
Didn't you all have some fun?
Yeah, it was a great resort.
What brought you
out this way?
I'm a doctor.
We were part of the convention
at the resort.
Cool. I'm actually going into
my second year at med school.
Good luck to you.
Tough road ahead.
You know,
they keep telling me that.
Hey, he's my kid brother.
He's not gonna sweat it.
We came to invigorate
our marriage.
Didn't we, honey?
Yeah.
All right, last stop, people.
You want anything?
Coffee.
Sex would be nice...
once in a while.
God.
Tornado-like winds...
are ripping through
the Midwest,
leaving behind death
and destruction.
- Rescue crews have...
- Hey, you want a cold one?
- splintered houses...
- No, I'm good.
and smashed cars.
Fires burning from...
Keeping it healthy, huh?
airports are
expecting delays.
- What have we got here?
- Authorities are calling this
the deadliest storm
to hit the area...
- Barbecue.
- in literally 100 years.
- Stay tuned for more updates.
- Is that all?
Other than your name, yeah.
I have a boyfriend.
Look, I wasn't asking you out.
I was just trying
to be friendly.
It's Courtney.
It's a pretty name.
- Together?
- Uh-huh, yeah.
Why, you got a real natural look
over there.
Bonita.
$17.20, please.
Okay.
I got it, bro.
Thank you.
Hurry up, boys,
before they, uh...
I could imagine
waking up to her every day.
kicking your ass every day.
Leave us behind.
Yeah, I hear you.
- It's good to dream.
- Yeah, I agree. Thank you.
See you.
It's good meeting you.
Take care.
After you, Romeo.
Hello.
- Boys will be boys.
- Oh, yeah.
Can I have a pack
of those, too, please?
Sure.
- Anything else?
- Uh...
I'm Bill.
Courtney.
Ahh.
So, what does your wife
say about all of this?
She doesn't say a thing.
Here. You, uh, give me a call.
I'll show you Chicago.
"Bill McCormick...
corporate lawyer".
I hate big cities...
almost as much
as cheating husbands.
Heh.
You like me.
Heh. Get out of here.
You know how I can tell?
Come here.
You didn't charge me.
Forget it. Ha ha ha!
Have fun in the...
your life in the gas station.
Asshole.
Where's my coffee?
What?
Oh, they didn't have any.
They didn't have any coffee?
Nope.
Is there any girl in the world
that you wouldn't
want to sleep with?
You knew what I was like
before we got married.
Whoa!
Thank you, sir.
Name is Jack. You okay?
Yeah.
I think he might be dead.
- Aren't you a doctor?
- I'm a med student.
You're a med student?
You can't tell the difference
if someone's alive or dead?
He's dead.
Anybody else hurt?
What?
That's... that's it.
You're all lucky to be alive.
Hardly call this lucky.
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
- I'm gonna... I'm okay.
- You hit your head.
- Can you come look at this?
- I'm all right.
Oh, my God. We need
to get him to a hospital.
Not gonna happen.
Not in this weather.
Hospital is two hours away.
Just nothing a good shot
of whiskey won't cure.
What about going back
to the gas station?
My house is just up the road.
Let's go.
- Oh.
- Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's all right, boys.
Just a head rush.
Goddamn phone.
No, those phones don't work
out here, son. Let's go.
- Come on, Adam.
- What about the driver?
We can't just...
can't just leave him here.
I'll make a call when we
get back to my house.
Can't help him now.
Let's go.
The storm is coming soon.
We're lucky you came along.
Thank you.
Jack, I need a washcloth,
rubbing alcohol,
any bandages and an ice pack,
and let's get the room
ready for him.
- Straight ahead.
- Thanks.
- A little help, guys.
- Sure, sure. What do you need?
Why don't you sit on a chair
like a normal person?
Show some respect.
Would you look at me? Look.
I'm covered
in your fruit punch,
your Kool-Aid,
whatever you drank.
Yeah, warm and sticky,
just like I like 'em.
You are the most
disgusting man in the world,
and I am married to you.
Yeah, well, I tell you...
You used to be nice to me.
Yeah, before you died inside.
Well, what do we have here?
Don't touch that.
Huh?
It's very valuable.
A family heirloom. Very sharp.
What are you,
a bear hunter?
Fuck you. I know how
to handle a knife, Tonto. Hmm?
I bet you do, too.
Oh. Look at this handsome devil.
Very auspicious.
Uh, family relative?
All right, fuck you.
I'm just being cordial.
May I have your phone, please?
Will you show me
where your phone is, please?
I don't have one.
What do you mean, you don't
have one? Where's your phone?
Where's your phone?
That's why we came here.
Now, would you have preferred
to have been left outside?
I would prefer to be back
at the gas station.
You wouldn't have made it.
How... how...
That's nothing you can know.
What, do you have
all the answers?
I have one answer.
You're stuck here now.
Stuck? And you look
pretty thrilled about...
I'm onto you, Jack.
I'm sorry. He has a head injury,
which is making him...
- Shut the fuck up.
- an asshole.
Shut up!
Listen, you think I don't know?
I think you had a hand...
in having that girl
in the middle of the road.
I think you're gonna eat us all,
one by one.
- Bill!
- I'm serious!
Look at him.
Bill.
I'm sorry.
He's a little disoriented.
He needs a pill.
Take your pill, sweetheart.
You think that any of us
are gonna make it through
the night? I don't think so.
I can feel it in my bones.
Do you guys have anything
to drink around here?
My liquor cabinet.
Help yourselves.
Oh, thank you very much.
I'm going to get some firewood
from the barn.
Could you guys get us
something to drink, please,
some whiskeys?
Cheers to that.
Come on.
Let's go upstairs.
It's kind of creepy
in here, man.
I know.
Hey, look what you found.
How is it?
Okay. Like that, huh?
Ohh.
Maybe this will be better.
What do you think?
Mm.
Mm-hmm.
You remember how Mom used to say
there were no accidents?
Yeah.
To Mom.
Okay. I'm gonna get this
up to our guy.
Mm-hmm. I'll be here.
There you go.
Thank you.
Bring the whole bottle.
You hear that?
Did you hear that?
What, the wind?
No, no, no, it sounded like
girls screaming in the...
Okay, you're only
doing water for now.
No, listen.
The curtains keep moving.
Even though the window's closed,
the wind keeps blowing
right through the wall.
Bill, it's okay.
You're just
a little bit delirious.
You need to relax.
No, I don't...
You can't relax with Jack here.
This... it's the whole place.
We have to get out of here.
Jack and the house, everything.
The man is trying to help.
No. No, he's not.
You... the longer we stay,
the more in danger we are.
Now, I want you to help me
out of here right now.
Bill, we're all gonna be fine,
all right?
Please don't leave.
Just stay here.
Just a little while. Please?
Okay.
Bill, I know
I'm just a med student,
but you gotta relax.
You gotta just
get some rest, okay?
Look, we're gonna stay with you
till you calm down.
Hey. Hey, Jack.
You got a nice place here, man.
Thanks.
Uh, excuse me, Jack.
Do you have a bathroom
I can use to clean up
a little bit?
Sure. One minute.
I got some dry things here,
if you want.
Um...
I got...
I got a shirt.
Okay, thank you.
Cool.
Okay, right this way.
Oh!
She did it. She did it.
All right. Okay.
Jack, do you happen to have
any food or anything over there?
Venison.
Help yourself.
You hunt, Jack?
Mm-hmm.
Hey, Jack, how far is
that gas station from here?
About four miles.
You mind if I borrow
your truck, go back,
see if their phones work?
No point.
Roads were closed earlier.
I know, but I...
I gotta try.
Not a good idea.
There's already one dead body.
You're much safer here.
Yeah, he might be right, Adam.
Look, if it's
too crazy out there,
I'll turn around
and come right back.
Oh, that's a stubborn one, eh?
Yeah, he is.
Well, I'm starving. Do you
think you could you pick up
some food or some snacks
or something?
Well...
don't say I didn't warn you.
Okay.
Key is by the front door.
Storm is approaching.
Shit.
Haven't we met before?
Oh, the friendly guy.
You need a ride?
What's the, uh...
what's the problem?
I knew I should've
filled up this morning.
I was practically on empty.
Don't you work at a gas station?
Funny.
That's like a plumber
who doesn't turn the water off
when he's fixing a leak or...
I don't know... a dentist...
who eats a steady diet of
candy bars, but never flosses.
You know, you'd think...
You'd think they'd just know.
Ha ha!
Okay, here's a better question.
If you're out of gas, why are you
looking under the hood?
This kind of reminds me...
You know that ad
with the hot chick
on the side of the road?
They got grease
on her cleavage.
She's posing all sexy
next to her car.
Hood's up,
smoke's just billowing out,
and she's waiting
for some phantom cowboy
to ride her off
into the sunset.
I don't watch TV.
Well, it's not so much
a fantasy, is it?
What's your name again?
- Adam.
Adam, better hop back
in your pickup and scram
before that handsome cowboy
sees you and keeps on going.
Thanks a bunch, buddy.
Okay, well...
I'm not the stud cowboy
with the white horse,
but I am a nice guy
who wants to help you.
You don't have to.
It's okay. I'll be fine.
Yeah? Well, considering you're
looking for spare gas
in the engine, something
tells me you might not be.
No, really. I got it handled.
Come on. It is gonna pour
any second now.
Your only option is to get in
this vomit-green,
cozy, dry pickup.
I'll take you back
to the gas station.
Good point.
That's a good choice.
Here. I'll get it.
- Thank you.
- You got it.
It's a good color, right?
Cool car.
Yeah.
So, um, what's your story?
Married?
Have any kids?
Divorced. No little Lipskis
running around.
- Free man.
- Yeah.
Only way to fly.
So, I guess you're single.
Yeah.
Just me. Well, my brother Adam.
See, our mom, she...
she just passed.
You know, we thought
we'd get away...
forget our troubles,
be brothers again.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
What was your mom like?
Mom?
Yeah, she was...
she was amazing.
She was, uh, incredible,
you know?
Smart and warm,
and everybody loved her.
A lot like Adam, you know?
And what about you?
Yeah, I...
I took after Pops.
So, uh,
where's Prince Charming?
- What?
- Your boyfriend.
He's not worthy of discussion,
believe me.
Hey, that's the road
to the Food Mart!
Okay.
Well, I guess I'll be
a gentleman and take you home.
Don't think we're gonna make it.
It's a good 15 miles from here.
If there are trees down here,
there are trees down everywhere.
All right, looks like
you're coming with me.
Yeah, you know,
it's been about a...
about a month since we
lost her, and, you know...
I'm so sorry
for that, Isaac.
- Here's to life.
- Cheers. Cheers.
Hey. No way.
Hey, guys. Uh...
this is Courtney.
Hi.
- Hello, Courtney.
- Hi. How are you?
I'm Jack.
You work at the Food Mart.
Yes.
Thank you for letting me
into your home.
Oh, well... home,
sweet home.
Hey, Courtney, you, uh...
you need some clean clothes?
What?
I got clean clothes
if you need 'em.
No, thanks. I'll survive.
Okay.
I think I have something more...
suitable for you upstairs.
Follow me.
What's this?
Ahh.
It's a little dated,
but it's clean.
It's beautiful.
Better.
No.
Help me.
Please, please, help me.
There's bad people here.
They're trying to hurt...
What's wrong?
What's going on?
I'm so glad you're here.
I just need your help.
We're in danger.
We've got to get out of here.
What are you talking about?
You have to help me, please.
I want you to stay
with me, please.
- Please stay. Just...
- Let me go.
No, no, just wait.
Let me explain.
Let me explain, please.
- We're in danger.
- Okay.
Just stay here with me,
please. Please.
I'll go get you some help.
Just let me go.
Just let me go. I'm gonna
get you some help, okay?
Okay. Don't... don't...
it matters who... who...
- Wait. Wait!
- You're hurting me! Let me go!
- Wait! Wait!
- You're hurting me!
Hey.
- Hey, what's up?
- Where's Lipski?
I don't know. Have you seen Jack,
though? I need some food.
Listen, something's wrong
with McCormick. I don't know.
We've got to find Jack.
I'm gonna get the doc.
What are you talking about?
Hey, slow down.
What do you mean?
Aah!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Bill?
Bill? Bill!
Why isn't he answering me?!
- What happened?
- Hey, what's going on here?
- He was fine when I left him.
- Oh, my God. I think he's dead!
I knew we should've
taken him to the hospital.
We did
everything we could.
He seemed okay.
What? What?! What?!
There are some marks around his neck,
but I don't remember...
- if they were there before.
- What do you mean, marks?
What do you mean,
you don't remember?
I don't know
how I could've missed them,
- but I'm not sure.
- What kind of fucking doctor
- are you?
- Try to fucking remember!
Were the marks there
before or not?
What?!
I'm sorry.
I just can't remember.
You did this.
You screwed up.
You fucking murderer.
Fucking liar!
Get off me! Get off me!
Let me go!
Get your hands off me!
Everyone just calm down.
I'm sorry.
I just don't remember.
Yes, you are sorry.
Who was the last person
to see him alive?
I saw him about
ten minutes ago.
What were you doing
in his room?
I heard him calling for help.
Then I went to get you.
Yeah, I told Courtney
to go look for you.
And I couldn't find her.
So, where were you?
What? Me?
What, are you accusing me
of killing my own husband?
She was the last person
in his room.
She was going for help, okay?
Look, there were...
there were no red marks
on his neck. I'm positive.
You're not helping.
You're just scaring everyone.
Well, maybe we should be scared.
He's right. You know what?
You may think
maybe I'm crazy, but...
I think we should get outta here
right now, all of us.
Courtney, come with us.
Yeah, come on. You, too.
But either way, I'm out of here.
Isaac! Come on.
We gotta wait for Courtney!
Yeah, right.
Hey, God damn it, please,
just give her a minute.
Okay, one minute, Adam.
If she's not here,
we're leaving without her, okay?
Now screw your fucking head on!
I got nothing here.
Help me out.
Open her up.
What have we got?
What the hell?
- Come here.
- What is it?
Oh, great.
Fucking great.
God damn it. God damn it!
I guess we're staying, huh?
Jack.
Yeah.
Why'd you fuck up
the truck, Jack?
Hmm? Fuck up the truck?
Yeah, all the wires are cut.
Who do you think
you're accusing?
Who else would it be, Jack?
Oh, I'm gonna trash
my own truck?
Yeah, maybe so. It'd be
a good way to trap us, wouldn't it?
You were the last one
to use the truck.
- That's bullshit.
- That's fuckin' bullshit,
and you know it.
You got a flashlight, Jack?
Find it your damn self.
Some more lights wouldn't hurt.
Ah, shit!
What?
What happened? Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. It's just
a nail or something here.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, shit.
Let me see.
It needs to get cleaned.
I'll get some towels.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
You are one clumsy
son of a bitch.
Yeah, I am.
- Let me see.
- What do you think?
- You'll survive.
- Here.
Let me clean this.
- Uhh!
- Does it hurt?
Yeah, a little bit.
Poor thing. You're such a girl.
Yeah, I know.
I'll get that. Fine?
- Thank you.
- Okay.
We're not just gonna
let Jack slide on this, are we?
You kidding me? No, we're not.
We should take care
of McCormick's body
before rigor sets in.
Can you give me a hand now?
Come on.
Okay, watch your back, eh?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
I'm a baby, but not that bad.
Doc...
look, right before
Brooklyn screamed,
no one knew where Jack was.
And you saw he was...
he was the last to get here.
I don't know.
I just can't be sure...
this wasn't
because of the accident.
I wanted to get him
to the hospital.
Don't you think
you would've seen the marks?
I'm telling you,
I didn't see a thing on the guy.
I honestly can't be sure.
I just started
my practice again.
Yeah?
What? What...
what happened?
I had a problem
with painkillers.
It clouded my judgment.
I missed things.
You second-guess yourself a lot,
don't you?
I'm just
not as confident as I was.
Well, you didn't
misdiagnose this.
I'm telling you,
I looked closely.
There were
no red marks on his neck.
It was just a head wound.
I don't...
I don't know.
My mom used to say that...
death was the end
of one chapter
and the beginning of another.
Mm-hmm.
You were close to your mother.
Yeah.
You were her favorite.
You've been talking
to Isaac, I see.
No. I just knew it.
How long have you had
this house?
Feels like...
forever.
We're done here.
Aah!
We interrupt this broadcast...
to bring you some breaking news.
We're under a tornado watch
for the following counties...
Scott, Bernette, Polk,
Marshall and Red Lake.
There is severe wind,
lightning and rain.
Several inches have fallen
in just a few hours tonight.
Travel is near impossible
due to downed trees
and flooded roads.
Officials told Newswatch
that five people have perished
in the storm.
The aforementioned counties
have been declared
a weather emergency.
How are you?
Terrifying nightmares.
This is the worst storm
to hit this area in a 100 years.
Regardless,
I need to get some sleep.
Yeah, I could use
some rest, too.
I'll show you to your rooms.
You two can share a room, yes?
Uh... yeah.
You'll sleep on the floor.
Guess I'll be down here,
checking this thing.
Okay, I'll flip you for it.
- ¶ Of the silvery moon ¶
- If you want, brother.
- Call it.
- Heads.
- ¶ I want to spoon ¶
- Tails.
Sleep tight, brother.
¶ To my honey, I'll croon ¶
- ¶ Love's tune ¶
- Hey, you okay?
- ¶ Honey moon ¶
- It's gonna be okay.
Are you asleep?
Nope.
Don't get any ideas...
but maybe you could
sleep up here with me?
I'm a little frightened.
Uh, yeah. You know...
since you asked me nicely.
I don't mean to scare you,
but I think I saw something
earlier in the mirror.
You saw something?
Actually, it was a little boy.
He was staring at me
in the mirror.
Never mind.
You don't believe me.
No. No, no, no.
I, uh...
I've actually been
seeing things, too.
Like what?
I saw the woman in the robe
that McCormick talked about.
Do you believe in ghosts?
I don't know.
I mean...
I've never really
thought about it.
You think this has
anything to do with...
What, McCormick's death?
No. No. I don't think so.
Hey, don't be scared.
Oh, it's you.
Hey, you've been busy, huh?
I guess you're good
with that ax, right, Jack?
Wow, this weather's
not so good, huh?
Hey, Jack.
May I ask you a question?
Living out here by yourself
in the middle of nowhere,
you ever get lonely,
freaked out?
Mm-mm.
I was meant to be here.
Yeah.
I just know I couldn't do it.
That's all.
I sense you feel alone.
Well, you know, I guess.
I guess we all do
sometimes, right?
You know...
You know, even as a kid,
you know, my brother Adam,
he was kind of hard
to get to know sometimes.
I mean, I love him.
Heh. Sometimes he thinks
he knows everything. That's all.
And you're the oldest.
Uh-huh.
He was your mother's favorite.
She loved me, man.
She loved me.
He got the grades,
got the looks,
scholarships.
You know how it is.
Jack...
you can kind of
sense things, right?
Mm-hmm.
Cool.
How you doing?
Hey, let me help you.
So, when you were a kid,
even back then,
you could... you could
feel things, sense things,
or what?
Hey. Wait.
Oh, my God.
No, no, no!
Okay.
Whew! Oh, my God.
I think we're all,
uh... on edge here.
Let's have a drink. Cheers.
Cheers.
Hey, brother, you wanna play
some cards, have a drink?
- Yeah.
- Where were you?
I woke up,
and you weren't there.
I, uh... I think...
I think I saw a little boy
kill a little girl.
What are you talking about?
Nightmares? You, too?
Yeah, join the club.
No. No, no,
it's not a nightmare.
I'm telling you, it was, like,
as real as I'm fucking
standing here right now.
It was like that.
Let me ask you...
Hang on. Slow down.
You're telling me you saw,
like, a little boy?
- Yeah.
- Dark hair, dark eyes?
Yeah.
I know. Yeah.
Hang on. Wait a second.
Like this?
Yeah, it was that.
It was that.
It was him.
Yeah, this kid right here,
and he... he killed this girl...
right here.
It was his face
I saw in the mirror.
I saw this little girl.
Okay, something is
going on in this house.
- Yeah, there... yeah, there is.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Okay, uh...
We gotta find Jack.
Okay. I'll go with you, okay?
I'm staying with you.
Yeah, it's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
Don't worry.
I'm not going in there.
Why not?
I don't think
he'd want us going in there.
Okay.
Stand guard.
Make it fast.
You okay?
Yeah.
Stay with me.
What?
Oh, my God.
"Child killer"...
You okay?
Yeah. Just please go away.
You give me a shout
if you need me.
Yeah.
Jack.
No.
What is this?
Find what you're looking for?
Isaac?
Ohh! Oh, my God!
I'm sorry. I heard you call my name.
Are you okay?
- You scared the crap out of me.
- I'm sorry.
You okay?
I don't know.
Did you find Jack?
No, not yet.
I'm gonna keep looking.
You should...
you should get some rest.
Yeah, right.
I'll see you in a minute.
Questions?
Yeah.
Who... who are these people?
A tragedy struck this house
a century ago.
Tragedy?
Have a seat.
Hello?
This is William,
the adopted boy's father.
So, what led him to kill 'em?
He was a very disturbed
little boy.
When the authorities asked him
why did he kill his family,
he... he...
he said
that he didn't remember.
He said that he didn't know
that he killed them.
When the storm came on,
he said he felt like
he was possessed...
a demon.
There was a storm this size
that night also.
How do you live
in this house, Jack?
You must get spooked.
This is my sanctuary.
Your sanctuary? Jesus.
Yes.
Why'd you keep this a secret
from us this whole time?
The time wasn't right.
Well, it's time
to tell the others.
Hmm.
100 years ago...
a little boy murdered
his entire family
in this house.
Some people say
they've seen...
the ghost of the boy
and his family.
Sometimes, when a person
dies a violent death,
their spirit can't rest.
So, it's possible
that their spirits
are living in this house.
Why didn't you tell us?
Would you have preferred
that I left you outside
while the storm was approaching?
Heh. No, I think we all agree
that you're much safer in here.
Now, it's been a long,
long day for all of us.
I'm going to get some sleep,
and I suggest you do the same.
Boo!
Ha ha ha ha!
I'm sorry
I got you into this mess.
Actually, I feel like
I should be apologizing to you.
Hmm?
Bad things seem to follow me
wherever I go.
I swear, sometimes I'm cursed
or something.
Ah, we all have trouble
in our lives.
Trust me, I'm hard to top.
When I was ten, my dad
shot my mother and himself.
Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry.
We had just moved to the U.S.
I got home from school.
The police were already there.
I spent the next eight years
going from one foster home
to another.
And the stuff I saw,
I experienced,
I can't talk about it.
So, how did you
find your way out here?
I wanted to get as far away
as I could from everything.
It's quiet out here,
you know, peaceful.
Something about it
just felt like home.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Mm-hmm.
I don't know.
Maybe it's you, but...
something about you
feels like home.
We should get some sleep.
Okay.
This couch is so uncomfortable.
I can't sleep.
Well, you've been
through a lot, you know.
It's understandable.
Hey, look, I'm...
I'm really sorry.
Are you okay?
Ohh.
I saw more of the murders.
An old lady in a wheelchair.
And the other sister,
he... he killed her.
Babe, it was just a dream.
I don't know. It...
I mean, it happened here.
It happened.
I can't take this anymore.
Look.
I found this...
in the study.
That looks exactly like Jack.
But this is so old.
Could it be his grandfather?
That's his face.
I don't know,
but I say we leave.
I say we...
What is it?
Adam, maybe someone else
is in the house.
What just happened?
Stay here.
What about you?
You get any rest?
In this place?
Not a wink.
You sure you don't want
to get some real sleep
upstairs in the bed?
i don't want to be alone.
It's okay.
I'll come with you.
I'll keep an eye on you.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Come on.
Yeah, you're gonna feel okay
when you get some sleep,
you know?
- Ohh.
- What is it?
The floor's wet or something.
No, it's not.
Blood.
- What the...
- Aah!
- Okay.
- Ohh! Oh, my God!
Okay. Hang on.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
Adam.
Somebody was in this room.
- What?
- Yeah...
Are you okay?
- It's not mine.
- What happened to you?
It's Lipski's. He's dead.
- What?
We found him in Brooklyn's room.
His throat was cut.
Okay, we're getting
the hell out of here right now.
Well, that's a good idea, Adam.
I've been ready for a while.
- Shall we? Let's go.
- Yeah.
Okay, you guys
grab whatever you need.
Let's grab some supplies
from the barn.
Okay, good idea.
Flashlight's gonna help.
If we keep heading west,
I think we'll hit the highway.
I still got nothin' on my phone.
Yeah, keep trying, brother.
What's the fuckin' purpose
of these things?
- Aah!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. What?
Hey, hey, hey. Are you okay?
- I twisted my ankle.
- Ah, shit.
What happened here?
Go. I'll catch up. Go, go.
I'm not leaving you behind.
Look, I gotta
take a look at this.
You guys go ahead,
and we'll catch up.
Okay. Make it fast,
Adam, please.
Yeah.
- Does it hurt?
- You stay with me, okay?
- Stay close.
- Okay.
This... this place
is creepy as shit, man.
You see that?
I have no idea
where we are.
Brooklyn. Brooklyn?
- Ahh!
- How does that feel?
- Let me see.
- Okay.
- Easy, easy.
- Ah, yeah.
Yeah, it's better.
Okay, let's just take it slow.
Okay.
Hey.
Thank you for staying with me.
I got you.
- Come on.
- Okay.
What was that?
Shh.
- Who is that?
- You okay?
- Whoa. Isaac?
- Yeah.
What are you doing?
Look, Brooklyn, she's gone.
- What do you mean, gone?
- What?
I was walking. I turned around.
She disappeared.
I mean literally disappeared.
I've been everywhere.
- I can't find her.
- Oh, that's perfect.
We gotta find her, bro.
- Okay?
- Okay.
I'll go this way.
Keep her safe.
- Let's meet back right here.
- Yeah.
I'll be right back.
Okay. Get back A.S.A.P., okay?
Or quicker if I scream.
Isaac?
Isaac!
Oh, it's you.
Courtney, you okay?
There is light over there.
It looks like a house.
Oh, yeah. I see it.
Hey.
- Did you find her?
- No.
We got a house
or something over here.
There's lights.
I don't know about you guys,
but I say we go get some help.
Let's go find out.
The light at the end
of the tunnel.
Yeah. Let's hope so.
Let's go see
if they have a phone.
¶ By the light ¶
¶ Of the silvery moon ¶
¶ I want to spoon ¶
¶ To my honey, I'll croon... ¶
Ah, Adam,
this is the same house.
We've gone in one big circle.
I'm telling you, guys,
we were headed west.
¶ Keep a-shinin' in June ¶
Okay, let's go.
¶ Your silvery beams ¶
¶ Will bring love's dreams... ¶
This isn't happening.
Welcome home.
¶ By the silvery moon ¶
I gotta be dreaming.
No, this isn't possible.
Sure it is.
You're not leaving.
This is your home.
It always has been,
and it always will be.
Have a seat.
I saw his throat cut.
No, I gotta be...
I gotta be dreaming, right, Jack?
I assure you,
you're not dreaming.
I have your favorite drink.
Relax. Have a seat.
No, no. I'm okay.
Okay, we're getting
out of here right now.
- And going where?
- Let's go.
- This is your home!
- You stay away from us!
This is your home!
Oh, my God. Brooklyn!
No.
Ohh.
- Isaac! Wait!
- Brooklyn.
- Be right back.
- Talk to me. Brooklyn.
¶ Swing low, sweet chariot ¶
¶ Coming for to carry me home ¶
¶ Coming for to carry me... ¶
Home.
Isaac!
What is that?
What's your name?
Uh...
Courtney, what are
you doing here?
You see the boy?
Where'd he go?
Isaac!
"McKnight, Amanda".
"Sara".
"Brooklyn".
"Lipski".
No.
No. No.
This... this isn't happening.
Courtney.
What's going on here?
You killed them.
And you buried 'em out here.
No? Then who did?
No, that's not...
That's not possible.
Huh.
It's what was meant to be.
It's happening again.
It took a century
for you to come back home.
What are you...
what are you talking about?
She has blood on her hands.
I don't understand
what you mean. What...
I don't get...
I don't understand this.
Stop filling him with your lies.
What's happening now
is bigger than all of us.
There's a grave
with my brother's name on it.
Jack, why is there
an empty grave?
The cycle must be complete.
Cycle?
The cycle of death!
Call it fate, karma,
the cycle of carnage.
What does this... what does this
have to do with me?
Destiny.
You must complete the cycle.
Sara.
Sara!
Why are you calling me that?
- Sara?
- No, stop it.
- Stop it!
Your destiny awaits you, Sara!
Why are you calling me that?
I... I don't understand!
In your last incarnation,
you were murdered by Sean,
your adopted brother.
You give me one good reason
why I don't bury you out here.
We're all family here,
my dear boy.
You're Sean, Jack.
You're the killer.
I was a servant in those times.
It was up to me to see
that destiny was fulfilled.
And now I'm here once again
to seal your fate.
Your souls belong to me.
I don't buy it.
You don't have to.
The past is set.
The past doesn't change.
The past only repeats itself.
You killed
McCormick and Lipski, and...
Shh.
Look at me. Hmm.
It's not in my nature.
You're a liar!
The truth is in you.
You're the killer,
you sick son of a bitch.
It's her birthright.
It's not for me to claim.
What's up to me...
is to reveal your fate.
Courtney, what are you
doing here?
You see the boy?
Where'd he go?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Where'd you get this?
Put the knife down, Courtney.
Courtney, I don't want
to hurt you.
You put the knife down, okay?
You're gonna give me the knife.
Please. Okay?
Okay.
Aah!
She was and still is
the killer amongst us.
I'm sorry, Adam. I'm so sorry.
The cycle ends with your death.
No.
My parents, my past...
I'm cursed. I've known it.
You can't escape it.
Who the hell are you?
Well, I've been called
by many names
throughout the centuries.
I prefer to be called...
the agent of destiny.
I have to end it...
now.
No. No, Courtney, Courtney...
drop the knife.
Stay away!
Get back!
Wake up, baby. Baby, wake up.
- Kill him!
- Don't listen to him.
You look at me.
Look me in the eyes.
You know me.
Courtney, trust me.
Please, just... just...
listen to me.
No.
Oh, Jesus!
Ohh!
Courtney, hang on, baby.
Come on. Stay with me.
- Adam, I...
- I'm here.
I wanted to tell you that...
that I've felt alone
my whole life...
except the time
I spent with you.
Oh, baby.
No. No, no. I'm so sorry, baby.
I'm so sorry.
You're free now.
Huh.
Courtney?
Baby, hang on.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
Come on. Yes.
Hey, baby. How's it coming?
- Perfectly.
- Mmm, good.
I am starving.
Everything okay?
Sweetheart?
Hmm?
Let's celebrate our happiness.
I love you.
I love you more.
Heh.