Colony ARK monthly basis ore
I Crew: 4 men
A 187-day mission a year
I alert the storm
emergency situation.
A meteor shower.
I isolated rain of meteors.
Just a detector.
- How I did not see it?
- We're as surprised as you.
I this is not a satisfactory response
.
I Give me a damage report.
decompress the external repository.
Apparently he was hit
second escape capsule.
What the hell... Madsen?
Received, over?
Streaming inactive  I ~ ~
- telecommunications, have fallen.
I ~ 09 ~ Fault aggregate filter
- It's a good...
I emergency alarm.
All crew stations.
Johns, wake up!
We have an emergency.
Legs shake and fuck up!
Blackout in bays one and two.
Decrease power.
Here Commander Gerard Brauchman,
ARK on monthly basis.
I officially declare new Code .
Immediate evacuation of the entire crew to Earth.
I repeat: we are in a state of emergency
.
Request immediate launch of the shuttle.
Personnel evacuation to Earth.
Fault  I span three oxygen filter.
Level four and growing.
What the hell happened to
levels from one to three?
I was knock a meteor storm. Telecommunications,
fell.
Losing power.
# We reserve the power and I lost
escape capsule.
- Both solar panels are damaged.
- Can anyone stop that?
I transferred commands.
- See if you can reconnect with the base.
- Understand.
UA E ª Þ I
Translation: Reef
addic7ed.com
I can not breathe. I...?
Krauss, see aeraþia reserve.
- Johns, are you okay?
- Yes, well.
backup systems, active.
Reduction Functions.
oxygen level stabilizes.
A
meteor broke a hole through the roof span three.
- Hit and carbon monoxide filter.
- Come Johns, have to isolate that area.
- And quickly, drain poison station.
- Get welding equipment.
- Sealed airlock.
- Soon.
- I'll go.
- No, you can...
I repaired and coca,
I got it.
Good, close each of span locks
you.
Otherwise, sparking're in a chain reaction and everybody decompression
send us to hell.
Okay, now I work in a relaxed...
Doctor, I want to go
the energy cells.
Perhaps
save time by enabling backup filter pumps.
I left.
You ready, Cameron?
Done.
When I open the lock, and comes much debris
compressed carbon monoxide.
- So welded fast as you can.
- Good.
I Cameron, I hear over
They destroyed all the costumes output,
except one. It burned a little, but good.
's Too risky.
Cameron and the smallest cracks
in costume and you could be sucked into the vacuum.
Cancel the mission?
'm Airlock span three.
Gravitational activate it outside.
Is about running out of time...
S do.
Undocumented bravery.
If you look bad year.
Keep . Out now.
- Open airlock and get your transfer orders.
- Yes, sir.
Do not hang the door in bay three.
Is blocked!
I - Close it and uatã
- I should cancel?
- Will be leakage station.
- Security, keep two.
Continue the mission!
Estimate damage me.
Still keeps sleepers.
Carbon monoxide level is off the charts.
Severe impact.
Must be damaged and four bays.
So sealing is paramount.
Must close thing.
Gotta go
filtration unit and to get the hell out of there.
I see what we have here
No, I do not see anything
you're on your own.
I Where exactly is meteor
new cylinder was stuck,
between it and the filter.
Meteor's stiff.
Try it out.
Cameron, come!
I Cameron, I hear
not going anywhere.
- I need to guide the valve.
- Right underneath.
Valve should be right underneath
right.
's Damaged valve,
I covered leak.
Monoxide leak stopped,
have to go from there.
- Are on the verge of collapse.
- Cameron, get out of there, you hear?
I Cameron...
Cameron!
Cameron, I hear?
Cameron, copy?
Answer  I, Lieutenant
'm airlock span three.
Come on. And, if you can, close the hatch
span two.
- Dom 'colonel-ngroa and joked it!
- Spans four cede!
Christ,
Cameron is still there!
Put ​​your mask.
Ava!
Cameron... Where are you?
- Here.
- Did you hear?
Are you okay?
If you grasp this,
try to get out on her.
- I stood up.
- Good!
Come on! Are you okay? Thank God,
I thought I lost you.
Right, but I inhaled
monocarboxylic acid.
- Come on!
- Yes, we...
Bruce should be
to look at it.
- Got some kind of increase it.
- Come on, get out of here!
The less we leave the station
poison, the better it will be.
Okay, go!
Okay, keep gasket.
Enough to stop leakage in the cabins.
- You've given us a great show.
- Thanks.
Lieutenant, you're exposed to chemicals
, get in the shower.
Lieutenant...
Good work.
Same.
- Where are we?
- We're good.
It was a little close.
95% of the base has no power, so I
,
fix it until the backup generator,
will have to work in the dark.
- We have only 72 hours.
- Measured by the standard procedures.
92 hours to 72 hours and still launch
until rescue mission for us.
- So we must win and tigãm some time.
- What about the escape capsule?
Not an option,
there in only two.
We still have traces of gas leak.
Carbon monoxide level is abnormal.
Dom 'doctor...?
Johns.
's CO is odorless,
no color, no taste.
Neurological manifestations of poisoning include hallucinations,
disorientation, headache,
gas gangrene, vision...
- And death.
- Super, and more good news. Solutions?
'm On. Keep an eye
one another and if one of us sees another
Showing any of these symptoms,
Come live with me, understand?
Understood. I want to try and remove as much carbon monoxide
possible here
opening the filter still operational. Close the lock.
I hazard.
Sas open.
good news is that functioned.
The carbon monoxide minimal.
Bad news is that
squeezed and more energy in cells.
- If solar panels fix it?
- Costumes, and destroyed.
- Damn right we Are uaþi.
- Johns, you're the engineer.
Come with solutions,
or you can breathe in space?
Lance stops installation for drilling,
squeeze vital energy systems.
- Good, now.
- I'll go.
If the doctor could look at meteor
That one... has some kind of spores attach.
What do you mean some kind of increase?
Call of alien infection agent.
Should immediately put in quarantine.
We are not here to play games savanþii,
goal is to save our skins.
- Got it?
- I got it.
And I see that's very important.
If you start to feel dezorientaþi or abnormal in any way,
be mild and
auditory or visual hallucinations, Come to me immediately.
Scientists...
I The installation of drilling at rest.
Should reduce the power consumption.
Ava, can you come here?
You have to see this.
- You isolation?
- Yeah, come and get it concerns.
I I've never seen anything like. Kind of shaped cell structure
old,
I being reproduced in an incredible pace.
What?
I have a sample there. Running tests,
see what you find.
Here ARK monthly basis, Colonel
Brauchman, to base. Answer!
Madsen? Are you there?
You hear me?
Madsen, if you can hear me, I closed
whole mining operations.
I currently used only for emergency lights.
I Confirms please
receipt for the escape pod.
Here  U.S. monthly basis ARK Colonel
Brauchman, to base. Answer!
A was passed through three different tests,
all with identical results.
Waxed
meteor can reproduce without carbon, oxygen, hydrogen and nitrogen.
Looks like a
triggers exposure to light.
Yo, bro, if you tell them what it is,
I just entered a science fiction film.
I can multiply and produce
nutrients by themselves.
- As bacteria?
- Just that much intelligence.
Spores are dormant codes, but nobody knows how show
multiply.
Might turn total,
change, develop...
Developed what?
Who knows? But the growth rate
is absolutely extraordinary.
a hundred times faster
like any cell in the human body.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I feel a bit of nausea.
I'm going to lie down.
Good.
Easy... Take it easy.
Where am I?
The infirmary.
Why you're all here?
What happened?
- No, It's okay...
- What do I do?
- Relax, Ava...
- What is happening?
- Jesus...!
- Cover it!
Come Johns.
Now the hall.
Need to breathe...
Look at me, right?
Listen...
You gotta breathe, breathe...
Slowly but calm down, okay?
I'm here.
Ava, you listen to me now, right?
A and A. ..
You
what appears to be an extremely accelerated.
So, Ava...
I can not explain. Simply
can not be that fast.
- You can not.
- Good...
I argue that on the
What...?
Gerard
just more cautious than normal. Yes...?
I have to give the country and nationality
end, I promise.
Do not worry.
You need to rest.
Good...?
- I have to go now.
- Do not go.
Right back.
You're safe here. It's okay.
Wants to close.
Lance, should be quarantined.
I have to side at this stage THII.
The form
accelerated growth.
Without functional equipment,
I can not diagnose correctly.
- You guys have done that...?
- Oh, come on, man...
Six months pregnant in 24 hours, you let me?
Has a reaction to chemical exposure.
Must have access to treat.
Goes to isolation.
Do not risk safety stations.
You can not close, dom 'colonel.
Requires constant medical supervision.
E infection, according to the protocol enters
48 hours in isolation under surveillance.
What if he dies there?
You will have access surveillance.
But that hatch remains closed.
I Access denied.
Colonel protocol is unacceptable.
Must have access to Ava 24/7.
Colonel, can you hear me?
'm Just worried for Cameron as you.
But as commander,
are bound by regulation.
Remain in isolation.
You will have access to it when needed, just give me the news story.
Well how about now?
Well not a doctor, but according
and they have your
is already in the last quarter, when the child
organs are almost fully developed?
How to be?
Rational diagnosis is that it would be a kind of cyst.
But even so, an accelerated cancer
imitating pregnancy is exaggerated.
But if spores that have infected her
in any way?
When we were in shit
up to his neck.
Ava!
- Jesus...
- I touch!
Dies, brother...
Cameron, come on.
Ava, wake up!
Come hear me?
What the hell is all this?
Dom 'Colonel, I need light! Return
get your Bruce, illuminated here.
- What happened?
- Come out at what caused the swelling.
Got internal bleeding,
methylergometrine on the top shelf.
- Gentlemen, you must leave.
- Die if we do something!
- Is now officially in the quarantine room!
- Can not you close here!
- Reach out. Ava, let me help you.
- I never leave here.
Why do you want me  lock?
What's wrong with you?
Go on, Bruce.
I stop the bleeding.
Colonel, you do not have jurisdiction here,
I am Dr. stations.
Infirmary is yours.
Report to me when you're done.
You have to pay your me,
bastard!
Bastards!
E infection,
Now you could be and you!
And risked his life for us, so
-I thank you?
Focus on communication equipment repair,
basis will tell you what to do with it.
Until then, follow my orders!
Sure... Sure!
So right?
I'm afraid it took less
everybody claustrophobia.
Perhaps
from carbon monoxide intoxication.
"El Capitan"
closure ordered Ava and I. ..
Maybe spores that infected a
created... you some weird stuff.
And I still need to figure out what.
Heater is off by seven hours. Began to feel the thrill.
But... Back to work.
Chief engineer Bruce Johns,
ARK monthly basis.
Ava, do you?
Ava!
Ava! Ava!
- Go ahead!
- Calm down.
S stretches her bed.
- Ava, calm down.
- Hold it!
- What the hell happened to you?
- Calm down!
Johns,
we need your help!
- I was bitten!
- What the hell are you talking about?
- I was bitten...
- Okay, ready...
There was something here!
There was something here.
There's nothing here.
Yeah, well something has taken a bite out of my leg that
!
- Look!
- Bruce, listen.
You probably cut
cabinet or any shard of broken glass. There is nothing...
No, listen. There was something here.
Right there. I swear. Take a look!
Come on, forget it!
Close my room.
Let me know when you're done here.
Consulted him on it and has the symptoms of carbon monoxide poisoning
.
There was something on me.
I felt weight on his chest, right?
Thing, this creature,
feed my bosom.
Was not real. Nothing, Ava.
There's nothing here.
You understand ?
You had hallucinations.
A and A. Go to sleep again.
Need to look at the cut of Bruce. Be right back.
Bruce, come into the dining room to see your
cuts.
I know that was something here,
with me.
I know and you've seen.
Is possible for me to have given birth to something?
Not know.
If you close your eyes, it's about 25 years old
whiskey. There, God!
Bottle you cut deep enough.
M has bitten something.
Quit that good?
You do not help.
Listen,
I swear I saw something there.
You hear stuff?
- Do not believe me...
- No, you and Ava have the same symptoms.
Yeah, well... If something used
Ava to reproduce?
A creature that has no DNA.
- And I'll endeavors to enhance the mind?
- Come on, unaware that it is possible.
Only when you have the opportunity to examine the fluid
Ava will be able to determine precisely.
But until then, the most logical and rational
rash remains a fibroid.
There was nothing in that room
which to prove otherwise.
Now...
I want to go get some rest, and
That's an order.
Yes, Colonel wants to communicate again.
MA ask me, we are already in hell.
Antenna and destroyed.
What...
What the...
Shit!
Johns, working on solar panels?
We need power.
Come, come...
O...
So, to straighten them...
Come on...!
I Calibrating solar panel's EC ª
A manual like...
I manual calibration ON solar panel
Good...
Look! Restoring communications, we see
get off this rock.
I just said that Johns
antenna and destroyed.
How's, is apt debt?
I need it.
Worries me, showing signs of paranoia
. He has hallucinations.
- Bea...?
- Like crazy.
But clearly suffering from exposure to chemicals,
and I do not treat it properly.
Let alone put them
proper diagnosis.
It seems
it's just me, dom 'doctor, right?
Yet.
Not crazy...
Not crazy!
Not crazy, not
Inne...
Not crazy...!
Johns!
Johns.
Listen, Johns reach.
I want on the treadmill until
get your alcohol out of the body
and then treat yourself
carbon monoxide intoxication.
This stops now, right?
Hai, I want functional again.
Yo, be...
I knew it!
What...?
- What are you doing?
- I want to see your finger.
What the...?
You came into direct contact with spores that.
Why did not you report this, you know the rules.
Yes, because you're only THII rules,
not dom 'Colonel?
- We have rules for a reason specifically.
- "Normal"...?
Cam What to do when a crew member is sick
Fish
After he saved the lives of all?
Fuck you!
Cameron, Dr. Krauss
tighten up and realizes what the hell is wrong with you,
are forced pertain to you under observation.
You mean I closed  If you give me
way, all put lives in danger.
You know I do not give in to threats.
You will arrive at the court martial after that.
I know I saw something,
was not a nightmare.
- Cameron...
- If not let me go,
-... all put lives in danger!
- Cameron!
There's nothing there, suffering from exposure,
have to put you in isolation.
Come back!
Let go of me!
- Colonel!
- Bastards...
Let me see.
- Let's check it out.
- Da...
What happened in the hallway?
Apparently knock hierarchy.
I attacked Bruce and lost minds.
Go and finds it, I want an explanation
.
Fuck, door!
Bruce...?
Ava...
Bruce!
I know you're here.
I'm not afraid of you.
Fuck, Fuck...
What the fuck is wrong with me...?
What the fuck is wrong with me?
O Lord...
Fuck!
Cameron...
Come on, wake up, ending
fannies!
Who gave you the way?
to let you hurt me.
Ava, I came
to hurt you.
Company are rules, and you have to tell
pertain locked.
I'm not gonna put in that cell.
Something happened here and you do not believe me.
Do not make me have to do bad, please.
What the hell happened?
I attacked.
Let 's covenant.
Let's see what you got.
Hold on a
Good...
What...
What?
Stop !
Stop! What?
Stop!
Do you have an explanation for this?
Yes, I have. I threatened,
and the rules...
Regulation requires to put in solitary confinement for not Think
clear.
Was stabilized until you went there without
you talk to me.
And who issued it?
Bruce.
Look... I watched the tapes
.
Cameron to cut my finger with a test tube which was a bonus
that's why.
Do not believe me?
Look at her right index finger.
E infection.
- What's this?
- An alarm.
- I know "what". But why?
- As an additional precaution.
You  pertain under observation,
antibiotics that make you gave them are very strong.
I had to defend myself, right?
I'm not crazy!
Why did you hide such a thing from me?
I was scared...
A little of me exited,
is not it?
I Tell me...
I saw something here.
I was not dreaming.
I have to go.
Now I can not do that.
're Making a huge mistake.
Ask Bruce.
I Bruce, open the door
Bruce! Open!
I No matter what may come out of it
Ava...
I is here.
I can see it.
I Blestemãþia that... pursues me.
I'm studying
're Driving me crazy and I .
I think I'll die...
Bruce...?
No, Bruce!
Fuck!
Jesus!
- What happened?
- Bruce came.
He tried to kill me.
- When?
- Now, a few seconds!
- Bruce is dead.
- Impossible was just here.
No matter what you think you saw,
May Think about it, because there was Bruce.
Colonel...
Is there anything to do with us to the resort.
Incubated in
Ava and now turned into a copy of Bruce.
Both were infected spores!
Vent wells was used
to move.
When you have to kill him.
And
Ava we need to help us.
Ava...
Bruce is dead.
How do you know that?
Making sense.
Ava, we need your help.
You could be the only one who can control.
And I do not now.
Mo used to be is born, but now
are a threat to him, and as you.
Suppose
took a sample of his DNA to Bruce when bitten.
And I realized that a male is stronger physically
,
so in one copy,
to survive.
But we still need your help.
Can we trust you?
You can trust me.
Here ARK monthly basis,
log entry 184.
We have evidence of alien life forms
.
A used lt's body. Cameron as host
and now turned into a life form resistance.
Looks damn
decided to kill us.
Took human form
should be easier to find.
Something is not right.
Offer compressor pumps.
We cut the oxygen reserves.
A disused chimney three.
Trying to destroy the system.
It makes no sense, if dropped Statham
will die with us.
He knows, by Bruce,
Where escape capsule.
I will try to override the system.
See if it can find!
Go with you.
Cad compressors!
Gimme  lamp.
- Cut hose!
- You can make a derivation?
- How's that?
- Baga oxygen.
Come quickly, come!
- What are you doing?
- I know they were trying to kill him.
Ava...
Position us know by me.
- Damn it, Cameron, stay with us!
- Ava, come back!
Bitch...
- Ava!
- Wait.
I Danger! Locks open.
Fault system.
Take the Ava safe.
I close my shield!
This is crazy! We can not override
hatch here!
I Danger! Locks open.
Fault system.
Give me your hand!
overridden system.
No!
I block system.
Evacuation begins in 30 seconds.
Damn!
I block system.
Access denied.
Get me out of here!
Must have an open soon!
- Do not go.
- Try again.
I Ten, nine...
I Eight, seven...
I Six, five...
= = I four...
I Three...
I Two...
I One.
It returns...
- I can not stop!
- Bruce to go to his cabin.
Can
discovered something about him that would help us. Come on!
Come motion!
Christ...
I fuck me...
I'm not crazy
has several entries in the log.
I thing,
who grew up in Ava...
I I
crew could reveal that I was infected, because...
= =
I can not risk putting me in solitary.
I know what I must do,
cloned himself in me.
's me one to copy.
I am afraid of what may become afterward.
I What a be its original form.
I can...
Maybe it developing in form
human would be killed easily.
I'm thinking to carbon monoxide.
When I watch it now ,
I only way to survive is to
Get out the escape capsule.
- How long does it take to preparing your dish?
- Too much.
Unless...
Sacrifice the whole station to all the energy directed toward launch.
To do.
If you start it, there's no place's back.
We have one chance.
Then take advantage of it.
We need this
capsule prepared for the final ascent.
There is an emergency contact in the roof span. It engages.
Coming in here.
Ava!
O can do.
A and A. ..
Let's see what we have here.
Am diverted supply pipes.
I Turn everything when you're ready.
'm on my way.
It returns...
- It's okay, it's me.
- I do not see anything.
- Thou hast prepared?
- Cells will be at 80% when we arrive.
Okay, let's go.
- I have not flashlight.
- Together, come on.
I hazard. Carbon monoxide,
Level 4 and rising.
I hazard.
Oxygen low.
E monoxide.
No sense we fish poisoning everybody.
Try what he said to Bruce's
get them to kill us.
Opened lock
span two.
Go to  capsule and starts the launch sequence
. Go!
No need
to stay together.
Can not coordinate release unless you're there. Go!
Go!
I hazard.
Oxygen low.
I hazard. Carbon monoxide,
Level 2 and rising.
bitch!
Look-a and a ..
I launch sequence,
turned on.
Ava! We started launching.
Enter get your code!
Ava copy?
Ava!
I carbon monoxide,
in Level 3.
I launch in three minutes.
We are the 80%.
Gerard, descends once.
I hazard.
Oxygen low.
Gerard! It is here in the bay
Release!
launch in two minutes.
Gerard!
Breathe!
Come!
I launch into a minute.
bastards!
Is blocked.
I can override it.
Need to stop the launch.
Opening!
I launch in 30 seconds.
Get in there!
I All schemes prepared.
Launch, start.
- Close roof capsule.
- That's what I try to do.
I... nine, eight...
I... Seven, six, five...
I... Four , three, two...
I One. Release.
Fuck!
I've done.
All-units were empty.
View in tanks
emergency.
Oxygen available for 17 minutes.
We have 17 minutes.
To be true...?
Here colonel Brauchman.
I have an urgent message.
I have lost contact with the base on Earth.
I have a message for Captain Madsen emergency.
Is an emergency broadcast,
are Brauchman colonel.
Answer!
-'s Beacon rescue shuttle.
- God, how timely!
Aselenizeazã.
- Do you think you will arrive on time?
- Fifty-fifty.
Or sit here and pray to God
to reach us...
Or...
've got three minutes until landing dock.
Can you hold your breath
three minutes and a half to run?
Da...
Tail, wait.
Cap, we run overkill.
Fuck... Come on!
Still no communication from monthly basis.
We only beacon pod.
Hatch must be open at impact.
No sign of life.
Na exited anyone here, I see traces
.
Escape pods have to be docked from now.
Let's hope we find some answers.
Until then, keep quiet.
- You called the Task Force?
- I'll be here in ten minutes.
Crows capsule basic coverage.
Breathing thing, get on all networks.
Isolated area, and enter
nobody gets out.
Sir, I think it would be
to see this.
Base, this colonel Brauchman,
reporting the USS Magellan spacecraft.
I Madsen, any
out of that pod, kill him.
Do not benevolent
killed by Krauss and the Johns.
I is clearly a threat to humanity.
Translation: FROM Romanian Utilizator
by. Matrixz